<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sat May  6 00:10:38 2023-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Enlightenment from Dreamland</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The secret association of &quot;Enlightenment of Dreamlike Fantasyland&quot; can be upgraded and unlocked earlier, which can increase the city's charm value and [ICON_Amenities] livability; the population becomes higher quality, which will increase the additional output per population of [ICON_Citizen].</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_TITLE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>secret society</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_SHORT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dreamlike Gensokyo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_SHORT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dreamlike Gensokyo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_DISCOVERY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After you passed by an inconspicuous village, the villagers there were having a banquet. You participated in the banquet and learned about a place called Gensokyo from their customs. At first, you thought it was just crazy talk. But after waking up the next day, the village became dilapidated, as if no one had lived in it for a long time. Just when you felt that you had lost an adventure and opportunity, a villager you saw at the banquet dangled from a house Walking out in a hurry, it seems that the opportunity has come again.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_MEMBERSHIP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You returned to the capital together. After some cross-examination, you began to understand this place called &quot;Gensokyo&quot;, and tried to contact the various existences of Gensokyo through the realm and back and forth. After various considerations, you decided to slowly become them. members of . [NEWLINE]*ah shit, this is good*</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>home of fantasy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[COLOR_RED]This association upgrade unlocks faster[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City +1 plot charm value, city +1 [ICON_Amenities] amenity, each [ICON_Citizen] population +0.5 [ICON_FAITH] faith value +0.3 [ICON_Production ] Productivity</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Great Enchantment</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>City +2 plot charm value, units within 4 blocks of the city +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power, if the city's plot charm value reaches 7, each [ICON_Citizen] population +0.5 [ICON_Culture] culture value +0.7 [ICON_FAITH] Faith +0.7 [ICON_Production] Production</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODIFIER_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_STR_NEAR_COUNTRY_GET_YES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+5 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength from Hakurei Great Barrier</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Spell Card Rules</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>City +3 plot charm value, city ecstatic output bonus +30% (half if it is happy), each [ICON_Citizen] population +0.8 [ICON_Culture] culture value +0.8 [ICON_FAITH] faith value +1 [ICON_Production] Production</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Millennium Fantasy Township</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>City +3 [ICON_Amenities] Amenity, plots whose charm value reaches 10 +3 [ICON_Production] Productivity +3 [ICON_Science] Technology +3 [ICON_Culture] Culture, per [ICON_Citizen] population +2 [ICON_Production] Productivity +1.5 [ICON_Science] Technology +1.5 [ICON_Culture] Culture</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo is the main stage of the Touhou Project series of stories, and is often used to refer to the entire Touhou Project world. [NEWLINE] Gensokyo used to be a place known as &quot;the frontier of the eastern country far away from human villages&quot;, hidden deep in a certain mountain in Japan. [NEWLINE] Even so, it is impossible to travel between Gensokyo and the outside world by ordinary means, because it is cut off by the barrier of common sense &quot;Hakurei Great Barrier&quot;. [NEWLINE] If there is anything special about Gensokyo, it is of course—youkai, gods, magic, and other fantasies that are regarded as &quot;uncommon&quot; or &quot;non-existent&quot; in reality are all taken for granted here . [NEWLINE]To be denied, to be forgotten, to be the destination of fantasy things, that is Gensokyo. [NEWLINE]Here, humans still fear gods and talk about monsters. [NEWLINE]Whether witches can fly in the air, vampires release blood-red mist, winter and night will not end, or a saint is resurrected suddenly... [NEWLINE]Monsters and other inhuman things set off changes, The heroes among human beings go to deal with it, this is the daily life of Gensokyo.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_SECRETSOCIETY_TH_SC_TANSHOU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo was originally part of the outside world, and the geographical concept of Gensokyo has existed for at least 1,200 years. [NEWLINE] More than five hundred years ago, due to the increase in population, in order to restore the power of youkai oppressed by humans in Gensokyo, Yakumo Murasaki, who manipulated the realm, planned and implemented a plan to expand youkai. A realm of fantasy and reality is created around Gensokyo. The inside of Gensokyo is a fantasy world, and the outside world is a real world. The monsters whose power has weakened in the outside world will be automatically summoned by Gensokyo. Since then, youkai have also immigrated from countries other than Japan. The effect of the realm is still ongoing. Also, the cleverness of this plan is that the more youkai in the outside world disappear, the stronger the youkai in Gensokyo. The outside world is dominated by humans, while the inside of Gensokyo is still dominated by monsters. [NEWLINE] About Meiji 18 (1885), sages including Yakumo Zi created the Hakurei Great Barrier to separate Gensokyo from the outside world. Neither humans nor youkai can easily travel between Gensokyo and the outside world unless they are summoned by the realm of fantasy and reality or hidden by the gods. However, at first a large number of monsters united against it, and a fight broke out between the sages and the monsters. During this period, the monsters did not attack humans, and the humans in Gensokyo began to praise the Great Barrier. As a result, the benefits of the Great Barrier spread to the monsters, and now there are almost no people who oppose this Barrier. [NEWLINE]Humans and youkai have undergone tremendous changes since the Hakurei Great Barrier was created. Whether it is human beings who are very afraid of youkai, or human beings who actively fight against youkai for a living, they no longer exist. In Gensokyo now, monsters will go to human villages to have fun, and humans will be entertained by demons to their homes. It is rare for humans to be eaten by monsters. However, because of this, Gensokyo experienced a crisis after a hundred years. That is, after the monsters stopped attacking humans, the power of the monsters began to weaken. If new monsters flow into Gensokyo after being extinct outside, the original monsters in Gensokyo will lose to the new monsters, and Gensokyo will be dominated by the new monsters. Some people will say that Gensokyo will collapse because of the Great Barrier. [NEWLINE]At this moment, a powerful monster, the vampire, broke in from the outside world. Soon the vampire recruited a large number of monsters as subordinates. As a result of the turmoil, the most powerful monster defeated the vampire, and concluded a contract with him for various forbidden things, and reached a settlement. The commotion became known as the Vampire Mutation. Afterwards, Yokai and Hakurei Miko discussed and introduced the spell card rules. That is a simulated battle in the form of a duel. Let both monsters and humans continue to fight. Monsters attack humans, and humans retreat from monsters. Even if it is simulated, monsters can maintain their strength. Since then, mutations have occurred frequently everywhere, but they will not leave troubles after they are resolved. The mutation is repeated until the Miko wins. Once the winner is determined, the game is over. The red mist mutation in the first Th06 Dongfang Red Demon Township in Dongfang's new work is the first mutation that applies the rules of spell cards.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
