<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Mon Dec 30 00:10:06 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yan is a country located in the easternmost part of Terra continent, with a vast territory. Not many people have ever been to the heart of Yan, but the stories about the strange people and events in this country have never stopped.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In the public history of Da Yan, thousands of years ago, giant beasts and evil spirits were rampant on Yan land. A certain Da Yan emperor lamented the natural disasters and man-made disasters on the land, and decided to mobilize the whole country to recruit talents, lead the army in person, and kill the gods. Among them, the giant beast that the real dragon first saw &quot;betrayed its own people and divided its own power&quot; and participated in this rare hunt.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although the blood flowed like a river and corpses lay for thousands of miles, Da Yan paid a painful price and the controversy was rampant, but the True Dragon never stopped the pace of killing the gods, and eventually drove all the giant beasts and evil demons except the original giant beasts out of the territory of Da Yan. The True Dragon spared its life and only required it to submit to Da Yan.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>From then on, the fate of the Great Yan nation was only in the hands of the True Dragon and the people of the Great Yan. This was the amazing &quot;myth&quot; of &quot;ennobling the gods&quot; during the long changes of the Terran nations.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>But in fact, the Sui Beast issue has always been a highly confidential matter in Yan State, so the real situation does not completely conform to the above description.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The &quot;first giant beast&quot; is Sui, who is interested in the war between humans and his own kind, and uses his power to send down &quot;divine signs&quot; to help the Yan army defeat his own kind. But since the beginning of the war to kill the gods, Sui has been on the list of gods to kill. After the Yan army killed Sui, Sui fell asleep in hatred and doubt, and was divided into twelve fragments and scattered all over Da Yan. These fragments have part of Sui's power, and are monitored and restricted by court commissioners to prevent them from causing chaos again.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As the resurrection of the Year Beast approaches and the layout of the &quot;Second Brother&quot; of Shangshu City begins, the Year Beast problem is imminent. Once the Year Beast wakes up, not only will Da Yan face the giant beast again, but the existing twelve fragments will also return to one and disappear from everyone's memory. Rhodes Island, Yan State officials, and the Year Beast fragments are all working hard to prevent the Year Beast from waking up.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SHU_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Millet</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SHU_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Millet</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SHU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;There is a beast with a pale color and a thousand-mile-long aura. Its number is six. It carries things without making a sound. When it wakes up, it knocks on the walls and hits the earth. The nine regions are at peace. When it closes, disasters and anomalies are rampant. Its fate is unpredictable. Karma is hard to escape. The result follows the cause. Therefore, it embraces the state and carries the earth. It controls the time with its body in the four directions. The cycle of reincarnation never changes. The stars move and things change. The heart withers and flourishes, and the valleys remain green.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHONGYUE_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chongyue</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHONGYUE_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chongyue</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHONGYUE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;There is a beast howling in the clear sky. Clouds and mists are heavy and round. Their number is one. Dark and bright are just beginning to take shape. Black and transparent, their whole body is not stiff. It is hard to catch. I bend my head to find. What is closed and dark? What is opened and bright? I can see as far as I can. How big is the impact of a emaciated insect? What realm can a common man reach? Then the soldiers fight and become huts. ■■■ bodies ■■ with the same strength. ■■■■ reverse and match. Heaven and earth are like reverse. Extremely sad. Cicadas are like this. It is easy to stop fighting. But for the sake of seeking, the clouds have dried and the smoke has dissipated. All things are lonely.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LING_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>make</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LING_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>make</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LING_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;There are beasts that sleep alone in the mountains. There are three of them, with spines and bones. Their breath is as faint as the sun and moon, and their voices are as mute as a thousand bells. They are dark black and deep, with the color of scales and toes. The mountains have lost their weight and their shapes are no longer visible. The water has disappeared and the leeches have disappeared, and their voices are no longer heard. When you feel them, you will see the future. Good and bad things will come in all directions, and they will turn muddy and clear. When you meet them, they will wander thousands of feet high, and they will stop fighting and take on poetic forms. People value tools more than animals, and beasts sympathize with emotions. The long river is far away, and I will bury my body beneath it. I will be free.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_JIUSELU_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Nine-Colored Deer</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_JIUSELU_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Nine-Colored Deer</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_JIUSELU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In her early years, Jiuselu had traveled around Dayan, practicing medicine and saving lives everywhere. Saving the dying and the wounded without asking for anything in return is her motto. When passing through a village that had just suffered a natural disaster, she stopped and stayed there to rescue the wounded. She faced people with the greatest kindness, but unfortunately she did not receive their kindness. At that time, communications in the village had been interrupted, and the medical supplies and medicines in stock were seriously insufficient. More and more patients fell down due to lack of adequate medication. In order to fill the gap in the lack of medicine, she and the only remaining doctor in the village had to go to the nearby mountains and forests to find herbs. She firmly believed that she could lead this village, which had nothing left, out of danger. But things went against her wishes, and rumors began to spread among the already fragile people. In the rumors, Jiuselu changed from a doctor to a villain who brought disaster.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_JIUSELU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;This woman stayed here just to promote her medicine and gain everyone's trust!&quot; &quot;Look at her Originium skills! She brought the disaster!&quot; She had to face not only the patients groaning in pain, but also the unpredictable human heart. Although she never paid attention to the villagers' gossip, these rumors corroded some people's hearts. Finally, some rude villagers gathered in front of her and forcibly demanded that &quot;Elafia, the disaster-bringer&quot; leave this place.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_JIUSELU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Finally, she gave the doctor a book of treatments for various diseases and the recipes for making herbal pills, and she walked a long way to the nearest town to let the outside world know that the village still needed help. Then she left and went to the mountains to seek a quiet place.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_JIUSELU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>However, the mountain was not always peaceful. There were always patients who needed help at the clinic at the foot of the mountain. After much hesitation, she finally sent the herbs to the doctor. Fortunately, the same situation did not occur here. She still adhered to her principles. She firmly believed that healing the heart was more important than healing the body.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_WEIYW_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wei Yanwu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_WEIYW_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wei Yanwu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_WEIYW_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Politician, ruler of Longmen. He is wise and polite, but also good at strategy and tough. He has a high reputation in the political circle. Relying on unique diplomatic and business strategies, he has made Longmen, an isolated city, handle political relations with various countries with ease. He is considered one of the outstanding leaders of the contemporary era. The current rapid development of Longmen is the best proof of this. It is rumored that due to his past career, his physical fitness is beyond ordinary people.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SWIRE_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shi Huaiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SWIRE_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shi Huaiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SWIRE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Miss Shi Huaiya does not shy away from her investment in Xiosta.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SWIRE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>She would &quot;occasionally&quot; pass by the Engineering Department with the design drawings for the expansion of the water park, and get some free ideas that were not in line with business logic; she would also suddenly pick up Operator Xue Zhi who had just finished her field work, saying that she wanted to &quot;have the chief designer attend the ribbon-cutting ceremony&quot;, and then ask Xue Zhi to produce some new design drawings.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SWIRE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Under her command, a water park that is as fun as the Obsidian Music Festival has been built as planned, and is expanding in size and attracting tourists. Operator Xuezhi earned enough money from this trip that she couldn't save for many years, and obtained various design patents. With this trip, Miss Shi Huaiya and Baisong truly entered the torrent of Terra's cross-border logistics and trade.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SWIRE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fenglian Trading is in a period of steady development. The success of the fledgling cross-border trade in Xista gave the two young people the confidence to move forward. Their next stop, Longmen - Yanguo's most important external port city - is also waiting for a new atmosphere. Compared with the ultimate goal of connecting the entire land, what the two young people are doing now can only be regarded as a small step, but this small and determined step has already aroused the echo of the times.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SWIRE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;What's the point of following the old generation and fighting for what they left behind? If we want to do something, we have to open up new markets. What I can do is not only to maintain the law and order of Longmen, I also have the power to build it.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_SWIRE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The various forces of the Longmen Chamber of Commerce are constantly competing and playing games. The names of various groups are also printed in large fonts on the scaffolding of Xiosta's new high-rise building. Xiosta is facing a transformation, and so is Miss Shi Huaiya. Regardless of which side, they have already given a gratifying answer.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>List</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>List</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chen graduated from the Victoria Royal Guards School with all A's in regular subjects and all instructor recommendations. After returning to Longmen, she almost immediately joined the Longmen Guards.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>No one knew her experience before she entered the Royal Guards School, just as no one doubted her ability, her dedication to duty, and her hatred of evil. Police officers who had worked with the Guards Bureau had complained about Chen's style of doing things - too strict and too harsh. Almost everyone believed that Chen would disappear in the power struggle, and her sharpness would soon be polished away by endless incidents.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>To everyone's surprise, crime and casualty rates have fallen for two consecutive years, and the promotion of the younger generation of police officers has become faster and more substantial. Chen has been promoted step by step and joined one of the most important teams in the Guard Bureau, the Special Inspectorate.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The term of office of the special inspector team members generally does not exceed two years - to protect the lives of police officers or to reduce the possibility of mistakes caused by their accumulated stress. Perhaps this position itself is not suitable for long-term stay: heroic death in the mission is almost the consistent ending of all old inspectors.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chen did not retreat at all. She had never retreated, would not retreat, and did not know how to retreat.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>She became the fastest promoted officer in the history of Longmen Police, and also the youngest leader of the Special Inspectorate of the Guard Bureau. Those who had mocked her or secretly slandered her were all impressed by her courage and perseverance. After all, having a plan for the future is one thing, and executing the plan every day is another.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CHEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Why did she work so hard? Why did she devote her life to such an extent? No one understood, and no one could understand. In Chen's wastebasket, there were often torn or crumpled pages filled with inexplicable anger.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
