<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun Jul 16 19:54:45 2023-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_CONCERTO_DAL_CIELO_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Citizens can improve mountain tiles, mountains provide +2 [ICON_Production] production, frozen soil and snow have the same output as plains (tundra provides +1 [ICON_Production] production, snow provides +1 [ICON_Production] production +1 [ICON_Food] food). Non-wonder buildings with [ICON_GreatWork_Writing] writing or [ICON_GreatWork_Music] music slots give +1 charm to the city's plot.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_CONCERTO_DAL_CIELO_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gao Tian's concerto</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wendy (Barbatos)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_SHINING_MIRACLE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The recruited rock band initially has the [ICON_Promotion] promotion of religious rock, and it only takes half the usual time to build the Holy Land and Theater Square area. Has an additional unique unit, Priest Priest, replacing Guru.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_SHINING_MIRACLE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>shining miracle</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>barbara</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_RITES_OF_TERMINATION_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The tavern provides an additional [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] relic slot, and the city where the tavern is located has +20% [ICON_Faith] Faith. Has an additional unique unit, the Sister of the Crown of Thorns, which replaces the Inquisitor.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_RITES_OF_TERMINATION_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>life-long sacrament</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rosalia</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_DEACONESS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Prayer Priest</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_DEACONESS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Provides additional recovery to nearby units within 1 cell. Units adjacent to the praying priest have +15 [ICON_Religion] religious combat power.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SPINEA_CORONA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sister Crown of Thorns</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SPINEA_CORONA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If the Sister of the Crown of Thorns dies in a Theology battle, a relic will spawn. +10 [ICON_Religion] Religious Combat Power when fighting Theological Combat in the country's borders.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LAND_OF_WIND_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>land of wind</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LAND_OF_WIND_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_AGENDA_DESTINATION_CIV_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_DEACONESS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>glorious season</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_DEACONESS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Provides additional recovery to nearby units within 1 cell. Units adjacent to Priests have increased religious combat power.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_SPINEA_CORONA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>confession of guilt</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_SPINEA_CORONA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If the Sister of the Crown of Thorns dies in a Theology battle, a relic will spawn. [ICON_Religion] Religious combat power is lower, but [ICON_Religion] Religious combat power is doubled when fighting theological battles in the country's borders.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_DEACONESS_STRENGTH_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>pure bond</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_DEACONESS_STRENGTH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Units adjacent to the praying priest have +15 [ICON_Religion] religious combat power.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z" Language="en_US">
			<Text>He is not only the praying pastor of Westwind Church, but also the shining idol of Mond City. For Mond, who is used to traditional bards, &quot;idol&quot; is a new thing that he is not used to. But in Mond, everyone loves Barbara. Such is the free spirit of the Free City--so gratefully Barbara sums it up for all the favors.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rosalia - a nun affiliated with the West Wind Church in Mond City. Except for weird nuns who don't look like priests in any way. Cold, sharp, a woman as sharp as a blade. Unpredictable whereabouts, often leave without saying goodbye. Has a mission, but people don't seem to understand what she represents...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_QUOTE}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The most amazing magic is real effort.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>choir? I'm sorry, I don't participate in church activities, and don't look for me when I work overtime</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_SPINEA_CORONA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The maverick Rosalia is simply a church figure. But please don't forget: if there is black, there will be corresponding white; where there is light, there must be shadow</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DEACONESS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Barbara is the Priest of the Zephyr Knights. She heals wounds with water elements, and soothes people's tired hearts with singing. In the hearts of the Monds, Barbara possesses magical magic that can heal the patient's body and mind—and in Barbara's heart, this magic is called &quot;practical effort.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As the demon god Barbatos has the ability to use mountains and blow away ice and snow.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mond, led by the demon god Barbatos, is a civilization that focuses on culture and beliefs. He uses taverns and broadcasting centers to create high-charm plots, and recruits more naturalists from the beliefs brought by the bonuses of taverns. Construct national parks in mountainous and high-attraction land to obtain high tourism performance and more easily obtain cultural victories.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Barbara is a devout pastor of the Zephyr church more likely to win religious victories</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As a praying priest, Barbara has a unique unit, praying priests. Using the characteristics of civilization and the high amount of faith produced in characteristic building taverns, recruit more praying priests to provide high religious combat power bonuses for religious battles. . When Rock Band can be recruited, use Religious Rock's ability to take down a Religious Victory in one fell swoop</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rosalia uses the advantages of religion and belief while using relics to accumulate tourism performance</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rosalia, who walks in the dark night, guards the young and ancient city. The characteristic unit, the Sister of the Crown of Thorns, can sweep away the religious forces that do not belong to Mond, and maintains an absolute advantage in super-high religious battles in the country. The relics left by the Sister of the Crown of Thorns' death, combined with the additional relic slot, make it easier to obtain tourism performance .</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wendy was originally an elemental spirit among the thousand winds of Mond. In Old Mond, Wendy met a boy. The boy led the people to rebel against the tyrant Dekarapian who ruled them. In the end, the tyrant fell and the boy died in battle. Wendy gains power to become the new god, Barbatos the Demon God. Andreus, the demon god who has been fighting with Dekarapian, also chose to leave because of his own characteristics. The Demon God War ended, and the Demon God Barbatos became the God of Wind, one of the seven rulers in the world. In order to commemorate her friend, the first thing Wendy did after gaining the supernatural power was to reshape her body with the appearance of a boy, played her friend's favorite harp, and walked in the world with this boy's body ever since.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Afterwards, Barbatos-Wendy imparted his wisdom to the Mond people, modified the terrain of the current Mond area, migrated from Old Mond (now the ruins of Fenglong) and settled down, setting up many festivals and celebrations. Later, Wendy left Mond because she didn't want to become a new tyrant, making Mond an autonomous free state. After the demon war ended, Fengshen went to Liyue, a neighboring country, to invite Yanshen to taste dandelion wine. Since then, the original seven gods have met in Liyue many times.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>About 1600 after the completion of New Mond, the nobles headed by the Lawrence family took control of Mond, and Wendy woke up again in response to the prayers of his followers. Walking in Mond City as a bard, I found that the atmosphere in the city was extremely depressing. On the day of the Badminton Festival, I played &quot;Song of the Wind&quot;, which has not been played for a long time, to an Apple vendor, and was warned by the vendor, &quot;Don't touch that shuttlecock.&quot; During the celebration, I found out about the absurd and brutal behavior of the nobleman, stepped forward to snatch the badminton to play with the nobleman, was chased and killed by the soldiers, met Vanessa on the way to escape, and got her cover. Vanessa was arrested for offending the nobles. Wendy got the cell key that night and entered the cell to talk to Vanessa. Wendy wants to escape Mund with Vanessa and her people. But Vanessa said that her people have forgotten the meaning of &quot;freedom&quot;, and they have to participate in the duel on the second day anyway to awaken the people's sense of resistance and freedom, otherwise they will only be shackled by another power. .</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The next day, the nobles shamelessly drove all the Vanessa clan out of the city, demanding that they defeat the dragon Uzzah, and shot and killed the retreating people with arrows. At this time, Wendy suddenly appeared, guided the power of the wind to make Vanessa hit the dragon, and used divine power to order the dragon to retreat. At this time, Wendy asked to write Vanessa into the poem, and was agreed, saying that this would be a new chapter with the Vanessa family as the protagonist. In the end, Lawrence was asked to follow the rules and hand over control of Mond. In addition, by forging Morax's signature to create the &quot;Secret Treaty of Leeward&quot;, a large number of soldiers rebelled, and together with Vanessa, they overthrew the aristocratic rule. The followers of the wind god Barbatos form the Guardians of the Four Winds. Fengshen left again.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>500 years ago, all the gods, including the god of wind, came together and destroyed Kerriya. The Calamity of Kerriya spread throughout Teyvat. The dragon Durin and the dark wave of monsters attacked Mond together, and the Zephyr Knights fought hard. Fengshen and his family member Twalin fought against Dulin together, and finally cut Dulin off the snow mountain. The wind god and the wind dragon corrupted by the poisonous blood of the dragon fell into a deep sleep.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>His father, Simon Page, is the bishop of the Westwind Church, known as the &quot;Cardinal of the Dawn&quot;. His mother, Frederica, comes from the Gunnhild family, and her sister, Qin, is the pride of the family. Barbara can't surpass it only by hard work people. The parents' marriage split and they went their separate ways, with Barbara following her father and Jean following her mother. Stimulated by a little competitive spirit, Barbara tried to catch up with her sister in swordsmanship, but after realizing that she was not good at fighting, Barbara chose to be in charge of logistics. Under the guidance of his father, he became a healer.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Influenced by Alice, Barbara has now become an idol in Mond City. Currently, my father is traveling with the head of the north wind knight Falga.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Born in a mountain village, he was taken away by a group of bandits who slaughtered the village, and trained as a thief and a servant. She was discovered by the old thief who captured her during a sneak escape, and the old thief asked Rosalia to duel with him in exchange for the chance to leave. Rosalia was victorious, granted the Eye of God, and accepted into the band of thieves. A few years later, the Thieves Group was wiped out by the Zephyr Knights. Because she was young, Rosalia was considered to have room for repentance. She was brought back to Mond by the head of the group, Falga, and was incorporated into the Zephyr Church as a nun to study. Skipping class. Later, he secretly handled the danger for Mond, but still attached to the Westwind Church, which always broke the hearts of Sister Victoria and Barbara.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't force yourself, you can call me if you have any difficulties.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh, the obvious camouflage.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If one day you encounter a problem that cannot be solved. Maybe I'll solve the problem for you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't force yourself, you can call me if you have any difficulties.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Who knows? Everything always has two sides.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>pray. Not for God or anyone else, but for yourself.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tremble!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Would you like a drink? This is the dandelion wine of the year, and it tastes very good.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tch, trouble.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I think we share similar tastes in many ways.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>But that's all.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A slick, hypocritical and cunning person. You threatened Mond. (condemns you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Get your work done and enjoy every day. Isn't that what Mond's life is like?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This believer, if you have troubles that are difficult to solve, you can come to me.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Skip the pleasantries. I'm here to get work done.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you need help? I have time now.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hope it goes well.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Is there anyone or something you want to deal with? I can do a little favor, just don't tell anyone else.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tsk, what a hassle!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Maybe it's... destiny...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...but there are some good ones too.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is not my area of ​​interest.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>fair enough</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>God may protect everyone, but He won't do it. Otherwise, human suffering becomes a joke.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There are two tricks!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's okay, not too much trouble.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Alas, nothing but trouble is trouble.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>sorry to bother you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My wish is to bring smiles to everyone around me! As long as I can help you, I will be very happy.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>sorry, not yet... not yet</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If only I could help everyone.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I will pray for you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, never mind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>no, not good...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Barbara go!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Today is lucky day!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you, but sorry.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Please accept it! Wait for the next new song, I will sing it to you as soon as possible!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...why is this happening.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>hate... (condemn you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Barbara, come on stage~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Leave the treatment to me, you won't be disappointed!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If you become an idol too, I will definitely support you with all my strength.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I will work hard to be worthy of your trust...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you like spicy small dried fish? I have two more here...here, here's one for you!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for accompanying me to the present, I am getting closer and closer to my dream. Please take care of me in the days to come~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I don't like it very much.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I can't hear everyone's voice...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mmmmm♪ What a lucky day~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Eh? ask me? Well... Anyway, it's just a second.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Everyone will have their own wishes.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The wind that guides me. Give me the strength to move on when I am stumped, give me the wisdom to discern good and evil when I am confused, and give me the courage to fight when I suffer from injustice...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Huh...huh...no problem!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Just leave it to me.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sorry, it's not...it's time for the show yet.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for your support~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SPINEA_CORONA_FRIENDLY_TERRITORY_COMBAT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Sister Crown of Thorns gets an additional [ICON_Strength] combat strength bonus when she is in friendly territory.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DEACONESS_STRENGTH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gain +15 [ICON_Religion] Religious Combat Strength when adjacent to Priests.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
