<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun Aug  4 17:38:29 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_SULEIMAN_GOVERNOR_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The greatest sultan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_SULEIMAN_GOVERNOR_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Exclusive unique Governor with military and diplomatic abilities. After researching the &quot;Gunpowder&quot; technology, he gains the unique unit &quot;Janis&quot; and a Governor title of [Icon_Governor]. Unlocks Military Engineering at the start. When in the [ICON_GLORY_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age or Heroic Age, +15% [Icon_Science] and [Icon_Culture] Culture. When not in the [ICON_GLORY_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age or Heroic Age, he gains +5 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gunpowder and conquest</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_GREAT_TURKISH_BOMBARD_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_Production] Production when producing siege units. Allows recruitment of Dardanelles Cannon. +5 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength for units that consume gunpowder. No [ICON_Citizen] Population loss when conquering cities. +1 [ICON_AMENITIES] Amenity, +4 Loyalty, and +15% [Icon_Science] and [ICON_Culture] Culture output per turn for non-Ottoman-founded cities.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_GRAND_BAZAAR_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ottoman unique building. Each different strategic resource improved in this city gives 1 additional point. Each luxury resource improved in this city gives 1 [ICON_AMENITIES] Amenity. +2 [ICON_Culture] Culture to trade routes from this city. +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to international [ICON_TRADEROUTE] trade routes from this city for each strategic resource in this city.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_OTTOMAN_BARBARY_CORSAIR_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unique Medieval Ottoman naval unit that replaces the Privateer. Does not cost [ICON_Movement] movement to perform a coastal sweep. Can only be spotted by other Naval Raiders unless adjacent to a unit. Can reveal the position of Naval Raiders within line of sight.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SFDH100_DARDANELLES_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dardanelles stone-throwing cannon</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SFDH100_DARDANELLES_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A unique Ottoman siege unit from the Renaissance era, replacing the Stone Cannon, unlocked with the Metal Casting technology. Has a higher combat power, suitable for attacking cities. Cannot move and attack in one turn (unless it has the Expert Group upgrade).</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_GAUL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mines provide a small adjacency bonus to all regions, cast culture bombs on unowned territory, and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] culture.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_OPPIDUM_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A Gallic unique district that replaces the Industrial District. It costs less to build and appears earlier. The Oppidum District is defensive and has ranged attacks. It cannot be built next to a City Center. Once this district is built, the Apprentice technology is unlocked. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add +1 [ICON_Production] Production per adjacent Quarry Improvement or Strategic Resource.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_HANSA_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A German unique industrial district that replaces an industrial zone. It is cheaper to build. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gives a +2 [ICON_Production] productivity bonus from each adjacent Commercial Center. Each adjacent Resource gives it 1 [ICON_Production] productivity bonus.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ELECTRONICS_FACTORY_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unique Japanese building. Provides 0.5 [ICON_Production] productivity per population point. Its [ICON_Production] productivity bonus extends to all city centers within 6 tiles, and after researching &quot;Electricity&quot; technology, it provides +5 [ICON_Culture] culture to the surrounding 6 tiles (provided it does not already have a bonus from other buildings of this type). [NEWLINE]For each Electronics Factory in the country, foreign trade routes from cities with Electronics Factory will receive +3 [ICON_Gold] gold.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_MAGNANIMOUS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My beloved motherland</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_MAGNANIMOUS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Reduces the Faith [ICON_Faith] required to sponsor a Great Person by 25%, and increases production by 50% [ICON_Production] when building academies, industrial zones, and ports.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_AMAZON_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rainforest Country</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_AMAZON_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unimproved Rainforest tiles gain +1 [ICON_Faith] Faith and +1 [ICON_Production] Production. Civilian and Scout units gain +2 [ICON_Movement] Movement if they start their turn in a Rainforest. City Centers gain 1 [ICON_Science] Science per turn for each adjacent Rainforest tile. Rainforests provide the standard adjacency bonus to all regions.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_WATER_STREET_CARNIVAL_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Brazilian special zone that replaces Water Park, +3 [ICON_Amenities] Amenities. Unlocks the &quot;Carnival&quot; project, which gives an additional +1 [ICON_Amenities] Amenities upon starting the project, and several [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person points upon completing the project. Cannot be built in a city with &quot;Street Carnival&quot;. Cannot be built on reefs.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_STREET_CARNIVAL_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Brazilian specialty area that replaces the Entertainment Facilities area, +3 [ICON_Amenities] Amenities. Unlocks the &quot;Carnival&quot; project, which gives an additional +1 [ICON_Amenities] Amenities after starting the project, and several [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person points after completing the project. Cannot be built in a city with &quot;Copacabana&quot;.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_GREAT_MOUNTAINS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Workers can start improving Terraces. Mountain tiles provide +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and +1 [ICON_Housing] Food for each Terrace Farm adjacent to them. Units adjacent to mountains gain +2 [ICON_MOVEMENT] Movement, +3 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength. -80% cost to purchase Mountain tiles.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_PACHACUTI_QHAPAQ_NAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cities adjacent to mountains gain +2 [ICON_AMENITIES] Amenities, +2 [ICON_Housing] Housing. Mountains gain +1 [ICON_Food] Food, +2 [ICON_Gold] Gold. Terraced Farms gain +1 [ICON_Food] Food, +1 [ICON_Production] Production. Unlocking the &quot;Foreign Trade&quot; civic grants Inca Road Improvements.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_NOBEL_PRIZE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sweden gains 100 [ICON_Favor] Diplomatic Favor (at standard speed) when recruiting Great People. +2 All Great People Points per turn when in the Golden Age. City construction zones in deserts, frozen soil, and snow are 25% faster, and an additional zone can be built. Melee units gain +1 [ICON_Movement] movement, +5 [ICON_Strength] combat strength, and heavy cavalry units can move after attacking. If Sweden enters the Industrial Age in the game, 3 special World Parliament competitions will be added. Sweden also has a wonderful bonus, but it can't be written here. For more information, please follow and consult the B station UP Slimy Eel Girl.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_NOBEL_PRIZE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Swedish land, Swedish sea</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_KRISTINA_AUTO_THEME_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When all slots are filled, buildings with 3 or more Great Work slots and wonders with 2 or more Great Work slots automatically gain a theme. The Queen's Library can be built in the city center. Buildings in the Town Square are 100% faster, and the Town Square and its buildings gain +2 [ICON_Science], +2 [ICON_Culture], and +2 [ICON_Faith]. Cities in frozen land and deserts gain +1 Charm.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_QUEENS_BIBLIOTHEQUE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unique Swedish city center building. +2 extra Great People points of all types. Contains 8 slots for 2 [ICON_GreatWork_WRITING] books, [ICON_GreatWork_MUSIC] music, any type of [ICON_GreatWork_Landscape] Great Work of Art, and [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] relics. [NEWLINE]Rewards 1 [ICON_Governor] Governor title.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_ALL_ROADS_TO_ROME_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Roman Empire</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_ALL_ROADS_TO_ROME_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>All cities you create or capture start with a Trade Post. Cities automatically build a road to Rome if they are within the [ICON_TradeRoute] trade route of your [ICON_Capital]. +2 [ICON_Gold] for each [ICON_TradeRoute] trade route that passes through your city's Trade Post. 100% faster construction of Dams, Breakwaters, Recreation Districts, Harbors and Commercial Districts. 100% faster construction of Ancient and Classical Wonders.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_TRAJANS_COLUMN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Found, acquire or capture a city and grant all unlocked City Center buildings. Unlocks Pottery and Wheel technologies at the start of the game. Monuments grant +2 [ICON_Culture] Culture and +2 [ICON_Gold] Gold.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_WONDER_TOURISM_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>God's filial son</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_WONDER_TOURISM_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Construction of Holy Sites is 100% faster. Construction of Medieval and Renaissance Wonders is 100% faster. Heavy Cavalry units gain +5 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength, and Siege and Ranged units of the Renaissance and later eras gain +5 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_ELEANOR_LOYALTY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Each Great Work in Eleanor's cities reduces the Loyalty of foreign cities within 9 tiles by 2 points per turn. After a city leaves another civilization due to losing Loyalty, if its Loyalty to Eleanor is the highest per turn, it will skip the Free City stage and join Eleanor's civilization. 100% speedup when constructing theaters and the buildings within them. +2 [ICON_GreatProphet] Great Prophet, [ICON_GreatWriter] Great Writer, [ICON_GreatMusician] Great Musician, [ICON_GreatArtist] Great Artist points per turn, doubled in the [ICON_GLORY_GOLDEN_AGE]. Holy Sites gain an adjacency bonus to theaters, and theaters gain +1 [ICON_GreatWriter] Great Writer and [ICON_GreatArtist] Great Artist point per turn. Your [ICON_GreatWork_Writing] and [ICON_GreatWork_Landscape] Great Works of Art gain +2 [ICON_Science] Technology, and your [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] and [ICON_GreatWork_Music] Great Works of Music gain +4 [ICON_Science] Technology.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_TRAIT_BABYLON_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[ICON_GreatWork_WRITING] Writings and [ICON_GreatWork_Landscape] Great Works of Art give +50% [ICON_Tourism] Tourism.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_BABYLON_BONUS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_LEADER_TRAIT_BABYLON_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ARMAGH_BONUS_XP2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Builders can now construct Monastery improvements. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Monasteries provide +2 [ICON_Faith] Faith, +1 [ICON_Food] Food, and +2 [ICON_Food] Food if in frozen ground. Each adjacent Holy Site gives +2 [ICON_FAITH] Faith. Provides +1 [ICON_HOUSING] Housing. Only one can be built per city, and must be on flat ground.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_TRAIT_ARMAGH_EXPANSION2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_CIVILIZATION_ARMAGH_BONUS_XP2}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MYN_MERCHANT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fed</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MYN_MERCHANT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A level 4 Commercial Center. Each civilization can only build one. It can only be purchased with [ICON_Gold]. If this city does not have a Plaza, Palace, or Diplomatic District: If you are not at Government Level 4, this city unlocks the Commercial Victory series of projects; -2 [ICON_Amenities] for all cities; and 5% more [ICON_Gold] per turn for each city-state your civilization controls. Cannot be built if there is already a Central Bank.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MYN_MERCHANT_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Central Bank</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MYN_MERCHANT_2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Commercial Center Level 4 building, limited to one per civilization. +10% [ICON_Gold] Gold, +1 [ICON_Amenities] Amenities for all cities. +2 for each Central Bank in the world during the 5th stage of the Commercial Victory Waiting for Victory. Cannot be built if there is already a Federal Reserve.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cover your hands and make it rain</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The first phase of the Commercial Victory project. After completion, -1000 [ICON_Gold] coins per turn for 30 turns (at standard speed), unlocking the next phase project &quot;This is Freedom&quot;. Double the product effect, and reduce the favorability of other civilizations towards you by 1. If other civilizations receive less than 500 coins per turn, their gold coins per turn will be reduced by 25%.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is freedom</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The second stage of the Commercial Victory project. After completion, -2000 [ICON_Gold] gold coins per turn for 30 turns (at standard speed), unlocking the next stage project &quot;Fools are fools&quot;. +10 [ICON_Gold] gold coins to your foreign trade routes, +1 [ICON_Amenities] amenity to all cities, +10 [ICON_GREATMERCHANT] great merchant points per turn. -10 [ICON_STRENGTH] combat strength to all units, and other civilizations' favorability towards you is reduced by 1. If other civilizations have less than 10 trade routes, their foreign trade routes will be -10 [ICON_Gold] gold coins for 30 turns.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fools are fools themselves</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The third stage of the Commercial Victory project. After completion, you will receive -3000 [ICON_Gold] coins per turn for 30 turns (at standard speed), and unlock the next stage project &quot;The World is Under Our Feet&quot;. A random civilization will declare war on you. All cities will receive -2 [ICON_Amenities] Amenities. If your military strength is less than 2000, you fail.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The world is under our feet</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The fourth stage of the Commercial Victory project. After completion, you will receive -4000 [ICON_Gold] coins per turn for 30 turns (at standard speed). All civilizations will declare war on you, and all cities will receive -8 loyalty. Wait for a few turns before you can get the Commercial Victory.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MYN_MERCHANT_VIC_1_TOOLTIP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Completed Phase 1 of project {LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_1_NAME}. [NEWLINE]{LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_1_NAME}: {LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_1_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MYN_MERCHANT_VIC_2_TOOLTIP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Completed Phase 2 of project {LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_2_NAME}. [NEWLINE]{LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_2_NAME}: {LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_2_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MYN_MERCHANT_VIC_3_TOOLTIP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Completed Phase 3 of project {LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_3_NAME}. [NEWLINE]{LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_3_NAME}: {LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_3_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MYN_MERCHANT_VIC_4_TOOLTIP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Completed Phase 4 of project &quot;{LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_4_NAME}&quot;. [NEWLINE]{LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_4_NAME}: {LOC_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_4_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MYN_MERCHANT_VIC_5_TOOLTIP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Need to wait {1_Num} [ICON_Turn] turns to achieve business victory, have waited {2_Num} turns.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MYN_MERCHANT_DUMMY_DISLIKE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>-1 Favorability</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MYN_MERCHANT_DUMMY_TRADEROUTE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is the punishment of freedom</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MYN_MERCHANT_DUMMY_UNLOCK_PROJECT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unlock Business Victory Project</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_MYN_MERCHANT_UNWELCOME_REASON_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>………(indifferent)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_DESCRIPTION_MYN_MERCHANT_UNWELCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The arrogance of the elite</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODIFIER_PROJECT_MYN_MERCHANT_2_COMBAT_STRENGTH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is Free Project-10</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_MYN_MERCHANT_CONGRESS_BUTTON" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Business</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_MYN_MERCHANT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Business Victory</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MYN_MERCHANT_VIC_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Use your wealth to make the whole world surrender. Use gold to create eternal financial hegemony.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_MYN_MERCHANT_TEXT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As we all agree, the world needs us to push it forward. The masses are blind and short-sighted. We will use our power to lead them to a better world.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_MYN_MERCHANT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>To achieve the [COLOR:ResGoldLabelCS]Business[ENDCOLOR] victory, you must build the Federal Reserve, a tier 4 building in the Business Center. If a city has a Federal Reserve but does not own a Town Square, Palace, or Diplomatic District, and you are not at government level 4, the city will unlock 4 Business Victory projects. Complete all four projects and wait 3 [ICON_Turn] turns to achieve Business Victory. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]To counter an opponent who is about to achieve Business Victory, build a Central Bank, also a tier 4 building in the Business Center. Each Central Bank in the world increases the number of turns to win in the fifth stage of Business Victory by +2. You cannot have both a Federal Reserve and a Central Bank. Additionally, in the fifth stage, if the Federal Reserve is being pillaged, the countdown to win cannot be reduced. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After this victory is enabled, any civilization that has a 0 [ICON_Gold] Treasury and negative [ICON_Gold] gold per turn will revolt and become a Free City.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_WORLD_RANKINGS_MERCHANT_POINTS_TT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Currently in stage {1_Num}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_WORLD_RANKINGS_MERCHANT_POINTS_TT_FINISHED" Language="en_US">
			<Text>completed</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
