<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun Dec 29 20:37:38 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LEITHANIEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Leitania was originally composed of ten independent regions including Syracuse. Under the threat of Kazdel, the nine tribes and the families of Syracuse decided to unite and establish a defensive alliance, which is the predecessor of the current Leitania country. After consultation, they formulated the &quot;Golden Rule&quot;. Leitania continued its love for Originium skills and music, and promoted this love, nurturing an atmosphere that values ​​Originium skills and art.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LEITHANIEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In 967, an independence movement broke out in Syracuse, which triggered a wave of secession in various parts of Leithania. The Elector took the opportunity to strengthen his own power, and the Leithanian regime was shaky. In 969, the &quot;Witch King&quot; Herhunzollon came to power. He revised the Golden Rule to recognize the independence of Syracuse, and took back part of the power of the Elector and the army on the grounds of suppressing domestic rebellion, quickly resolving the domestic crisis.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LEITHANIEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In the first ten years of the Witch King's reign, he worked hard to govern the country and began to carry out drastic reforms, bringing prosperity to the country through rich Originium skills. However, the nobles were increasingly dissatisfied, and the Witch King could only suppress dissidents with tough measures, hunting down and even slaughtering opposition parties in the country, and Leitania was in a protracted bloody storm. The Witch King also locked himself in a high tower, practicing a weird and crazy mysticism, which made many Leitanians fear him even more.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LEITHANIEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In 1029, Letania refused to become a vassal of Gaul and took the lead in provoking a war against Gaul in the Four Kingdoms War, which was the Gallo-Letanian War. The war lasted for two years and ended with the defeat of Gaul.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LEITHANIEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After the war, Lethania seized Gaul's land, technology, and talents, but the country was devastated and the Witch King continued to rule. The Witch King gradually fell into madness, and the electors took back some of the real power.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LEITHANIEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After 1070, the Twins appeared in the political arena of Leithnia and openly opposed the rule of the Witch King. In 1077, the September Uprising broke out, and the coalition of electors attacked the capital. The Twins defeated the Witch King and became the new ruler of Leithnia. The Witch King's horns were chopped off and his body was put on display. But the shadow of the Witch King did not dissipate, and there were still supporters of the Witch King who opposed the rule of the Twins. Those who opposed the rule of the Twins were called the &quot;Witch King's Remnants&quot;.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LEITHANIEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In 1100, the 23rd Queen's Celebration of Leitania was held. The remnants of the Witch King started a riot, the Golden Rule was destroyed, and the Witch King's tower &quot;Horn of Origin&quot; descended. The twin queens worked together to defeat the Witch King. In order to prevent the invasion of evil demons in the wasteland, one of the twin queens, Helinmart, built a new &quot;tower&quot; and was sealed in the wasteland. Leitania announced to the outside world that Helinmart had &quot;lost her voice&quot;.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LIESELOTTE_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Liselotte Yvignad</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LIESELOTTE_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Liselotte Yvignad</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LIESELOTTE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>One of the two queens who ruled Leithania, with a pure white skirt, &quot;Eternal Grace&quot;. &quot;White Sheep&quot; is actually a man-made weapon against the Witch King made together with the other queen, Helinmart Hildegard. She seems to be a gentle &quot;Eternal Grace&quot;, but in fact she acts hard and ruthlessly. She hopes to take the sunset for herself, so she condones the whole incident and clears the obstacles for her own power.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HILDEGARD_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Helena Marthe Hildegard</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HILDEGARD_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Helena Marthe Hildegard</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HILDEGARD_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>One of the two queens who ruled Leitania, the dark black blade, &quot;ruthless authority&quot;, &quot;black goat&quot;, is actually a man-made weapon made with the other queen, Liselotte Ivignad, to fight against the Witch King. It seems to be a stern &quot;ruthless authority&quot;, but in fact there is still a soft side in the heart. He believes that the sunset should belong to everyone, and took in and taught Misha from the Lupercan region. Before the incident, he joined forces with Fremont, hoping to safely make the &quot;Origin Horn&quot; appear under control so as to stably receive the Witch King's legacy. Throughout the incident, he indulged Liselotte to implement her plan. After Pavillon defeated the Witch King, he volunteered to stay behind to cover the retreat, and then lost his voice.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HERKUNFTSHORN_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Herzogen</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HERKUNFTSHORN_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Witch King&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HERKUNFTSHORN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Full name: Otto Dietmar Gustav von Utica. &quot;The Horn of Origin&quot;, former ruler of Leithania, the most gifted and capable magician in Terra's history.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HERKUNFTSHORN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>He studied under Fleimont and later became close friends with Fleimont. He rewrote the Golden Rule to remove the melody of &quot;Syracuse&quot;, making Syracuse independent while maintaining the stability of Leithnia. He is also the only king to have changed the Golden Rule so far.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HERKUNFTSHORN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>He blocked the Gaul offensive and won the Battle of the Four Emperors. He never stopped and believed that immortality lies in renewal, so he carried out reforms in Leitania, greatly weakening the power of the nobles, allowing fresh blood to flow into the tower, and at the same time taking power back to the central government, making Leitania a peaceful place where different classes could exchange what they had.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_HERKUNFTSHORN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After borrowing the Life Knot from Fremont, he began to explore the void, opening up the &quot;Origin Horn&quot; and &quot;Own Pavillon&quot;, the symbol of Leitania, and leaving his own figure in it. After learning the truth about the Originium, he gradually fell into madness, and Leitania entered into extreme despotism and lost all vitality. The fear brought by this still affects Leitania to this day.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Viviana</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Viviana</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In that dream in the wilderness, Viviana saw herself when she was young, and saw many mistakes and regrets. Many past events have gone with time and will never come back, but there are still some, small ones, that can be found from the corners of memory. As an adult, she still has some innocence. In the past, due to the constraints and the tabloid reporters, she could only hide the impulse in her heart, but now...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Ah... uh...&quot; Looking at the dream palace built by various dolls in the corner of the dormitory, the brilliant knight Lin Guang didn't know what to say for a moment. The owner of the palace was looking at the stunned guests with satisfaction and joy.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>No wonder the Knight was so surprised. In that small world, the carpet was painted with grass and lakes, the half-open cabinet in the corner was made to look like mountains and castles, a suspended lamp emitted soft light, and the surroundings were covered tightly with dust covers.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stuffed beasts of various shapes ate on the ground, not caring at all about the humans working nearby. Tin sentinels held their spears tightly, and the Silver Princess ran barefoot on the grassland.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The knight was about to say something, but the owner of the little world pressed a button, and the cupboard castle was transformed. More wonders began to emerge: the Golden Law Guard was holding a pair of scissors to repair the vines, the blindfolded lady was playing an exotic musical instrument leisurely, the poet fell asleep on the recliner with his wife in his arms, and at his feet, a delicate model that looked like a staff or a sword was also sleeping quietly in the cotton wool...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The knight studied the pile of dolls carefully, still not recovering from the shock, especially after seeing a plush doll with the Linguang family crest in the corner. Apart from giving his old friend an awkward smile, the knight really couldn't do anything else...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This sudden farce did not last long. After a brief teasing and communication, the knight got the record she wanted from her friend: it contained the full picture of the incident compiled by Viviana based on her memories. Margaret was busy with work, and the meeting between the two on Rhodes Island came to an end. Before leaving, the knight suddenly remembered a question. She saw herself in the dolls, but among these dolls, there was no figure of the owner herself.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The master did not answer, but smiled and pressed another switch. The &quot;sun&quot; slowly turned, revealing the mystery inside -</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIVIANA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The young &quot;master&quot; was curled up and sleeping, but her horns had intertwined and turned into light, illuminating the entire room.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_EBENHOLZ_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Black Keys</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_EBENHOLZ_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Black Keys</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_EBENHOLZ_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When he first arrived at Rhodes Island, Black Key did not show much of the harshness or verbal aggression described by operators Fleur and Czerny. Most operators only knew that a silent and polite Leitanian operator had come to Rhodes Island. At that time, Black Key did not take the initiative to talk to people, and often stared blankly when no one was around, staring at the cello that he almost never left. When an operator asked him out of concern if he needed help, he just shook his head slightly.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_EBENHOLZ_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Black Key's transformation occurred after his first field mission. It was a highly successful operation, in which Rhodes Island rescued more than a dozen orphans from an orphanage in extremely poor conditions, contacted reliable institutions for children who were not infected with oripathy, and admitted those who were infected.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_EBENHOLZ_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It is worth mentioning that Black Key played an important role throughout the process, from seeing through the disguise of the orphanage manager to providing Originium skills support in the rescue operation.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_EBENHOLZ_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After returning to Rhodes Island, Black Key began to break away from his previous state little by little. He started talking to people who came to him actively, started to understand everything about Rhodes Island, and began to harshly comment on things that he couldn't stand - of course, only to the Doctor and a few operators.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_EBENHOLZ_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>He even attended a book club held by the operators themselves and established correspondence with several of them after the meeting.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_EBENHOLZ_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Most operators on Rhodes Island could hardly notice these changes in Black Key, but there was one thing that everyone saw: Black Key no longer stared at the cello in a trance. He often played it and hummed along with the music, as if he was talking to a friend.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Plastic Heart</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Arturo Giallo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You stepped into a nightmare. [NEWLINE]In the nightmare, you couldn't make any sound from your throat, and you couldn't see other people's faces. But you heard a familiar voice, warm and bright, like a nursery rhyme from long ago. [NEWLINE]&quot;Arturo, Arturo? Are you feeling better? [NEWLINE]&quot;Are you still feeling bad? Can you tell your mother about your nightmare last night? [NEWLINE]&quot;Arturo, don't be afraid. [NEWLINE]&quot;Don't be afraid of not being able to make any sound from your throat, and don't be afraid of not being able to see other people's faces. [NEWLINE]&quot;Arturo, come, come to your mother. [NEWLINE]&quot;Look, this is a cello. Mom will teach you.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The bow was placed on the strings, playing a silent rain, you know it was rain because the raindrops fell on your face. [NEWLINE]It hurts, it burns, you look for the nursery rhyme, where is she? [NEWLINE]You are pushed, everyone is wearing a veil, they are all far away, but there is a hand strangling your arm. [NEWLINE]&quot;Arturo Giallo, don't be sad.&quot; [NEWLINE]&quot;Your father doesn't blame you, he just can't accept it for a while. [NEWLINE]&quot;Your mother left you this pair of gloves, she hopes you can wear them. [NEWLINE]&quot;If you can't control your music, you will need someone else to control you. Start with these gloves. [NEWLINE]&quot;This is not a punishment, Arturo, this is to protect others, to protect the people around you, to protect the people close to you. [NEWLINE]&quot;Don't hurt them anymore, Arturo.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The silhouette melted into the inky rain, and the burning raindrops merged into an inky sun. [NEWLINE]It hangs over your head, and its black light blinds you. [NEWLINE]&quot;You came too late, Arturo.&quot; [NEWLINE]&quot;You didn't get to see your teacher for the last time, and you didn't get to say goodbye to him properly. [NEWLINE]&quot;You foresaw his death, didn't you? [NEWLINE]&quot;When you knew he had played under that tall tower, his death was already doomed. [NEWLINE]&quot;Unfortunately, even for Emmanuel, fighting against fate still ended up like this. [NEWLINE]&quot;You? What can you do about it? [NEWLINE]&quot;You can't do anything, Arturo.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The inky sun sank. It plunged into the ocean of people without hesitation. [NEWLINE]The noisy ocean finally condensed into a tear, which passed across your cheek and fell into your heart. [NEWLINE]You heard that voice. [NEWLINE]&quot;Don't be afraid, Arturo.&quot; [NEWLINE]The music stopped at this moment.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;I'm sorry, I didn't notice you were here. I only practiced this new piece of music when I was alone. I'm sorry to bother you, but I'm not very good at it yet. [NEWLINE] &quot;In fact, this piece of music is not yet finished. The inspiration for creating it just came to me. This kind of composition method is very new and difficult for me. There has never been such a piece of music created on this earth. [NEWLINE] &quot;So I can guarantee that every part of the music comes from the heart. It is my own melody. [NEWLINE] &quot;But I have already thought of the name of this piece of music. [NEWLINE] &quot;Its name is 'Plastic Heart'.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_BULL_GUARD_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Imperial Guard is the most elite force under the Leithanian Imperial Court. It is a part of the Imperial Court, only obeys the Emperor's orders and is not subject to the laws of the regions.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_SPIRE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Leitania is a confederation, with nine electoral districts, or &quot;districts&quot;, with leaders called &quot;electors&quot;. Each district has great power, a complete government, and its own laws and armies. However, due to cultural unity and political needs, the laws and military regulations in each district are roughly the same, with only differences in details and some clauses. [NEWLINE] Each mobile city-state has twelve towers, which belong to the Leitanian nobility, and the mobile towns are used to develop economic industries.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_AFTERGLOW_HALL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The concert hall located in the Sunset District of Visheim is called the Sunset Hall. Under the rule of Count Gertrude, even the infected settlement area is full of Originium skills and cultural arts.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GOVERNMENTS_PAGE_POLICY_LEITHANIEN_1_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The blooming ones are enough to make spring stop, [NEWLINE] seem not to come from the earth, but to spread out of the courtyard wall, swaying with fragrance [NEWLINE] Rose, your smile is overwhelming to all living beings [NEWLINE] The sounds everywhere tempt everyone to run [NEWLINE] With your magic, the hurried footsteps are temporarily stopped [NEWLINE] Your vines pick up the scattered poems [NEWLINE] and depict them as petals [NEWLINE] Teach everyone to pick them, and laugh and talk</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GOVERNMENTS_PAGE_POLICY_LEITHANIEN_2_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The damaged wood core has never broken. They staggered with their carving knives and hoes. Vidunia, we carved your coffin. We tightened the strings of fate. We carved out the black gold keys. We carved out the melody of the fall. We carved! We carved!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GOVERNMENTS_PAGE_POLICY_LEITHANIEN_3_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The towers are silent [NEWLINE] The fountains are gushing red, lifeless [NEWLINE] The crowded horns are silent in the park [NEWLINE] With your back turned, you are about to stop crying</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GOVERNMENTS_PAGE_POLICY_LEITHANIEN_4_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The eternal palace. Above the sky, you climb there, trembling, crawling on the stairs of chaos. The walls spin the words of origin, binding you tightly. The rocks in the cracks maintain a life span like the night, peaceful as the veins on the arm. The stairs are suspended, high in the abyss, leading to the tower where the mist is gone. Listen, the tower has never discussed the scenery at the end with the outside world.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GOVERNMENTS_PAGE_POLICY_LEITHANIEN_5_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If, one day, the footprints of life will be buried by the dust of time... then we can never stop...</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
