<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun Jul 16 22:13:36 2023-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu, the protagonist in the series &quot;Touhou Project&quot;, is the existing witch of Hakurei Shrine in Gensokyo, responsible for solving various changes that occurred in Gensokyo. He appears as the protagonist in the games of the &quot;Oriental&quot; series, and also appears as the main character in other works. As a priestess of Hakurei Shrine, exterminating monsters is her daily job. Because there are not many visitors to the shrine, I live a leisurely life drinking tea and sweeping the floor all day.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_ALLY_OF_REIMU_TANSHOU_BROKEN_YES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu likes the peaceful days of Gensokyo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_ALLY_OF_REIMU_TANSHOU_BROKEN_NO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu hates days when someone is restless</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo - Hakurei Shrine</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The only shrine that exists at the eastern end of Gensokyo. The shrine sits on the dividing line between the outside world and Gensokyo (×4 is right, not in Gensokyo.). From the shrine, you can see Gensokyo at a glance, and it is a famous spot for viewing cherry blossoms. [NEWLINE]The shrine has an expert in resolving mutations, and the shrine maiden of Hakurei lives there. She will guard Gensokyo in the shrine, and dispatch immediately after a change occurs to investigate the cause. Recently, the red mist mutation and other mutations have just been solved. [NEWLINE]Originally youkai were not allowed to approach the shrine, but recently it has been rumored that it has become a lair for youkai, and people can no longer approach it. Like the human village, it is stipulated that humans will not be attacked by monsters in the shrine. But between the shrine and the village there is a sinister animal way. The shrine cannot guarantee safety on the way, so it has always affected people who want to visit. [NEWLINE]Other features are that it is easy to pick up things from the outside world near the shrine, and find people who strayed in from the outside world by mistake. Most of these outsiders are found and eaten by monsters. If they are lucky enough to find the shrine, they can return home without incident (×5 Recently, many people do not want to go back, so they will be arranged to live in the village at this time.). [NEWLINE]The outside world is magical and popular with humans and monsters alike. So there are many collectors near the shrine. It's just that most of the collected things don't know how to use them.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Shrine is located in the mountains away from human habitation, at the border between Gensokyo and the outside world. It is the only shrine with people in Gensokyo. However, although some parts of this shrine are connected to Gensokyo, it is not technically part of Gensokyo. Nor does it belong to the outside world. It is also on the border line. [NEWLINE]The cherry blossoms in spring attract many people. But judging from the character of the shrine maiden who lives here, there should be a lot of ghosts and ghosts gathered in this shrine, as if there is always something gathering here. For this reason, few people visit this shrine. It's ironic that the attractive character of the shrine maiden also attracts youkai, but people stay away. [NEWLINE]Of course, there's no better place for us youkai to hang out than here. It happens that there are still very strong humans here, so living here is also very interesting. And this shrine only has the role of being on the border between Gensokyo and the outside world. It is no longer a place to worship the gods, so even races that are afraid of sacred things can stay here at will. [NEWLINE]When you visit a shrine, you don’t need incense money, just bring some food or wine. In that case, the shrine maiden will lend you a place under the cherry tree while complaining. There are always people around at all times, so it's not a good time to have a quiet drink by yourself. [NEWLINE]The Hakurei Shrine existed before Gensokyo was completely cut off from the outside world as it is now. But I remember back then it wasn't as shiny as it is now, just a faded little shrine that didn't look useful. I am afraid that Hakurei Shrine is still that faded little shrine from the outside world. Perhaps the visiting youkai are also enjoying the glamorous shrine, and remembering the memories of that time.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo - Hakurei Shrine</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo - Hakurei Shrine</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CAPITAL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Shrine</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu is the first protagonist of the series' official works, and also a representative character of the Touhou series. Commonly known as the red and white witch [NEWLINE] Hakurei Reimu is also the oriental character with the most recognition and the most secondary creations in the world and in the Chinese community. [NEWLINE]She first appeared in the first game of the Touhou series, Touhou Psychic, and has been appearing as a playable mobile character in the official game ever since. [NEWLINE] As the first protagonist of the Touhou series, she runs through the entire story line of the Touhou series and is one of the most important characters in the Touhou series.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu is a shrine located in Gensokyo—the current priestess of Hakurei Shrine[NEWLINE]She lives in Hakurei Shrine on weekdays, and will appear in various places in Gensokyo and even when there are jobs or accidents. In the world outside of Gensokyo. [NEWLINE]As Hakurei Miko, she focuses on solving mutations, mainly subduing monsters and other enemies. In addition, she has a wealth of knowledge related to monsters. As an expert in this field, she will also help solve some problems related to monsters. Instead of simply serving the gods or running a shrine like ordinary priestesses. [NEWLINE]Due to the location of Hakurei Shrine, it is far from the human village in Gensokyo, and there are dangerous animal paths and uphill roads on the way, so there are not many visitors. [NEWLINE]Reimu often thinks of various ways to attract worshipers, but they often end in failure. [NEWLINE] Although resolving the mutation itself will bring income to Reimu, due to the lack of incense money and Reimu's greed for money, Reimu is generally set as an image of being poor and doing anything for money in the secondary creation. But her greed for money is not tainted with vulgarity, but a manifestation of her simplicity and loyalty to desire. [NEWLINE]Although she is a Shinto priestess, her abilities and skills are mainly displayed in the form of Chinese Taoism</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo is really peaceful today~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_ABILITY_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Great Enchantment</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_ABILITY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Converts a military policy slot into an economic policy slot, +7 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength when fighting barbarians; +1 [ICON_Amenities] Amenities for cities and all district adjacency bonuses will yield equal [ICON_CULTURE] Culture</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ABILITIES_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mysterious Miko Flying in the Sky</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ABILITIES_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[COLOR:StatBadCS] Cancel all ranged units and replace them with new air units[ENDCOLOR] [NEWLINE] Add 1 air unit slot to all areas outside the city center, air units +2 vision, +3 [ICON_Movement] movement , +4 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_ADD_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>incredible flying</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_ADD_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Incredibles of Flying: +2 Vision, +3 [ICON_Movement] Movement, +4 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODIFIER_ABILITY_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_ADD_STR_ADD_04_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+4 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength from Leader Ability: Sky-flying Miko</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_REIMU_TANSHOU_BROKEN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Miko</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_REIMU_TANSHOU_BROKEN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>like a quiet person who doesn't make trouble; people who don't like to make trouble</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_01_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>goblin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_01_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu's unique air unit replaces the Slinger with a lower cost. Air unit operations are possible.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_02_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>big fairy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_02_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu's unique air unit replaces archers with a lower cost. Air unit operations are possible.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_03_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Apparition</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_03_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu's characteristic air unit replaces the crossbowman with a lower cost. Air unit operations are possible.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_04_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>elite monster</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_04_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu's characteristic air unit, which replaces the field cannon and costs less. Air unit operations are possible.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_05_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self machine</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_05_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu's characteristic air unit replaces the machine gun team with a lower cost. Air unit operations are possible.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TANSHOU_REIMU_CONFIG_UNIT_TURN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>air unit replacement</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TANSHOU_REIMU_CONFIG_UNIT_TURN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Air units are replaced as follows [NEWLINE] Slinger ——&gt; Fairy[NEWLINE]4 [ICON_Movement] Movement, 15 [ICON_Strength] Combat Power, 3 [ICON_Range] Range[NEWLINE] Archer —&gt; Big Fairy[NEWLINE]5 [ICON_Movement ] Mobility, 27 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength, 3 [ICON_Range] Range[NEWLINE] Crossbowman——&gt; Monster[NEWLINE]6 [ICON_Movement] Movement Strength, 43 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength, 4 [ICON_Range] Range[NEWLINE] Field Cannon ——&gt;Elite Monster[NEWLINE]8 [ICON_Movement] Movement Strength, 64 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength, 5 [ICON_Range] Range[NEWLINE] Machine Guns—&gt;Own Machine[NEWLINE]10 [ICON_Movement] Movement Strength, 90 [ICON_Strength] Combat strength, 6 [ICON_Range] range</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>fantasy air raid</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_LEFT_01_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>POWER UP↑</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_LEFT_01_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+6 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength in any situation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODIFIER_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_LEFT_01" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+6 [ICON_Strength] Combat strength from promotion: POWER UP↑</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_LEFT_02_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>fantasy formation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_LEFT_02_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_Envoy] Envoy, which increases experience gain by 15% for all &quot;Fantasy Airstrike&quot; units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_LEFT_03_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sniper</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_LEFT_03_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+3 [ICON_Range] Range</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_RIGHT_01_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>winner's reward</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_RIGHT_01_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gain [ICON_GOLD] coins equal to 150% of the defeated unit's [ICON_Strength] combat power after defeating an enemy unit</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_RIGHT_02_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seal Moya Hole</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_RIGHT_02_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+8 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength when fighting with injured enemies</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODIFIER_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_RIGHT_02" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+8 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength against Wounded Enemies from Promotion: Sealing Moya Hole</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_RIGHT_03_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>dream born</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_RIGHT_03_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_Movement] Movement +2 Vision</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_ENDING_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>dream seal</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_ENDING_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+7 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength, Ranged Attacks are 100% effective when attacking area defenses</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODIFIER_PROMOTION_CLASS_UNIT_TANSHOU_REIMU_AIR_LEVEL_ALL_ENDING_STR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+7 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength from Promotion: Seal of Dreams</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_PROTECTION_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>small enchantment</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_PROTECTION_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This small barrier is derived from the Hakurei Great Barrier, which can be regarded as the differentiation of barriers. [NEWLINE] The Hakurei Barrier is a huge barrier that communicates Gensokyo and the real world. It completely isolates Gensokyo and the real world. In the real world, monsters and humans cannot know the existence of Gensokyo, which fundamentally protects Gensokyo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_PROTECTION_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Great Enchantment The founders of the &quot;Hakurei Great Enchantment&quot; are the strongest monster Yakumo Zi and the first generation Hakurei Miko. According to the &quot;Monologue&quot; (pp.152-155) of &quot;Seeking History&quot;, the Hakurei Great Barrier is a &quot;barrier of common sense&quot;, which distinguishes the &quot;common sense&quot; and &quot;uncommon sense&quot; of the outside world and Gensokyo. The &quot;common sense&quot; in the world is defined as the &quot;uncommon sense&quot; of Gensokyo, and the &quot;uncommon sense&quot; of the outside world is defined as the &quot;common sense&quot; of Gensokyo. &quot;Fensokyo Fudoki&quot; believes that monks developed this enchantment to prevent monsters from invading the world. Hida Akyu's &quot;Fantasy Township Origin&quot; in &quot;The History of Seeking News&quot; shows that it was established by various sages, including Yakumo Zi.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_PROTECTION_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo—the characteristic area of ​​Hakurei Shrine, unlocked by technological construction, does not require population, and has no limit on the number of constructions. [NEWLINE] [NEWLINE] Self +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Productivity +2 [ICON_FOOD] food; the land around the area +1 charm, when the charm value of the land around the area is charming, +1 [ICON_FAITH] faith value +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Productivity, +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food +2 [ICON_FAITH] Faith +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Productivity when the charm value of the plots around the area is amazing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="DISTRICT_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_PROTECTION_SELF_PRODUCTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from itself</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="DISTRICT_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_PROTECTION_SELF_FOOD" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_FOOD] food from itself</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Scarlet Devil House</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lost Bamboo Forest</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forever Pavilion</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>underworld</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Baiyulou</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Youkai Mountain</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>lost house</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Moriya Shrine</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There is a sky</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Big Toad's Pond</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The middle way</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sanzu River</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiutian Waterfall</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_14" Language="en_US">
			<Text>unnamed hill</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_15" Language="en_US">
			<Text>magic forest</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_16" Language="en_US">
			<Text>lake of fog</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_17" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xianglintang</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_18" Language="en_US">
			<Text>animal way</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_19" Language="en_US">
			<Text>sun flower field</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_CITY_20" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xuanwu Lake</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rinnosuke Morichika</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hyun Yeh</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Drizzle Marisa</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Izayoi Sakuya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Soul Youmu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dongfenggu Sanae</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lingxian</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ibaraki Hana fan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Suika Ibuki</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Takahashino Aun</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TANSHOU_REIMU_GENSOKYO_HAKUREI_FAMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shaomingzhenmiaowan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well then, ally.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo is not as simple as you think.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Are you also ready to solve the mutation?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Since Gensokyo has accepted you, it's best not to cause any trouble.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I don't want to think about it for now.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Are you the source of the mutation?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Are you the source of the mutation?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo is temporarily open, so please feel free to walk around.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The enchantment is not ready for outsiders to open, please go back.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sometimes it's a good idea to go outside for a walk, and we certainly didn't come here empty-handed.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Peaceful days are what I like best to see, and I hope you don't get in our way.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>None of us like to see the mutation happen again, you better not let me do it. (condemns you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakurei Reimu, the Miko of Hakurei Shrine, the guardian of the Great Barrier.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The enchantment is still open for the time being, feel free to</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh well.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We can share our addresses with each other if we want.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hello, what can I do,</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gensokyo is really peaceful today, well done.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Is the mutation going to happen again? What a headache.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is the agreement to be signed, let's take a look.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hopefully such a truce will teach you a hard lesson.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If the mutation is not resolved, I won't be able to deal with it. The spell card rules are temporarily invalid in this situation.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Then let's stop fighting.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The borders are open, feel free to come through.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>No, I have to think about this kind of thing.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We just happened to pass by, so don't make a fuss.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There are too many troops, you'd better withdraw some, of course, this is a warning.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_AI_RESPONSE_NEGATIVE_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forgive me.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_AI_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Then we'll leave first.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oops, I actually lost, my money!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I'm still very good at calculating benefits, so forget it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_TANSHOU_HAKUREI_REIMU_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is good, I think it's very good.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
