<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Fri Apr 11 23:41:38 2025-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_NW_TIBAO_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tibao (demigod)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_NW_WANDI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ten Thousand Enemies (Demigods)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_NW_AGELAIYA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Agreya (demigod)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_NW_NAKEXIA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>That moment Xia (demigod)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_NW_JIYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>memory</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_NW_JIYI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>One characteristic building in Onpharos can only be built, not at the same time as intelligence and the end. Once built, all [ICON_District] areas of the civilization obtain the [ICON_Culture] cultural value from other adjacent bonuses. Regional, downtown and wonder +1 great writer, great artist and great musician [ICON_GreatPerson] points and get a certain [ICON_Tourism] tourism performance. All regional level 1 buildings offer 3 extra masterpiece slots that can accommodate any type of masterpiece.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_NW_ZHISHI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Intelligence</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_NW_ZHISHI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>One characteristic building in Onffalos can only be built, not at the same time as memory and the end. Once completed, all [ICON_District] areas, downtown and other adjacent bonuses for the civilization also provide [ICON_Science] technology and [ICON_Faith] faith values, and +1 [ICON_GreatPerson] points for the Great Scientist, Great Prophet and Great Engineer. When creating a new city, recruiting great men or building wonders, the technology currently being studied will be unlocked immediately.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_NW_ZHONGMO_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>End</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_NW_ZHONGMO_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>One characteristic building in Onfaros can only be built, not at the same time as memory and intelligence. Once completed, other adjacent bonuses for all [ICON_District] areas of civilization also provide [ICON_Food] food, [ICON_Production] productivity. +1 [ICON_Amenities] Livability, +2 [ICON_Housing] Housing, and +1 General, Navy Admiral and Great Merchant [ICON_GreatPerson] Points. No maintenance fees are required for all units.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_NW_AMPHOREUS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The cycle of memory, intelligence and the end</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_NW_AMPHOREUS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After unlocking the &quot;Code&quot; municipal government, three types of civilized buildings are allowed to be built in the capital. If you have any kind of civilized buildings or are in the golden age, all cities will produce +12%. After the civilized characteristic building is built, the adjacent bonuses for all areas also provide [ICON_Gold] gold coins.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_STEAL_THE_DOOR_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Door&quot; half god</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_STEAL_THE_DOOR_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>初始解锁「占星术」科技。 Cities that believe in your mainstream religion will release additional loyalty pressures to the outside world and provide 1 point of full output per [ICON_Citizen] population. [NEWLINE] The city unlocking area project you founded and built &quot;Kefale Square&quot;: [ICON_Turn] &quot;Fire Chase&quot;.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_FIRE_DISPUTE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Strife&quot; half god</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_FIRE_DISPUTE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Initial unlocking of &quot;Mining&quot; and &quot;Bronze Casting&quot; technologies. When the technology to unlock the land military unit is completed, all cities will receive one of the units for free. [ICON_Production] productivity adjacent bonus +100% in the [NEWLINE] area. Permanent loyalty in cities with garrisons, loyal cities +5 [ICON_Amenities] livability, [ICON_Production] productivity increases by 30%. [NEWLINE] At the beginning of the round, the combat power of all current land units is increased, and the increase value is the sum of the livability of all current cities [ICON_Amenities]; if it consumes movement power on a neutral cell, it will immediately restore all its movement power. [NEWLINE] All land units +2 movement power, stationing for one round can restore full health, and can output full damage to the city.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_FIRE_ROMANCE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>「浪漫」之半神</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_FIRE_ROMANCE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Initial unlocking of &quot;irrigation&quot; technology. Improved facility cell +2 [ICON_Culture] Culture +2 [ICON_Food] food and provide additional [ICON_Housing] housing and [ICON_Amenities] livability. [NEWLINE] Improved Luxury offers [ICON_Amenities] livability to all cities, rather than the usual 4. [NEWLINE] The existing cells do not reduce the charm of adjacent cells, and the area obtains output equivalent to the charm value of the cell without exceeding 20. [NEWLINE] Any player recruits [ICON_GreatPerson] great man, increase all your [ICON_GreatPerson] great man points based on 3% of the points required to recruit the [ICON_GreatPerson] great man. When the [ICON_DISTRICT_BATH] was built, a Golden Desert was obtained. [NEWLINE] Cities obtain 20% of their corresponding output from specialized areas, and 15 [ICON_Citizen] Cities with population above double the effect. Each [ICON_Citizen] in the empire increased its population by 1% all output.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_FIRE_REASON_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>「理性」之半神</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_FIRE_REASON_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Initial unlocking of &quot;writing&quot; technology. When unlocking [ICON_Science] technology, it also randomly unlocks a contemporary [ICON_Science] technology. For cities with less than three specialized areas, the time required to build a specialized area is greatly shortened. Removal of landforms +50%, while unlocking the builder's ability to plant natural forests.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_KEFALEPLAZA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kefale Square</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_KEFALEPLAZA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The characteristic area of ​​Tirisipios, replaces the [ICON_DISTRICT_HOLYSITE] sacred land, with lower construction costs. When completed, it releases cultural bombs to adjacent cells. It initially has +3 adjacent bonuses and inherits the adjacent bonuses of the sacred land. After completion, [NEWLINE] is allowed to purchase buildings with [ICON_Faith] faith value, and you will enjoy a 50% discount when purchasing buildings in this city. [NEWLINE] Get +1 [ICON_Faith] belief value from adjacent flat terrain cells.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_FIGHTING_CAMP_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Suspension Arena</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_FIGHTING_CAMP_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The characteristic area of ​​Wanmen is replaced by a military camp, and the construction cost is lower. When completed, cultural bombs are released to adjacent cells, allowing construction on the first ring of the city, without reducing the charm of adjacent cells, and obtaining a golden descendant when completed. [NEWLINE] Each building in this area provides 2 points of [ICON_Housing] housing for the city. The area gains productivity from adjacent mines and quarries, with each built Suspension Arena +2 combat power for all units.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MARBLE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yunshi Tiangong</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MARBLE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Agraya featured area unlocked by irrigation, alternative canals, less construction costs and provides more [ICON_Housing] housing with [ICON_Gold] adjacent bonus, which adds charm and adjacent bonus to adjacent cells. [NEWLINE] When completed, a golden descendant will be given away. After completion, the city's [ICON_Citizen] population will be immediately filled to the [ICON_Housing] housing cap, and the city's plantation improvement facilities will be +1 [ICON_Food] food, +2 [ICON_Production] productivity. [NEWLINE] Each Marble Heavenly Palace is +20% for the construction area [ICON_Production] productivity, and the adjacent area adjacent to the Marble Heavenly Palace is +100%. For every marble heavenly palace on the field, [NEWLINE] all marble heavenly palaces can produce an additional 1 [ICON_Amenities] livability, 1 [ICON_Housing] housing, 2 [ICON_Food] food and 2 [ICON_Production] productivity.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_TREE_COURT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tree Garden</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_TREE_COURT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The characteristic area of ​​Nakshaxia, which replaces the academy, has higher construction costs but also has higher basic output, and has [ICON_Culture] cultural value adjacent bonus instead of the usual [ICON_Science] technology value. When it was completed, a Golden Man was obtained, a cultural bomb was released on adjacent cells and a wall was built in the city. When completed, natural forests will be generated in cells within the second ring road of this city. After completion, newly trained builders +1 usage count. The buildings +2 housing in the area, the foundation and buildings in the area are the woods +1 technology value +1 productivity, rainforest +1 cultural value +2 gold coins, and a random [ICON_Science] technology is given.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_A_JOURNEY_BY_FIRE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The journey to the fire</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_A_JOURNEY_BY_FIRE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The special project of Tirisipios requires the area &quot;Cefal Square&quot;. During the [NEWLINE] project execution, the city released a large amount of [ICON_Religion] religious pressure on each round and provided four times the [ICON_Faith] faith value and the Great Prophet's points for the &quot;Holy Land Prayer&quot;. [NEWLINE]After the completion of the project, the religion of Tirisipius will be spread to all cities, and the city's external export pressure will be increased by 400%. [NEWLINE]After completing the project, all &quot;Kefale Square&quot; +2 [ICON_Faith] belief values ​​and +2 [ICON_Tourism] tourism performance, and receive 1 Golden Gen (if available).</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_NW_WANDI_COMBAT_STRENGTH_FOR_ALL_UNIT_DESC" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{Property} From the city livability</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
