<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Mon Oct 23 18:09:08 2023-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_PEN_VICTORIA_LOCATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>unknown</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_PEN_VICTORIA_SIZE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>unknown</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_PEN_VICTORIA_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>unknown</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_PEN_VICTORIA_CAPITAL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Londinium</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A handful of red wheat. The earth breeds life, and life feeds the earth.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bagpipes</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Meticulous in combat and farming, ignorant of electronics and trends.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Graduated from the Victoria Royal Guards School, served in the Victoria Army for three years, retired and joined Rhode Island after being introduced by Superintendent Chen. Professional soldiers who have received systematic training, after a period of time, have demonstrated professional combat skills and tactical literacy in various missions in Rhode Island.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The results of the imaging test showed that the internal organs of the operator were clearly outlined and no abnormal shadows were seen. The detection of Originium particles in the circulatory system showed no abnormality. There were no signs of ore disease infection. At this stage, it can be confirmed that he is not infected with ore disease.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][Somatic cells and Origin Stone fusion rate] 0%
[NEWLINE]Operator Bagpipe shows no signs of being infected by Originium.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]【Blood Origin Stone Crystal Density】0.11u/L
[NEWLINE]Operator Bagpipe rarely comes into contact with the Originium.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Even in Vaifan, this little girl's body is one of the best I have ever seen. I even want to see if she can really fight off ori disease if she uses her physical fitness... Well, this probably won't work. Try it? No, not very good.
[NEWLINE]——Warfarin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A lively girl from Victoria.
[NEWLINE] She is a good girl next door who is very familiar with herself and cares about others subconsciously. After entering Rhode Island, she quickly formed a good relationship with most of the operators.
[NEWLINE] In terms of life attitude, she is informal at best and careless at worst. At first glance, it is difficult to connect her with the serious image of a soldier. At least in life, her military side has not been shown much.
[NEWLINE] He and Superintendent Chen attended the Royal Victoria Guards School together. According to my description, the two formed a deep friendship during their school days. Superintendent Chen will sigh when he hears Bagpipe's name, but judging from her willingness to vouch for Miss Bagpipe's identity, the personal relationship between the two is not that bad.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Of course, of course, although she feels like a sunny girl next door, Miss Bagpipe is indeed a regular soldier who served in Victoria, and she is also a very good soldier.
[NEWLINE]The Royal Guards School educates students in many directions. Different from other systems of military training, the Victoria Royal Guards School has its own educational policy: among the three training directions, most of the guards serve as bodyguards for the royal family, nobles and various dignitaries after graduation, while officers generally serve as military officers. Senior commanders and noncommissioned officers generally serve as the backbone field leaders and breakthrough initiators of the army.
[NEWLINE]As a graduated non-commissioned officer, Miss Bagpipe undoubtedly possesses excellent military talents.
[NEWLINE]In fact, there are differences in the implementation level between the training of operators and ordinary soldiers.
[NEWLINE] Operators emphasize individual and team combat. In the training of operators, the most important thing is to teach students according to their aptitude and maximize their personal strengths. Just like the individual operators on Rhodes Island, operators need to maximize their own uniqueness and rely on a small number of elite forces to cooperate to complete targeted goals.
[NEWLINE] Military personnel place more emphasis on the collective. In the training of military personnel, what is needed is comprehensive development, standardization and replaceability. The military will make decisions based on functions rather than individuals to ensure the stability and efficiency of the team.
[NEWLINE] A qualified soldier's comprehensive combat capability must be higher than that of a qualified operator. But in fact, the two do not constitute a comparison, because from the beginning, the profession of operator is not suitable for war, and war should be avoided as much as possible.
[NEWLINE] Therefore, Miss Bagpipe cannot directly become an operator role model to guide ordinary operators to learn. In fact, as early as when Instructor Dupin, professional soldier Jian Lei, and Shining Knight Linguang joined Rhode Island, although They quickly adapted to the situation, but at the beginning, the military training they received still caused them to show many aspects that were contrary to Rhodes Island's combat policy.
[NEWLINE] However, Bagpipe, who passed the military training test with perfect results and participated in the war as a member of the frontline troops, truly showed Rhode Island what an outstanding soldier on active duty should look like, which is a challenge to some who think they can It should be a small wake-up call for operators who are struggling against the army, or simply lack understanding of the army.
[NEWLINE]Although her city-breaking spear has lost its projectile function, it is still a terrifying war weapon. Please don’t try it with your life.
[NEWLINE] In addition, it is worth mentioning that, perhaps because of her cheerful nature, or because the Royal Guards School’s outstanding education is worthy of its reputation, Miss Bagpipe did not go through the adaptation period from soldier to operator, and she quickly became an operator character of.
[NEWLINE]As an operator, she possesses the toughness and discipline of a soldier; as a soldier, she possesses the mobility and adaptability of an operator. Even Instructor Dubin made this comment in private, &quot;What makes Victoria far better than other countries is the professional quality of their soldiers.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Even after going through the Royal Guards School and the baptism of modern life after graduation, Miss Bagpipe, who was born in a nomadic village in Victoria, still has a strong sense of country.
[NEWLINE] On the one hand, this is due to the influence of rural life itself, and on the other hand, it seems to be due to his mother's education since childhood - as we all know, Vaifan women are usually very powerful.
[NEWLINE] She has been helping her family with farming and animal husbandry since she was a child. After joining Rhode Island, she immediately became involved with the logistics operators responsible for related affairs and contributed valuable resources to Rhode Island’s planting and animal husbandry undertakings. With her experience and strength, her enthusiasm even made people think that she had transferred to the logistics department.
[NEWLINE] In addition, regarding her familiarity with various large-scale agricultural equipment, unfortunately, due to limited space, the planting scale in Rhode Island only allows the use of small tractors, which prevents her from showing her talents. After all, we can't let her drive the Rhode Island ship.
[NEWLINE]Of course, this does not mean that Miss Bagpipe has no knowledge of modern life, she just tried it and failed. This can be seen from her relatively frequent requests for equipment repairs compared to other operators.
[NEWLINE] Moreover, according to her, she also learned how to dress up from aristocratic classmates when she was a student, but the results were really embarrassing, and she gave up her efforts in this area over time, but it is obvious that Miss Bagpipe still cares about herself. Performances such as clothing and appearance... When he was a soldier, his attire was impeccable, but once he talked to her about his normal clothes and appearance, she always appeared worried.
[NEWLINE]No need, Miss Bagpipe. Many operators think you are cute enough on your own.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_VICTORIA_PEN_BAGPIPE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>pastoral</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_VICTORIA_PEN_BAGPIPE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Work to keep citizens happy and loyal. Like civilizations with similar governance attitudes; hate civilizations that have problems with happiness and loyalty.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_REASON_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Your city is very livable)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_PEN_BAGPIPE_HIGH_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>She likes civilizations where citizens are happy and happy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_REASON_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Your citizens need a higher habitability level.)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_PEN_BAGPIPE_LOW_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>She hates a civilization whose citizens are unhappy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I feel ashamed of this uniform...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I feel ashamed of this uniform...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Great! That’s it!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Can not be done……</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I've seen far worse situations, both in school and in the military.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The enemy has fled! Follow me in pursuit!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh...that's awesome...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I hope that the people of the two countries can communicate more freely.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well...that's not possible yet.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Please, can you open your borders to us?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PEN_VICTORIA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Londinium</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Highbury</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>sadeen district</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Askara County</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Duolun County</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xiaoqiu County</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Connor County</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>peninsula county</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kaiwen County</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Claybrasson</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tonel village</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oak Tree</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Linton</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Caraton</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lucian</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fischer</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Feist</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>charlie seymour</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tottel</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Elias Kurtz</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tracy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Edward</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Adam</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>forest</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fiona Young</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ravshini</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jane Wayne</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Susie Gritt</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Heidi Thomson</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rita Scamanderos</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Vina</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hannah</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>isabel montagu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Grace Arizona</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MODERN_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lucian</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fischer</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Feist</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>charlie seymour</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tottel</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Elias Kurtz</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tracy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Edward</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Adam</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_MALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>forest</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fiona Young</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ravshini</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jane Wayne</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Susie Gritt</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Heidi Thomson</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rita Scamanderos</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Vina</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hannah</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>isabel montagu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PEN_VICTORIA_MODERN_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Grace Arizona</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>victoria</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>victorian</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_PEN_VICTORIA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>victoria</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_PEN_SUN_NEVER_SETS_HEGEMON_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The sun never sets on hegemony</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_PEN_SUN_NEVER_SETS_HEGEMON_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Occupying cities does not reduce the population, owns non-Victorian cities with +1 livability, +35% [ICON_GOLD] gold, provides civilization with +5% [ICON_SCIENCE] technology value, and gains +5 [ICON_GOLD] gold from domestic trade routes. Each original capital owned provides Victoria with +3 diplomatic support each turn.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ROYAL_GUARD_ACADEMY_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Royal College of Guards</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ROYAL_GUARD_ACADEMY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Instead of barracks, municipal &quot;military traditions&quot; are unlocked and are cheaper to build. The area and each of its buildings provide +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] productivity to surrounding farms. Provides +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] productivity when producing military units, and an additional +15% if the city also has an industrial zone. The strategic resource cost required by the production unit in the city is reduced by 50%. Its productivity bonus also provides technology value.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_DISTRICT_ROYAL_GUARD_ACADEMY_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Royal College of Guards</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_DISTRICT_ROYAL_GUARD_ACADEMY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Instead of barracks, municipal &quot;military traditions&quot; are unlocked and are cheaper to build. The area and each of its buildings provide +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] productivity to surrounding farms. Provides +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] productivity when producing military units, and an additional +15% if the city also has an industrial zone. The strategic resource cost required by the production unit in the city is reduced by 50%. Its productivity bonus also provides technology value.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_PEN_STEAM_KNIGHT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>steam knight</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_PEN_STEAM_KNIGHT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Replaces the Cuirassier, has higher combat effectiveness, is able to jump with a radius of 4, and requires coal for maintenance. After researching &quot;steam power&quot;, the combat effectiveness is further improved, and it can cause full damage to the city wall.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_UNIT_PEN_STEAM_KNIGHT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>steam knight</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_UNIT_PEN_STEAM_KNIGHT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Replaces the Cuirassier, has higher combat effectiveness, is able to jump with a radius of 4, and requires coal for maintenance. After researching &quot;steam power&quot;, the combat effectiveness is further improved, and it can cause full damage to the city wall.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PEN_VICTORIA_JUNP_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Steam Rider-Jump</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PEN_VICTORIA_JUNP_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Steam Knight is able to jump with a radius of 4</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PEN_VICTORIA_ATTACK_WALL_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Steam Rider-Vaporization</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PEN_VICTORIA_ATTACK_WALL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After researching &quot;steam power&quot;, the steam knight's combat effectiveness is further improved, and it can cause full damage to the city wall.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PEN_VICTORIA_ATTACK_WALL_STR_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} from steam power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bagpipes</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bagpipe, graduated from the Victoria Royal Guards School. After serving in the Victoria Army for three years, he retired and joined Rhode Island through the introduction of Superintendent Chen. Professional soldiers who have received systematic training, after a period of time, have demonstrated professional combat skills and tactical literacy in various missions in Rhode Island.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bagpipe, graduated from the Victoria Royal Guards School. After serving in the Victoria Army for three years, he retired and joined Rhode Island through the introduction of Superintendent Chen. Professional soldiers who have received systematic training, after a period of time, have demonstrated professional combat skills and tactical literacy in various missions in Rhode Island.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_MILITARY_TRADITION_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>military tradition</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_MILITARY_TRADITION_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>All military units gain an additional 8 XP initially and after each promotion. Killing an enemy can obtain [ICON_GOLD] gold coins equivalent to 100% of the enemy's basic combat power. After a military unit is killed, [ICON_GOLD] gold coins equivalent to 100% of the basic productivity will be returned. Royal Guards Schools receive standard adjacency bonuses from adjacent farms.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PEN_VICTORIA_UNIT_GOLD_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>rusher</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_PEN_VICTORIA_UNIT_GOLD_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>All military units gain an additional 8 XP initially and after each promotion. Killing an enemy can obtain [ICON_GOLD] gold coins equivalent to 100% of the enemy's basic combat power. After a military unit is killed, [ICON_GOLD] gold coins equivalent to 100% of the basic productivity will be returned.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_FARM_1_PRODUCTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Adjacent farms provide +{1_num} [ICON_PRODUCTION] productivity.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let’s go do farm work together!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Now is not the time.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Want to go on a picnic? Just the two of us!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Great!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Eh?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Me and my city-breaking spear, from Victoria!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let me lead the team and immediately execute the battle plan and attack!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hello! I'm a bagpiper! Welcome to visit our country!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Would you like to visit some of our nearby cities?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Can I visit a city near you?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Can you share the location of the capital city with you? However, Londinium's city walls are very strong.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You are a trustworthy person.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for the delegation, I will treat them well.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...Uh...Sorry, I can't greet your delegation yet.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Would you like to receive our delegation in your capital?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>An inadvertent action may lead to more mistakes.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>No matter where I am, I have never seen anyone more evil than you!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Avoiding can't solve any problem.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let us fight side by side.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_PEN_BAGPIPE_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>All available! stand at attention! Enter combat readiness!</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
