<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun Oct 26 16:13:03 2025-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_NW_PHAINON_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Baie</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_NW_PHAINON" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In Xindan at the end of the world, the hero raised his sword reflecting the twilight, fighting and chasing the dusk night. Bai E's chest is dancing with shining stars, his eyes are burning like the dead sun disk, shooting silver needles towards the barren land. He hid his name, kept silent, buried the past in the hometown solidified in his memory, and vowed to defend the new dawn to the death. Even if that dawn will burn everything.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_NW_PHAINON_NW_PHAINON_CREATE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The fire that accommodates the &quot;negative world&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_NW_PHAINON_NW_PHAINON_CREATE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After every 20 rounds, Bai E will embark on the &quot;Eternal Return&quot;. During this period, Bai E can collect a fire ability each round. After collecting the fire, Baie will transform into Caeslana and immediately form an army with all combat units. Each time Eternal Calamity returns, Bai E gets +10% of all great man points and -20% of war exhaustion. After the war weariness is completely eliminated, all units will have +10 [ICON_Strength] combat strength +2 [ICON_Movement] movement strength. Moreover, as reincarnations intertwine, the fire may become more and more bright...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_NW_PHAINON_NW_PHAINON_CREATE2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>kauslana</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_NW_PHAINON_NW_PHAINON_CREATE2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After transformation, gain damage value equal to the number of completed &quot;Eternal Returns&quot;. If you have the civilization characteristic building &quot;Destruction&quot;, the damage value acquisition efficiency will be +100%. When a city produces a unit, it gets a copy of the unit based on the damage value.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_BAIE_GOVERNMENT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Creation Vortex Heart</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_BAIE_GOVERNMENT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Baie characteristic area, replacing the municipal square. [NEWLINE] In addition to the original bonuses, after completion, you will also get policy card effects unlocked through municipal administration or technology. The policy card effects obtained in this way will not expire and can be superimposed with the policy card itself. Unlocks the city's ability to produce Goldenborn.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Negative World&quot; [NEWLINE] provides research progress, municipal progress, faith value, gold coins for civilization based on the total number of fires, and provides production progress for all cities.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Sky&quot; [NEWLINE] heals all own units. The healed units will provide experience points to themselves and surrounding units.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>「海洋」[NEWLINE]已改良的奢侈品+1 [ICON_Amenities] 宜居度+1 [ICON_CULTURE] 文化值+1 [ICON_GOLD] 金币。</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;The Land&quot; [NEWLINE] Improved bonus resources +1 [ICON_HOUSING] Housing +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Productivity +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Years&quot; [NEWLINE] repeatedly obtains a fire effect from the past.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button5_BAN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Years&quot; [NEWLINE] repeatedly obtains a fire effect from the past. [NEWLINE][COLOR_Civ6Red]You must already own a Tinder[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Law&quot;[NEWLINE]According to the number of fires, strategic resources are obtained from unlocked and military policy cards within the government, gold coins are obtained from economic policy cards, envoys, governor points and faith values ​​are obtained from foreign policy cards, and great man points, technology values ​​and culture are obtained from wildcard policy cards.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Gateway&quot; [NEWLINE] The Goldens already owned can open the Hundred Realms Gate. After the Hundred Realms Gate is opened, other Goldens can no longer open the Hundred Realms Gate, but all units can be teleported to the location of the unit that opened the Hundred Realms Gate each round. The Goldens who have opened the Hundred Realms Gate can lead surrounding units back to the nearest own city at any time.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Trick&quot; [NEWLINE] Immediately obtain era points for the current round number and the total amount of fire collected, and immediately obtain gold coins that are the product of the number of activated trade routes, the number of spies owned, and the total amount of fire collected.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Death&quot; [NEWLINE] After the death of a friendly unit in this round, the faith value equal to the number of rounds * 16% of the productivity required to produce the unit will be returned, and 1 additional combat power will be provided to all friendly units.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Dispute&quot; [NEWLINE] resets the movement and attack times of all your units, and gives all your units a combat effectiveness equal to the number of reincarnations. Killing units will also gain general points.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Romantic&quot; [NEWLINE] +8% encouragement, immediately obtain 8 items of encouragement, and provide municipal progress equal to the total number of fires. If the &quot;rational&quot; fire has been activated this cycle, the effect will be doubled.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_NeiKos496InstanceA_Button12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Rationality&quot; [NEWLINE] +8% Eureka, immediately obtain 8 Eureka items, providing research progress equal to the total number of fires. If the &quot;Romance&quot; fire has been activated this cycle, the effect will be doubled.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_NEIKOS496_COREFLAME_STRENGTH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{Num} comes from the selected fire effect.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_COREFLAME1_OPEN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Open the Gate of Hundred Realms</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_COREFLAME1_MAINTRANS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Return to nearest city</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_COREFLAME1_OTHERTRANS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Teleport to the location of Baijiemen</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_FIRE_BAIE_TT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Use fire to create the world again.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_FIRE_BAIE_PROGRESS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>12 fire types need to be collected</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TOOLTIP_TRADITIONAL_DOMINATION_BUTTON" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tinder</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_WORLD_RANKINGS_TRADITIONAL_DOMINATION_TAB" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tinder</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORYSTATUS_TRADITIONAL_DOMINATION_PANEL_HEADER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tinder collection</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_FIRE_BAIE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tinder</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_FIRE_BAIE_SUBHEADER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tinder</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_WORLD_RANKINGS_TRADITIONAL_DOMINATION_VICTORY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tinder collection</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_WORLD_RANKINGS_TRADITIONAL_DOMINATION_PROGRESS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tinder collection victory progress</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_FIRE_BAIE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In order to achieve [COLOR:ResMilitaryLabelCS]Fire Collection[ENDCOLOR] victory, you need to use Baier (demigod) to collect 12 fires. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE] It is recommended to use Bai E (demigod) to play the game.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_WORLD_RANKINGS_TRADITIONAL_DOMINATION_DESC_LAST" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] The fire required to win the fire collection:</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_WORLD_RANKINGS_TRADITIONAL_DOMINATION_TT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Number of fire types owned:</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_VICTORY_FIRE_BAIE_TEXT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You have collected all the fire, and we look forward to meeting you in the new world.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
