<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Fri Mar 22 22:40:58 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GHILDEGARD_OF_BINGEN_TRAIT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If the holy land has at least a first-level building, the city will have +10% [ICON_Science] technology value.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_KHJY_OH_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ojo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_KHJY_OH_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>King of Happiness</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_KHJY_OH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I like civilizations with large populations, especially those with high gold coin income; I don’t like civilizations with sparse populations and low gold coin income.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You are very capable of governing the country, so we must encourage each other.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_DESCRIPTION_HIGH_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oho appreciates your way of governing the country.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oops...it's really miserable for your people to be ruled by people without talent.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_DESCRIPTION_LOW_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ouhu looks down on your incompetence</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_KHJY_OH_LOADING_INFO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The little prince of God's fingers, the calf horns of God's Son, the apple of the eyes of the guardians of the empire, the martyrs are also opening the way for you. Ouhuo, the king of happiness who brings happiness to the world, now the responsibility of bringing happiness to the world falls on you. Use your knowledge to feed people and bring your empire to new heights, and you will finally regain your dreams.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_KHJY_OH_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jizenian</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_KHJY_OH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Farmland +2 [ICON_Food] Food when adjacent to at least one Mississippi Mound. When replacing improved facilities with [ICON_District] area, you will immediately get 120 [ICON_Gold] gold coins once (the actual effect changes with the game speed). After unlocking [Political Philosophy]/[Divine Right of Kings]/[Economy], you can get an additional 1/1/ respectively. 2 times [ICON_Gold] gold coins.
[NEWLINE] [ICON_GreatWork_Artifact] Artifacts and [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] Relics provide 3x [ICON_Tourism] Tourism Performance and +2 [ICON_Culture] Culture if no other output bonus.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ojo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The second generation monarch of Keluqiya, King of Happiness, later known as: King of Adventure</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_KHJY_OH_QUOTE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thanks to the guidance of God's guidance and the teachings of God's Son, I will definitely be able to live up to everyone's expectations and bring an ideal world.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_KHJY_OH_QUOTE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I am also part of the people of Kedokiya and I certainly have a responsibility to look out for my own good.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Ouhuo, also known as Niujiao Ouhuo, was a monarch who suffered from conflicting emotions in the history of the Kedokiya Empire. He is Ji De's favorite disciple and is expected to become the next great monarch. At the beginning of taking over the rule, he showed excellent leadership skills, especially in farming, which led to a period of population explosion and prosperity in the Kedokiya Empire, named [Jize Year].</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] However, midway through his reign, Ojo fell into a situation where he lost himself. Indulging in pleasure and neglecting government affairs, his rule became more indulgent and laissez-faire. Although the Kedokiya Empire had a large population during this period, its political and social order gradually shook, causing a lot of controversy and dissatisfaction.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Ojo's life direction changed dramatically at the moment he was overthrown. Ji De, the mentor he had always admired and followed, was disappointed with his fall. Dubbed the &quot;Greedy King&quot;, Ojo was strongly criticized. At this critical moment, Jide's criticism became the trigger for his awakening.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] The exiled Oho begins his journey around the world, pursuing the adventure he has dreamed of since he was a child. He experienced many unknown worlds, witnessed various strange landscapes, and tasted exotic food. This wandering career has become a good story in &quot;Adventure King Ouhuo&quot;. The experience and wisdom he accumulated during the journey made him more mature and profound.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Ouhuo finally found his original intention. Although he can no longer rule the empire, as a wise man, he has made an indelible contribution to the cultural inheritance and prosperity of Kedokiya with his adventure stories and insights. The legend of Oho became a unique and profound chapter in the history of the Kedokiya Empire.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The construction of Kedokia's specialized area can be carried out very early. When completed, territory can be captured through cultural bombs. It itself can also provide flexible governance methods, and the builders who are initially gifted can also develop the territory earlier. .
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Under Ojo, the [ICON_Food] farmland built around the Mississippi Mounds ensured that the people never went hungry. When the population surges to a certain critical point, or when it is in great need, Ojo can get a considerable amount of [ICON_Gold] cash by replacing improved facilities with areas.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]At the same time, the relics and cultural relics obtained by Ouhuo are more attractive. The triple [ICON_Tourism] tourism performance and additional [ICON_Culture] cultural value allow Ouhuo to easily achieve cultural victory.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokia's zone building is often accompanied by culture bombs to the point where they can &quot;peacefully&quot; take over your territory, and it's not a good idea to peacefully coexist in close quarters with such a neighbor. [Mississippi Mound] can maintain the early economy of Kedoqiya, and the existence of [Urban City] also allows Kedoqiya to build a high-development city with high bonus trade routes and areas.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The farmland surrounding the Mississippi Mounds is of great [ICON_Food] value to Ojo, and if necessary, an area of ​​improvement projects can be immediately planned to extract [ICON_Gold] gold coins.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] At the same time, relics and relics are very threatening in his hands [ICON_Tourism] and almost unrivaled in terms of [ICON_Culture] cultural triumphs.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oops, hello! I am Ouhuo, the King of Happiness. Under the guidance of God’s Finger Chosen Zhao and God’s Son, I will create an ideal world.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Are you coming from far away? Come to my court as a guest, I am a worthy host.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>real? That's great, let's go!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Are you coming from far away? Come to my palace as a guest, and tell me about your hometown?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hello!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for the gift, I like it very much.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sorry, I've seen this stuff and I'm not interested.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hello! My emissary came with my old toys, and some cash as you probably look down on these little toys.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Then they ask you to take good care of them.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oops...sad.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>embassy! embassy! I want to establish an embassy in your capital!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zany!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>ah.....</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hee hee, go ahead, go ahead. Go ahead with confidence.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ahhh...I'm sorry~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey! Please open your borders to us.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Then, you are my 101st friend!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ahaha... I'm so sorry, I've been too busy lately.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey! let's make friends.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Then, you are my 101st friend!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oops...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey friends, do you want to form an alliance?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Money is a good thing, but unfortunately it is not everything.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The population is so large, your burden will be heavy next~ Come on, come on!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You are already poor, so stop trying to be fat.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you think that with fewer people, everything will be fine? There are always people who can't stand it, like me.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_KHJY_OH_LIKE_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You may have forgotten your agreement with me, but I don't blame you. Because I already have the ability to achieve it myself...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_KHJY_OH_LIKE_GID" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sister Shenzi~♥</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_KHJY_OH_LIKE_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lord God, I will never let you down.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_MODIFIER_AGENDA_KHJY_OH_LIKE_LS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Respectable elders still have to show the proper attitude</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_KHJY_OH_LIKE_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I really don’t know how you dare to say something like that————You’re so handsome!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_KHJY_OH_LIKE_KM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although he is strict, he is a kind brother Cammu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GID_LIKE_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As long as you realize your mistakes and spend your life trying to make up for them, you will still be my student.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_GID_LIKE_KHJY_OH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>my students my best students</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LS_LIKE_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Maybe you don't realize it, but I've already seen your future...well, you're a good person.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_LS_LIKE_KHJY_OH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The best student of the Son of God is also the worst student...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ouch, did my eyes see a mirage? How did your army change from one or two to three, four or more? Huh~?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_HUMAN_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hee hee, I actually don’t really like this kind of joke.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don’t regret it once you’ve made the deal~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oops...sad.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I am part of the people of Kedokiya, and I certainly have an obligation to fulfill my own wishes. What is the problem?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oops...things are getting bad. [NEWLINE](condemn you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Looks like the friends game is over? Do you think you can fight against me who has received the teachings of God's Chosen Zhao and God's Son? [NEWLINE]Ahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ouch, is this city going to be given to me? Then I won't be polite.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I'm tired of playing war games, but friend games are more fun, what do you think?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tch...Who are you trying to fool?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tsk...this defeat is only temporary, but I won't resist this surrender...as long as it doesn't go too far.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How could...how could I...Sister Shenzi...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How could...how could I...Sister Shenzi...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_FLIRTATIOUS_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My court often hosts balls, why not come and dance with me?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_CURMUDGEON_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My court often holds balls, why not go on a beauty hunt?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_FLIRTATIOUS_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't get me wrong, I just love dancing. Bitch.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_CURMUDGEON_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There is someone in my heart, and you cannot take her place.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_STANDING_ARMY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oops~ We are friends, you won’t let your troops come to our place to hang out, right?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_STANDING_ARMY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hahahaha...Are you really not considering getting some thug bodyguards?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_CLEARS_BARBARIAN_CAMPS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Those foolish things always have to be broken up before we can become honest.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_IGNORES_BARBARIAN_CAMPS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Women uniting helps politics, but men uniting is another matter...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sister Shenzi said: &quot;Culture is proof of the existence of a civilized society.&quot; [NEWLINE] She will definitely like your civilization very much.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sister Shenzi once said: &quot;Culture is proof of the existence of a civilized society.&quot;[NEWLINE]We can't let her see shameful things like you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sister Shenzi said: &quot;The development of technology means how far a civilization can go.&quot; [NEWLINE] She will definitely like your civilization very much.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sister Shenzi once said: &quot;The development of technology means how far a civilization can go.&quot;[NEWLINE]Don't let her see shameful things like you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_GREAT_WHITE_FLEET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh~ What a spectacular fleet~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_GREAT_WHITE_FLEET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hehe~ I seem to have seen a fleet of model ships in a bottle.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_TOURISM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I very much welcome the people of your country to appreciate my past glory. First of all, I would like to thank Master Shenzhi for your appreciation and promotion, and Sister Shenzi for... (a thousand words are omitted below)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_TOURISM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey? Can you actually surpass me in travel performance? It's incredible.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_AIRPOWER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah ha ha ha... We are friends, you won't let your air force fly over our heads, right?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KHJY_OH_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_AIRPOWER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yeah, your airplane aviation show is so beautiful. Can you show it to me again?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_KM_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cammu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_KM_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unswerving defender of Taoism</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_KM_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Will not hesitate to condemn and always refuse to surrender. [NEWLINE] Likes not to interfere with civilizations he believes in, especially civilizations that declare friendship, and does not like civilizations that change his beliefs, especially civilizations that backstab and launch surprise wars.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wouldn't it be great if everyone could take responsibility for their commitments like you do?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_KM_BACKSTAB_AVERSE_FRIEND" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cammy believed in your integrity</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_KM_SAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cammy is glad you share his interests.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You deserve to die! He deserves to be just like those businessmen who are unscrupulous for profit, just like those oligarchs who always think they are noble, just like the bureaucrats who forget their responsibilities, just like the gangsters who add insult to injury to the sufferers, just like the insensitive patients who are indifferent to the world. Just as damnable!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_KM_BACKSTAB_AVERSE_SURPRISE_WAR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cammy hates unfair means</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_KM_ENCROACHING" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cammy is wary of your attempts to change his mind!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_KM_LOADING_INFO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gouyue Kanmu follows the son of God Ji De! You will surely be able to spread the truth to all mankind, and then everyone will be on the right path! Awesome, Gouyue Kammi, you can always find the shortcomings of those so-called sages. Now they are not qualified to preach the right way. Then it is up to you to spread your gospel and let your evangelists guide the world. Running track!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_KM_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Up the right path</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_KM_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When you own the Palace for the first time, you get an [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] relic. The [ICON_Faith] faith value provided by the [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] relic is tripled. Each Town Hall building provides an [ICON_GreatWork_Relic_Themed] Relic slot.
[NEWLINE]Allows the purchase of land combat and support units using [ICON_Faith] Faith.
[NEWLINE]Has the unique unit Death Knight.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cammu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Follower of the Son of God, defender of Taoism, leader of the Knights of Death</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_KM_QUOTE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There is no limit to the prevalence of evil, and I cannot believe that this is the land that my husband and I have spent our lives building.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_KM_QUOTE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In view of this 3207th betrayal from the oligarchs, we have no choice but to arm ourselves with all our assets. [NEWLINE]Then—all are reckoned with!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Kanmi, or &quot;Gouyue Canmi&quot;. He is known as the &quot;living fossil of Kdokiya&quot; and is an unusually long-lived leader in the history of the Kdokiya Empire. In his early years, Cammu met Ji De, the son of God who was traveling in North America in his hometown of Yilinoyi. This admirable girl conveyed the light of knowledge. The young and stubborn Cammu once challenged Ji De publicly, but was defeated by the then 5-year-old Shenzi in a debate. Jide's tolerant attitude changed Cammy, and he became Jide's attendant and followed her teachings throughout his life.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The existence of Kamuo caused quite a stir in the Kedokiya Empire. He constantly questioned Jide's teachings, but was forgiven by Jide even though he was regarded as a heretic by his compatriots. This unique relationship has made Cammu a controversial figure, but Jide insists people should learn from Cammu. People talked a lot about him, and some people unconditionally believed in the words of God's Son Ji De and began to learn from his mean and stubborn words and deeds. But more people, even if Ji De praised Cammiu, were very dissatisfied with him.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]However, Cammy was not affected by the rumors at all. His behavior, his character, and his tone were consistent, and his strong words attracted the attention of Leso, the founder of the Kedokiya Empire. . When he mocked him in front of Leso: &quot;You are just a bastard who wants to be the emperor in the republic!&quot;, Leso smiled tolerantly and said: &quot;On the contrary, I just became a governor in the empire. .”</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]At the beginning of the 17th century, fifty years had passed since Leso's death and Jide's disappearance. Cammy had reached the age of 83. After years of divisions, coups, and warlords, the Kedokiya Empire has become an oppressive and authoritarian society that is in decline, and Cammy deeply deplores it. In order to uphold Jide's ideals, he once tried to be a wandering singer and use his singing to awaken people's insensitive souls. In the end, he woke up after being arrested and persecuted again and again, and formed a quasi-theocratic force - the Knights of Death. Under the leadership of Cammy, the Knights of Death tried to establish an ideal society with equal human rights. However, they eventually disappeared in the conflict with new weapons and nuclear weapons, becoming the end of the era.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Cammu's leadership style was tenacious, and although his actions divisive society, he left a legacy of legend and defiance in history. The Keluqiya Empire is a glimpse in the scroll of human history. The romantic glory of Kammu in his later years is enough to compete with the prosperity of the era of Ji De and Lesuo, but it has also ushered in an inevitable end.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The construction of Kedokia's specialized area can be carried out very early. When completed, territory can be captured through cultural bombs. It itself can also provide flexible governance methods, and the builders who are initially gifted can also develop the territory earlier. .
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Compared to other leaders of Kedokia, Kammu's ability was developed last, but it is worth it. It is entirely possible to consider religious victory or conquest victory as well as cultural victory.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]For Cammy, the [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] relic [ICON_Faith] is the most important, he can get 3 times the faith value of [ICON_Faith] from it. At the same time, Cammu can use [ICON_Faith] faith value to purchase land combat units and support units, which to a certain extent gives Cammu a combat advantage.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Although the Death Knights are expensive, their unique promotion tree is definitely worth the money. Their swift mobility can quickly rush to any battlefield, and they have the ability to provide medical support to nearby friendly units, while themselves The combat threat it can pose cannot be underestimated. What's more, their efficiency in learning from experience is unrivaled.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KM_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokia's zone building is often accompanied by culture bombs to the point where they can &quot;peacefully&quot; take over your territory, and it's not a good idea to peacefully coexist in close quarters with such a neighbor. [Mississippi Mound] can maintain the early economy of Kedoqiya, and the existence of [Urban City] also allows Kedoqiya to build a high-development city with high bonus trade routes and areas.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] By building the original capital, Cammu can get an [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] relic that produces more [ICON_Faith] faith values. If he loses the capital, he can get another [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] relic. For this purpose, his Civic Center building There is a [ICON_GreatWork_Relic_Themed] relic slot specifically for placing [ICON_GreatWork_Relic] relics. Moreover, Cammu can use [ICON_Faith] faith value to purchase land combat units and support units, which to a certain extent brings Cammu an advantage in battle. It's good to think about religious victories or victories of conquest as well as cultural victories.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]As an AI, Cammy will not hesitate to condemn and retaliate firmly against anyone who betrays him. Although he will not launch a surprise war, you will always be wary of this madman pursuing justice. .</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stop, who are you? What are you doing in a place like this?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I am Cammi, a student of the Son of God and the spiritual leader of the people of Kedokiya. This is not the place to talk, come and talk at one of our nearby strongholds.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...Then let's set off.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I am Cammi, a student of the Son of God and the spiritual leader of the people of Kedokiya. Please tell us where you are from and we will invite you to visit our base.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We will issue them self-defense weapons.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We have nothing to entertain you here, so go back.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Deep breath)...Gui'an, considering that you are foreigners after all, we have purchased some gifts for you during this visit.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It’s not that difficult either…</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...Tsk.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let's formalize diplomatic relations, let's build an embassy.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Um……</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...Tsk.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You should understand what this means.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I don't believe you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>By the way, I, Kanmi, will never betray you even if I promise you a thousand pieces of gold.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Then we are comrades.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let's... (take a deep breath)... form a friendship.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well...thank you...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...Tsk.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's time for us to take the next step toward alliances, come on.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_ANY_REASON_AGENDA_KM_SAME_RELIGION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let us fight for our common ideals and let the gospel of truth be delivered to the world, comrade.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_ANY_REASON_AGENDA_KM_ENCROACHING_RELIGION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stop leading people astray! I will punish you one day.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_KM_LIKE_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I haven't lost my respect for you, sir. No matter how disappointing you are.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_KM_LIKE_GID" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My husband, my guide, my judge, my traitor</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_KM_LIKE_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Betrayal is betrayal, and the meeting ceases to exist because of you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_KM_LIKE_LS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A tyrant with two moments of tyranny</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_KM_LIKE_KHJY_OH_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I have nothing to say to you.....</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_KM_LIKE_KHJY_OH_KM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Disappointing little traitor...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GID_LIKE_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What I like most is the firm will in you, which is what I long for...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_GID_LIKE_KM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A determined man must bring vitality to society...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LS_LIKE_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Boy, you are a real man. Even powerful things cannot break your heart.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_LS_LIKE_KM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I see my own reflection in you</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I don't care if you do it intentionally or not, I will transfer you from the army immediately!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_HUMAN_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>That's fine. Please forgive me for being emotional just now.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Um……</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...Tsk.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I was wrong? Where did I go wrong? Just wait, I'll come to your door right away to discuss it with you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You bastard are really not a human being! [NEWLINE](condemn you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My husband told me that the truth cannot be defeated!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I fight for the truth! And you will definitely fail.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I don't want to get things done.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you even want to bully others in this regard? !</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I can't beat you, I admit it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The truth cannot be defeated...but why would I be defeated...just like Mr.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KM_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The truth cannot be defeated...but why would I be defeated...just like Mr.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_FLIRTATIOUS_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I think I must be a pervert. When I see you, I can’t think of anything else...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_CURMUDGEON_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's a real pleasure to do things with you, unlike suitors who bring so many worries.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_FLIRTATIOUS_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank God, I finally lost interest in you and will no longer be affected by your asshole.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_CURMUDGEON_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't look at me like this, I'm already quite old, and I've already reserved a place in my heart for a damn... guy who's already dead...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sigh... Money, money, money is needed everywhere. Can you teach me how you make money?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ill-gotten gains, do you think your income is worthy of your people?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There is such a large population...can you guarantee their happiness?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ten rooms and nine empty rooms...You must be a tyrant, right?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_STANDING_ARMY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Why can't the iron discipline of the military cultivate the quality of the people? It's great that you think so too.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_STANDING_ARMY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your people are afraid of military service, huh?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_CLEARS_BARBARIAN_CAMPS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>These gangsters should have been killed long ago.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_IGNORES_BARBARIAN_CAMPS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Are you with those gangsters? If not, just kill them quickly!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The husband said: &quot;Culture is proof of the existence of a civilized society.&quot; [NEWLINE] Seeing all this, she must have a comforting smile on her face.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The husband said: &quot;Culture is proof of the existence of a civilized society.&quot; [NEWLINE] You don't seem to want your civilization to exist?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The husband said: &quot;The development of technology means how far a civilization can go.&quot; [NEWLINE] It's a pity that she can no longer see it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The gentleman said: &quot;The development of technology means how far a civilization can go.&quot; [NEWLINE] And you have to pay taxes when you stop in Keduqiya.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_GREAT_WHITE_FLEET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>One day, I will build a fleet as huge as yours.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_GREAT_WHITE_FLEET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You should not ignore the strength of the fleet, nor should you ignore my challenge.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_TOURISM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We always welcome people to appreciate and learn from Mr.’s legacy. Do you want to come too?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_TOURISM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't think that your husband's legacy will be compared to you. One day people will recognize her will.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_DIPLOVP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My way is clear and right, follow me.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_DIPLOVP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My path is clear and correct, and it will never be the untouchable fantasy you brought to everyone!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_TURTLER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You have always been able to do your own thing well, rather than invading the outside world. This is something I admire very much...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_TURTLER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you think we won’t know about your evil deeds? I will punish you one day.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_AIRPOWER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>One day, I will build an air force as great as yours.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_AIRPOWER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You should not ignore air power, and you should not ignore my challenge.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_SYCOPHANT_GOLDEN_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It’s such an enviable and wonderful era, but I still don’t understand why she always avoids him.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_SYCOPHANT_DARK_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What I appreciate about your will is that she never wants to see people living in dire straits.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_SYMPATHIZER_DARK_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It’s a really sad time of suffering, but unlike my husband, I don’t think suffering should exist.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_KM_REASON_AGENDA_SYMPATHIZER_GOLDEN_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What I appreciate about your will is that she never wants to see people indulge in false prosperity.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
