<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun May  7 18:59:54 2023-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ADDIS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Addis</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ADDIS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Addis Empire</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_ADDIS_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Addis</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_ALL_HOME_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cosmopolitan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_ALL_HOME_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ignores tech request to display [ICON_RESOURCE_Iron] iron resource. Cannot produce settlers, rewards a settler every time you clear a barbarian outpost. +1 [ICON_TradeRoute] trade route capacity per conquered city. Gain the &quot;Cartography&quot; technology after building the Armory for the first time.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_RUJIA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>B&amp;B</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_RUJIA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Replaces barracks but non-featured areas, cheaper to build. +1 [ICON_HOUSING] housing. Anti-cavalry units produced from this area have +1 [ICON_Movement] movement. +3 Loyalty per turn for the city you are in.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JLZ_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>marauder</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JLZ_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zhang Yu Medieval Anti-Cavalry Unit, replacing Spearmen. +10 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength when fighting on a continent other than the one where your capital is located. Can consume 1 [ICON_Movement] movement to loot. Upgrade to spear and shoot phalanx.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_FH_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>military</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_FH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Addis is a characteristic anti-cavalry unit in the classical period. It replaces spearmen. It has stronger combat effectiveness but higher maintenance costs. +10 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength when fighting barbarians. +5 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength when attacking area defense. Upgrade to Marauder.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_ZHANGYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zhang Yu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_ZHANGYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>budget carefully</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_ZHANGYU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After conquering a city, all units within 3 tiles gain bonus experience. Each battle unit has an additional +2 [ICON_Strength] combat strength for each promotion. [ICON_Gold] maintenance cost -1 for combat units per turn when at war with a major civilization.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_ZHANGYU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zhang Yu, an excellent leader! In your opinion, the strength of an army does not depend on the quantity, but on the strength and well-equipped of the soldiers! The soldiers under your command are not afraid of dangers and defeat all the enemies on the battlefield! And if you look around the world, brave raiders will bring you good news in distant lands! Don't care about other people's gossip and slander, you will eventually build a magnificent empire that amazes the world!</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
