<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Mondstadt_Texts_en -->
<!-- Author: zdaoting -->
<!-- DateCreated: 7/17/2023 8:10:12 AM -->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Otto</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Albert</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rudolf</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wood</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Athos</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Payne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jack</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Charles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Anthony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Miles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Aramis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Monroe</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wyratt</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Porthos</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Quinn</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Nelson</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cyrus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bruce</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Huffman</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_MALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Schulz</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jilliana</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Vile</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Victoria</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Nora</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ellin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Beatrice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Donna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Flora</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hertha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Marjorie</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Grace</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lily</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Susie</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ella</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Anna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Blanche</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Eury</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Helen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Margaret</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_MONDSTADT_Z_MODERN_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sara</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_MONDSTADT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mondstadt</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_STARFELL_VALLEY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Starfell Valley</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_STARSNATCH_CLIFF" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Starsnatch Cliff</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_WHISPERING_WOODS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Whispering Woods</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_MIDSUMMER_COURTYARD" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Midsummer Courtyard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_STORMBEARER_POINT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stormbearer Point</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_THOUSAND_WINDS_TEMPLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thousand Winds Temple</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_GALESONG_HILL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Galesong Hill</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_WINDRISE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Windrise</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_CAPE_OATH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cape Oath</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_DADAUPA_GORGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dadaupa Gorge</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_FALCON_COAST" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Falcon Coast</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_WINDWAIL_HIGHLAND" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Windwail Highland</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_DAWN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dawn</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_VALLEY_OF_REMEMBRANCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Valley of Remembrance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_SPRINGVALE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Springvale</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_FORSAKEN_RIFT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forsaken Rift</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_WOLVENDOM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wolvendom</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_CECILIA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cecilia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_BRIGHTCRowN_CANYON" Language="en_US">
			<Text>BrightcRown Canyon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_STORMTERROR_S_LAIR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stormterror's Lair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_EMTOMBED_CITY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Entombed City</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_SKYFROST_NAIL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Skyfrost Nail</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_CAPE_VINDAGNYR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Vindagnyr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_SNOW_COVERED_PATH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Snow-Covered Path</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_STARGLOW_CAVERN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Starglow Cavern</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_WYRMREST_VALLEY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wyrmrest Valley</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_MUSK" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Musk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_NAMELESS_ISLAND" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Nameless Island</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_DORNMAN_PORT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dornman Port</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mondstadt Empire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mondstadt's</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Just in time, traveler. I want to hear what your wishes are.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z" Language="en_US">
			<Text>But the wind direction will change[NEWLINE]From now on, with my blessings, live a more leisurely life[NEWLINE]One day, it will blow towards a brighter direction</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_ENTER_FOREIGN_LANDS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Free passage</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_ENTER_FOREIGN_LANDS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Free entry into foreign countries without open borders</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_FAVONIUS_KNIGHTS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>With the civics unlocking, the attack power will gradually increase.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_FAVONIUS_KNIGHTS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>civics (divine right ,Nationalism，ideology, Cold War)+10 combat effectiveness respectively</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_FAVONIUS_KNIIGHTS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Favonius Promotion</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Angel's Share</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PROMOTION_DEPREDATION_DESCRIPTION}{LOC_PROMOTION_ESCORT_MOBILITY_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Imminent Triumph</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PROMOTION_ELITE_GUARD_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Whispering Plain</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PROMOTION_RANGER_DESCRIPTION}+10 [ICON_Strength]combat power when fighting in the rainforest or forest.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE]Wind-Washed Mountains</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PROMOTION_ALPINE_DESCRIPTION}When fighting on hills,+5[ICON_Strength] combat power is achieved.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_5_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wayward Souls</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_5_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After being injured, there will be no combat power reduction benefit. +10 [ICON_Strength]combat power during defense.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_6_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Photon of Fluctuation</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_6_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>At the end of each turn (even after movement or attack), automatically restores health. +10[ICON_Strength] combat power during attack.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_7_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Acoustic Guitar Ver.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_MFK_7_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PROMOTION_MONK_COBRA_STRIKE_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_MONDSTADT_Z_LOCATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Teyvat</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_MONDSTADT_Z_SIZE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>unknown</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_MONDSTADT_Z_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>unknown</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_MONDSTADT_Z_CAPITAL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_CITY_NAME_Z_MONDSTADT}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_AGENDA_CITY_OF_FREEDOM_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>City Of Freedom</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_AGENDA_CITY_OF_FREEDOM_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_AGENDA_FUN_LOVING_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Venti led Mond to victory through culture and faith</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Venti's Mond is a civilization focused on culture and faith, utilizing the high charm of land and tavern bonuses to bring faith, recruiting more affordable and earlier cultural dissemination units, bards, and building on the tourism performance brought by masterpieces, making it easier to gain cultural benefits</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wendy was a Elemental in the wind of Monde. In Old Mond, Wendy met a young man. The youth led the people to resist the tyrant who ruled them, Diego Carapian. Finally, the tyrant fell and the young man died in battle. Wendy gained strength and became the new god, the demon god Batos. Andrus, the demon god who has been competing with Diekalapian, also chose to leave because of his own characteristics. The War of the Demon Gods ended, and the Demon God Batos became one of the Seven Rulers of the Earth, the Wind God. Wendy, in order to commemorate her friend, the first thing she did after obtaining divine power was to reshape her body in the form of a young man. She played her friend's favorite harp and walked the world in this young man's form from then on.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Afterwards, Babatos Wendy imparted his wisdom to the Mond people, modified the terrain of the present-day Mond region, migrated and settled from the old Mond (now the ruins of the Wind Dragon), and established many festivals and celebrations. Subsequently, Wendy left Mond due to her unwillingness to become a new tyrant, making Mond an autonomous and free state. After the end of the Demon God War, Fengshen went to the neighboring country of Liyue to invite Yan Shenpin to taste Taraxacum wine. Afterwards, the initial seven gods met multiple times in Liyue.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>About 1600 years after the completion of the new Monde, nobles led by the Lawrence family took control of Monde, and Wendy woke up again in response to the prayers of his followers. As a minstrel walking in the city of Mond, I found that the atmosphere in the city was unusually oppressive. On the day of the Badminton Festival, I played a song called "Song of the Wind" to an apple vendor that had not been played for a long time. Later, the vendor warned me not to touch that badminton. During the celebration, I heard about the absurd and cruel behavior of the nobles. I went forward and took away the badminton and played with the nobles, but was chased by soldiers. During my escape, I encountered Winnissa and received her cover. Vanessa was arrested for angering the nobles. Wendy got the key to the cell that night and entered the cell to talk to Winnissa. Wendy wants to escape from Mond with Vanessa and her people. However, Vanessa stated that her people had forgotten the meaning of "freedom" and had to participate in the duel the next day to awaken their resistance and freedom consciousness, otherwise they would only be shackled by another force.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The next day, the nobles shamelessly drove all the Vanessa clan out of the city, demanding that they defeat the demon dragon Usa and shoot arRows at the retreating people. At this moment, Wendy suddenly appeared, guiding the force of the wind to make Vanessa strike the demon dragon and use divine power to force the demon dragon to retreat. At this point, Wendy requested to write Winnissa into a poem and received approval, stating that this would be a new chapter with the Winnissa clan as the main character. Finally, Lawrence was required to comply with the rules and hand over control of Mond. In addition, he forged the signature of Morax to create the Secret Covenant of Leeward, which made a large number of soldiers rebel and overturned the aristocratic rule together with Winnissa. The relatives of the wind god Babatos form the Four Winds Guardian. The Wind God has left again.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>500 years ago, gods including the Wind God descended together and destroyed Canria. The Kariya disaster spread throughout Tiwat. The evil dragon Durin and the dark wave of demons attacked Mond, and the West Wind Order of chivalry fought hard. The Wind God and his family, Tevalin, together attacked Durin and ultimately beheaded him on the snowy mountain. The Wind God and the Wind Dragon corroded by the Poison Blood of the Demon Dragon each fell into a deep sleep.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mond, located in the northeastern part of the Tihuate continent, is known as the "City State of Wind and Pastoral Songs". Believing in the wind god Babatos, it is one of the seven earthly kingdoms of the Tihuate continent and also the starting point for travelers in the game to search for lost family members. Between the mountains and the vast plains, the wind of freedom carries the smell of Taraxacum across the Fruit Wine Lake, sending Babatos' blessing and grace to Monde City, which is located on the island in the middle of the lake.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>At least 3000 years ago, the demon god of the fierce wind, Dekkara Pi'an, established civilization in the ruins of the present-day Wind Dragon and is now known as the "Old Mond". At that time, the land of Monde was covered in vast ice and snow, and humans had to seek the shelter of the demon gods. Diekalapian established a royal capital around the ruins of the Wind Dragon and surrounded it with towering wind walls to prevent external threats such as blizzards.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>2600 years ago, another demon god in the Mond region, Andrus, declared war on Decalopian, but failed to break through the wind wall of Old Mond, and it seemed that Decalopian did not attack from Old Mond, leading to a stalemate in the war. At this time in Old Monde, Diego Carapian implemented a tyrannical rule of slavery. Diego Carapian had a rebellious personality, was solitary in his actions, and turned a deaf ear to the cries of the people under his rule for freedom. He regarded people's submission as respect and love, which sparked strong dissatisfaction among the people. Starting with a red haired knight, codenamed "Wind Flower", some Monds were secretly preparing to resist. They used songs and hymns to communicate signals and were suppressed by the old Mond rulers. Some other Mondes were disappointed with the status quo of Diecalapian. Under the leadership of a Diecalapian subordinate, they decided to leave the old Mondes, but in the harsh environment outside the wind wall, they could only struggle to survive. Later, the daughter of the leader, Gurnhild, received the protection of the wind elves and developed a belief in the wind. At a certain point in time, an unknown bard met a wind elf named Wendy, who was only one of the countless wind elves in the north of Mond at that time and had no vast divine power.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Under Wendy's guidance, Amos, an unknown minstrel, a refugee led by Gunnhilde, a Laurence family led by Van Nirary, a red haired knight, and a lover of Diecalapian, launched an uprising with the Old Mondes, overthRowing the authoritarian rule of Diecalapian, and Diecalapian also died on the tower. Wendy inherited the power of Diego Carapian and, with the support of Guernhild, became a new demon god named the wind god "Babatos". Babatos used his divine power to reshape himself according to the appearance of the bard, using the divine wind to disperse the snowstorm that covered the land of Mond. He then reshaped the terrain of Mond, allowing warm and humid sea winds to blow into it. He also guided the ancestors to establish the new city of Mond on Fruit Wine Lake. After the refugees, the Gurnhild family formed, and the Lawrence family opened up the city of New Monde. The unknown minstrel and Amos sacrificed themselves in the uprising, and the red haired knight left after the success of the uprising, with their whereabouts unknown.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Andreus discovered that the fierce north wind could only bring disaster, could not nourish life, and could not lead people to create a happy life. He was not qualified to become the future ruler of the world. He decided to let his power flow into this land and protect Mond in the form of his soul. With the death of Andrus and Babatos becoming one of the Seven Rulers of the Earth, as well as the establishment of the New Mond aristocracy system, the Demon God Wars in the Mond region came to an end. Babatos did not want to become a tyrant like Diego Carapian and decided to make Mond a "land of freedom". He taught the Monds some production skills and the ability to fly with the Wind Wings, and handed over power to the Mond people before leaving.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After the departure of Babatos, some prominent groups or heroes in the uprising gained recognition from the Mond people, and their descendants began to merge into several clans, rising to become the new aristocratic class of Mond. At the beginning of the establishment of the city of Mond, the mother-in-law of the Lawrence tribe, Vanilla Rui, led the people to build a huge statue in the square to commemorate the Wind God. Under the statue, he left behind the oath of eternal protection for Mond, led by the leaders of various tribes in the past. The Badminton Festival was also formed at this time as an event to commemorate the blessings of the Wind God.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Under the mild climate created by Babatos and the exploration of the Mond people, Mond agriculture developed rapidly. The new aristocracy, as a role model in the hearts of the Monde people, is greatly respected and loved. While enjoying the extremely high courtesies of people, they also bear in mind their obligations and strict self-discipline. This harmony between the nobility and the common people has shaped the cultural sprouts of Monde. For example, nobles and lords hunt together, and when they return with their prey, the nobles share the fruits with all the lords. This is a major festival in the territory, and the nobles also demonstrate their strength and generosity through it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>But with the passage of time, the life of the new aristocracy became increasingly extravagant and corrupt, and the self-discipline of the aristocracy based on moral responsibility gradually forgot and regarded themselves as the king who was initially superior to the common people. The co governance led by the aristocracy was alienated into aristocratic dictatorship. Within the aristocracy, the Lawrence family became the largest family and the true rulers of the Monde. Most of the other nobles remained loyal to the Lawrence family while brutally suppressing civilians. The nobles led by Lawrence used various means to restrict the freedom of the common people, and the church and court mages also colluded with the nobles, monopolizing cultural knowledge to prevent the common people from understanding Mond's past. The interpretation of the faith in the wind god and freedom was also alienated into strict abstinence, purification, and maintenance of hierarchy. The statues in the square were replaced by tall towers, becoming a symbol of the nobles' declaration of their power under the dictatorship of the nobles. Civilians can only engage in limited entertainment during festivals, and Monde's literary masterpiece "Monde Tower" reflects the fact that the church was an accomplice of aristocratic extortion at that time. The corruption of the church also made some saints feel disappointed with the clergy and went underground to promote the original doctrines to the common people. The underground preaching to some extent maintained the continuity of the free faith of the Westwind Church. According to the "Biography of the Ghuinhild", during this period, the Ghuinhild family still did not forget their initial vows, attempting to maintain a balance between the nobility and the common people, and maximizing the protection of the interests of the common people. The Emonoka family has not been mentioned in existing historical records and is unknown.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>At least 1010 years ago, a Munata tribe roamed the land, running out of food for several days and being attacked by the demon dragon Usa and forced to flee to the city of Mond to seek refuge. Usa invaded the city of Mond, but by this time swordsmanship had become a form of powerless resistance for the Mond nobles. They chose to secretly compromise with Usa, and the nobles sold the Munata people to pay tribute to him. Usa promised to ensure the safety of Mond. Vanessa was born into this already enslaved tribe. As a child, Vanessa participated in gladiatorial competitions for the enjoyment of the nobility and achieved remarkable results in the arena.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Vanessa's era had reached the end of the decadent and authoritarian aristocracy of the aristocracy. Under the influence of underground organizations, more and more civilians realized their own situation, and the voices of resistance against aristocratic rule began to rise. At the Badminton Festival when Vanessa was ten years old, Babatos was awakened by the prayers of the oppressed Mond people. He came to Mond in the name of Wendy and was shocked by the current situation in Mond. At the Badminton Festival, Wendy ignored the aristocratic decision and grabbed the badminton in front of the young master of the Lawrence family. He was wanted by the aristocrats and met Vanessa while running away. Vanessa was arrested and imprisoned by the Lawrence family for covering up for Wendy. Wendy sneaked into the prison at night and expressed her hope to help Vanessa and her tribe regain their freedom. However, Vanessa refused, but she agreed to make friends with Wendy. The next day, the then supreme ruler of Mond, Buck Lawrence, demanded that Vanessa and her tribe defeat the dragon Usa in the arena in exchange for the freedom of the entire tribe, and promised Vanessa the status of Lord of Mond if they truly defeated the dragon. Buck believed that Vanessa could not defeat the Magic Dragon and only regarded this competition as a noble entertainment event at the Badminton Festival. This unreasonable demand caused resentment among nearby civilians, but Lawrence naturally turned a blind eye. At this moment, Babatos descended in the form of a god, giving Winnissa the power to defeat the demon dragon and successfully drove away the demon dragon Usa, greatly shocking the nobles such as Lawrence.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Vanessa took the opportunity to set off a rebellion against the aristocratic dictatorship led by the Lawrence family, and quickly gained the support of the common people. Various underground rebel figures and organizations, including Legenfeld, Klutzlyde Lawrence, and the Gunnhild family, responded one after another, and the Second Revolution of Mond broke out. In the revolution, Babatos forged the "leeward secret agreement" in the name of a high-level noble. In the secret agreement, the noble betrayed Fengshen and sold everything of Monde to Morax. The content of the secret agreement made all the Mondes feel betrayed, greatly damaging the reputation of the nobles, and many soldiers under the nobles defected and surrendered. After a long struggle, the rebel army led by Vanessa achieved revolutionary victory. The Monde aristocracy and the forces that committed crimes against them were ultimately expelled from the Monde region. The original palace mage was also expelled for failing to fulfill his duty of guiding the Monde nobles towards goodness, but his legacy of knowledge is still used by people today.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After the victory of the revolution, Vanessa carried out multiple reforms on Mond. First of all, the superior social status of the nobility was abolished to prevent similar tyrants from reappearing. Second, the Westwind Order of chivalry was established and served as the first head, called the "Lion Tooth Knight". The old church was reorganized into the Westwind Church and attached to the Order of chivalry, and the free belief of Monde was established again. The tall tower on the square was also demolished and rebuilt as a statue of the Wind God. To commemorate this revolution, the Monds have formed the tradition of calling the "wolf" of the Beifeng Knights, the "lion" of the Taraxacum (lion's tooth) Knights, the "eagle" of the Xifeng Order of chivalry, and the "wind dragon" of Tevalin the "four wind guardian".</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Five hundred years ago, there was a disaster in Canrea. A large number of demons created by Alchemy researcher Reindote eroded the entire Tivat, which was called "the dark tide of beasts". This disaster changed the fate of many people. Among them, the evil dragon Durin invaded Mond, and Alan Durin and Rustan, as the then head of the Westwind Order of chivalry, led the Peloton to fight against the tide of animals. Later, Rustan died on the way to fight against the disaster, which made Allan Delin extremely sad, and then Allan Delin announced to withdraw from the Order of chivalry. The leaderless Order of chivalry fell into a hard battle and suffered huge losses. It was difficult to resist the attack of the evil dragon Durin and the corrupt Warcraft. The prayers of the Mond people finally awakened the will of the Wind God, and Babatos summoned Twalin. Twalin engaged in a battle with Durin, biting off the throat of the venomous dragon and beheading it on the Dragon Ridge Snow Mountain, but Twalin also swallowed Durin's venomous blood.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_14" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After the end of the disaster in Canria, Mond returned to the long period of peace before the disaster. With the development of peace and Mond City, people's beliefs also changed, and the belief in the protection of the Four Winds gradually lost, and the corresponding temples were also abandoned.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_MONDSTADT_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_15" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although Monde has encountered many events in recent years and was once in a difficult situation, in the second five hundred years when the West Wind Order of chivalry ruled Monde, the region under the rule of Aeolus never succumbed to tyranny, still sang the song of freedom, welcomed all respectable travelers from afar, and faced cultural integration and change with an inclusive attitude. May the wind of Monde's freedom blow for a long time.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_FAVONIUS_KNIGHTS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Order of chivalry governing the city of Mond was established by Winnissa, who overthrew the old aristocratic rule a thousand years ago, to manage the big and small affairs of Mond. Mond's "Westwind Eagle" is responsible for maintaining order in Mond City while also safeguarding the creed of Mond City's "freedom". Although referred to as a knight, it is not by anyone - the Westwind Knight carries noble responsibilities and can therefore be proud of its title.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_GLEEMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A poet and singer in Monde who excels in creating and reciting poems about heroes and their achievements, as well as other stories and emotions. Frequently haunted in squares and taverns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_MONDSTADT_TAVERN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Taraxacum wine produced by Monde is famous in the world, and it is also the largest export industry of Monde. Wine plays an indispensable part in the life of Monde people, but people's love of wine also brings a lot of trouble to public security.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Traveling with you is really fun.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you also need to show some sincerity. For example, piety, love, or</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I want to include you in the new song! Hey, how could you show such an expression? Are you worried about not being able to pay the manuscript fee? Haha, Mora won't do it, why don't you... tell me your story again!.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Come and sit this way. I have written a new poem, let's call it "Traveler's Wind".</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Um... oh... really can't do it?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Come and play together.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pay attention to your feet.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Help me get a glass of wine. I will definitely be grateful to you, it's a deal.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If you come here like this, you should be beaten away, right?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Would you like some music to relax? Caprice or Serenade?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How rude.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your land does not have sweet water, nor can it gRow any delicious fruits. Won't there be any good wine? Hehe, so I don't even want to go if you invite me. (Denounce you)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ha... You slept soundly. Hello, we have met again. Hmm? Don't remember me? Hehe, then let me join your journey again.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I like wine! There's still wind! Well, it would be great if we could use wind brewed wine here.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your poetry deserves to be sung by the best minstrel in the world!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey, are you going out? Take me one.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Just in time, traveler. I want to hear, what is your wish?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My wish? Mmm. Previously, I wanted to travel the entire world. Now it's the same, but with a proviso added, it's with you. With you, it is complete. The narrator really needs to be with the adventurer, hehe!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wait, this is not fun!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, the string is broken</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I have gained a lot, you can exchange it for a few bottles of good wine.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>you've gone too far</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, hey~</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't try to escape?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh, don't stare at me and fight.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Have you ever seen Cecilia flowers? That is a white wild flower that blooms silently on the top of a quiet cliff. In my heart, it is the most beautiful flower in all Tiwat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Um... if you want to go over, give me an apple.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I want to travel the whole world, want to be together.</Text>
		</Row>
	
</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
