<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- POFAH_Text_en -->
<!-- Author: zdaoting -->
<!-- DateCreated: 7/17/2023 9:15:34 PM -->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Row Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LAND_OF_WIND_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Land of the Wind</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LAND_OF_WIND_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_AGENDA_DESTINATION_CIV_DESCRIPTION}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_DEACONESS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_DEACONESS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Provide additional recovery for units within 1 nearby tile. Units adjacent to the Deaconess increase their religious combat power.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_SPINEA_CORONA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MONDSTADT_UNIT_SPINEA_CORONA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If the Spine Corona Sister dies in a theological battle, a relic will be generated. Religious combat strength is relatively low, but it doubles when conducting theological battles within the country's borders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_DEACONESS_STRENGTH_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ABILITY_DEACONESS_STRENGTH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Units adjacent to the Deaconess +15 religious combat power.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z" Language="en_US">
			<Text>He is both a prayer pastor of the Westwind Church and a shining idol of the city of Mond. For Mond, who is accustomed to traditional minstrels, 'idols' are a new thing that he is not yet accustomed to. But in Mond, everyone loves Barbara. This is the spirit of freedom in the capital of freedom - the love that comes from everyone, as Barbara concludes with gratitude.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rosalia - a nun under the West Wind Church in Mond City. A strange nun who doesn't look like a clergyman anywhere except in her attire. A woman who is cold and sharp, as sharp as a knife. His whereabouts are unpredictable and he often leaves without saying goodbye. Carrying a certain mission, but people don't seem to understand what she really represents</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_VENTI_Z_QUOTE}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The most magical magic is practical effort.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A choir? Sorry, no church activities are allowed, and don't come to me for overtime</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_SPINEA_CORONA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rosalia, who is a maverick, is simply a nominal member of the church. But please don't forget: if there is black, there will be corresponding white; Wherever light goes, there must be shadows</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DEACONESS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Barbara is a pastor of the Westwind Knights. She uses water elements to heal wounds and sings to soothe people's tired hearts. In the hearts of the Mond people, Barbara possesses magical magic that can heal both the body and mind of patients - and in Barbara's heart, this magic is called 'practical effort'.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As a god, Babatos has the ability to utilize mountains and blow away ice and snow.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As a god led by Babatos, Mond is a civilization focused on culture and faith. He uses taverns and broadcasting centers to create high charm plots, and recruits more naturalists from the beliefs brought by the addition of taverns. He uses mountains and high charm plots to build national parks and achieve high tourism performance, making it easier to achieve cultural victory.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Barbara is a devout pastor of the Westwind Church who is more likely to achieve religious victory</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As a prayer pastor, Barbara has a unique unit, the prayer pastor, which utilizes the cultural characteristics and high faith generated in the characteristic building tavern to recruit more prayer pastors and provide high religious combat power bonuses for religious battles. When you can recruit rock bands, use the power of religious rock to win religious victories in one go</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rosalia leverages the advantages of religion and belief while also utilizing relics to accumulate tourism performance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rosalia, walking in the darkness, guards the young and ancient city. The characteristic unit, Spine Crown Sister, can eliminate religious forces that are not part of Mond and maintain an absolute advantage in religious battles within the country. The relics left by Spine Crown Sister's death, combined with additional relic slots, make it easier to obtain tourism performance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Venti was a Elemental in the wind of Mond. In Old Mond, Venti met a young man. The youth led the people to resist the tyrant who ruled them, Diego Carapian. Finally, the tyrant fell and the young man died in battle. Venti gained strength and became the new god, the demon god Batos. Andrus, the demon god who has been competing with Diekalapian, also chose to leave because of his own characteristics. The War of the Demon Gods ended, and the Demon God Batos became one of the Seven Rulers of the Earth, the Wind God. Venti, in order to commemorate her friend, the first thing she did after obtaining divine power was to reshape her body in the form of a young man. She played her friend's favorite harp and walked the world in this young man's form from then on.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Afterwards, Babatos Venti imparted his wisdom to the Mond people, modified the terrain of the present-day Mond region, migrated from the old Mond (now the ruins of the Wind Dragon) to settle, and established many festivals and celebrations. Subsequently, Venti left Mond due to her unwillingness to become a new tyrant, making Mond an autonomous and free state. After the end of the Demon God War, Fengshen went to the neighboring country of Liyue to invite Yan Shenpin to taste Taraxacum wine. Afterwards, the initial seven gods met multiple times in Liyue.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>About 1600 years after the completion of the new Mond, nobles led by the Lawrence family took control of Mond, and Venti woke up again in response to the prayers of his followers. As a minstrel walking in the city of Mond, I found that the atmosphere in the city was unusually oppressive. On the day of the Badminton Festival, I played a song called "Song of the Wind" to an apple vendor that had not been played for a long time. Later, the vendor warned me not to touch that badminton. During the celebration, I heard about the absurd and cruel behavior of the nobles. I went forward and took away the badminton and played with the nobles, but was chased by soldiers. During my escape, I encountered Winnissa and received her cover. Vanessa was arrested for angering the nobles. Venti got the key to the cell that night and entered the cell to talk to Winnissa. Venti wants to escape from Mond with Vanessa and her people. However, Vanessa stated that her people had forgotten the meaning of "freedom" and had to participate in the duel the next day to awaken their resistance and freedom consciousness, otherwise they would only be shackled by another force.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The next day, the nobles shamelessly drove all the Vanessa clan out of the city, demanding that they defeat the demon dragon Usa and shoot arrows at the retreating people. At this moment, Venti suddenly appeared, guiding the force of the wind to make Vanessa strike the demon dragon and use divine power to force the demon dragon to retreat. At this point, Venti requested to write Winnissa into a poem and received approval, stating that this would be a new chapter with the Winnissa clan as the main character. Finally, Lawrence was required to comply with the rules and hand over control of Mond. In addition, he forged the signature of Morax to create the Secret Covenant of Leeward, which made a large number of soldiers rebel and overturned the aristocratic rule together with Winnissa. The relatives of the wind god Babatos form the Four Winds Guardian. The Wind God has left again.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>500 years ago, gods including the Wind God descended together and destroyed Canria. The Kariya disaster spread throughout Tiwat. Demon Dragon Durin and the pitch black wave of monsters attacked Mond, and the Westwind Knights fought hard. The Wind God and his family, Tevalin, together attacked Durin and ultimately beheaded him on the snowy mountain. The Wind God and the Wind Dragon corroded by the Poison Blood of the Demon Dragon each fell into a deep sleep.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Father Simon Page is the bishop of the Westwind Church, known as the "Cardinal of Dawn", mother Frederica comes from the Gunhill family, and sister Jean is a proud member of the family. Barbara cannot surpass her solely through hard work. The parents' marriage split and parted ways, with Barbara following her father and Jean following her mother. Under the stimulation of her small competitiveness, Barbara once tried to catch up with her sister in swordsmanship, but after realizing that she was not good at combat, Barbara chose to be responsible for logistics. Under the guidance of my father, I became a healer.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Influenced by Alice, Barbara has now become an idol of Mond City. At present, my father and the leader of the North Wind Knight Falga are on a long journey together.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Born in a mountain village, he was taken away by a bandit group in Tu Village and trained as a thief or servant. The old thief who caught her during a flight discovered that he demanded Rosalia to duel with him in exchange for the opportunity to leave. Rosalia achieved victory and was granted the Eye of God, and was accepted into the Thief Squad. A few years later, the bandit group was exterminated by the Westwind Knights. Rosalia, due to her youth, was deemed to have room for repentance. She was brought back to Mond by the leader of the group, Falga, and enrolled in the Westwind Church as a trainee nun for study. However, she repeatedly skipped classes and skipped classes. Afterwards, he secretly handled the danger for Mond, but still remained affiliated with the Westwind Church, always causing Sister Victoria and Barbara to be heartbroken.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't force yourself, you can call me if you have any difficulties.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, a clear disguise at a glance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If one day you encounter an unsolvable problem. Maybe I'll help you solve the problem.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't force yourself, you can call me if you have any difficulties.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Who knows? Everything always has two sides.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pray. Not for God or anyone else, but for yourself.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Trembling!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Would you like a drink? This is this year's Taraxacum wine. It tastes very good.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shh, please.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I think in many aspects, we have similar tastes.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>However, that's the case.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A glib and deceitful person. You're threatening Mond. (denounce you)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Complete your work well and spend every day well. Isn't Mond's life like this?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This believer, if you encounter difficulties that are difficult to solve, you can come to me.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Skip the small talk. I came here to complete the work.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Can I help you? I am available now.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I hope the cooperation goes smoothly.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Is there anyone or thing you want to handle? I can do a small favor, just don't tell anyone else.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tsk, that's really troublesome!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Perhaps... destined by fate</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There are also good things.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is not within the scope of my interest.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>That Will Be Fine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>God may protect everyone, but he will not do so. Otherwise, human suffering becomes a joke.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text> have real skill</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's okay, not too much trouble.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Alas, all trouble is trouble.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_ROSALIA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Could you please.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My wish is to bring a smile to everyone around me! As long as I can help you, I will be very happy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sorry, can we still</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If only I could help everyone.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I will pray for you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, it's okay.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>No, not good</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Barbara, go ahead!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Today is a lucky day!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you, but I'm sorry.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Please take it! Wait for the next new song, I will sing it to you as soon as possible!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Why is this happening.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hate... (denounce you)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Barbara, shining on stage~</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Leave the treatment to me, I won't disappoint you!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If you also become an idol, I will definitely give my full support.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I will strive to deserve your trust</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Why do you like spicy fish? I have two more... here, here's one for you!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for accompanying me until now. My dream is getting closer and closer. In the future, please take care of me too~</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I don't really like it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Everyone's voices, I can't hear them</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hmm, what a lucky day~</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey? Ask me? Um Anyway, that's it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Everyone has their own wishes.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The wind that guides me forward. Give me the strength to move forward when I am struggling, the wisdom to discern good and evil when I am confused, and the courage to resist when I suffer injustice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hoo... Hoo... no problem!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't worry, just leave it to me.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sorry, it's not yet time for the performance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBARA_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for your support~</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_SPINEA_CORONA_FRIENDLY_TERRITORY_COMBAT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Spine Crown Sister gains an additional [ICON_Strength]combat power bonus while in her own territory.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DEACONESS_STRENGTH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gain+15[ICON_Religion] religious combat power when adjacent to the Deaconess.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Traveling with you is really fun.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you also need to show some sincerity. For example, piety, love, or</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I want to include you in the new song! Hey, how could you show such an expression? Are you worried about not being able to pay the manuscript fee? Haha, Mora won't do it, why don't you... tell me your story again!.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Come and sit this way. I have written a new poem, let's call it "Traveler's Wind".</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Um... oh... really can't do it?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Come and play together.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pay attention to your feet.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Help me get a glass of wine. I will definitely be grateful to you, it's a deal.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If you come here like this, you should be beaten away, right?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Would you like some music to relax? Caprice or Serenade?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How rude.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your land does not have sweet water, nor can it gRow any delicious fruits. Won't there be any good wine? Hehe, so I don't even want to go if you invite me. (Denounce you)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ha... You slept soundly. Hello, we have met again. Hmm? Don't remember me? Hehe, then let me join your journey again.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I like wine! There's still wind! Well, it would be great if we could use wind brewed wine here.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your poetry deserves to be sung by the best minstrel in the world!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey, are you going out? Take me one.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Just in time, traveler. I want to hear, what is your wish?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My wish? Mmm. Previously, I wanted to travel the entire world. Now it's the same, but with a proviso added, it's with you. With you, it is complete. The narrator really needs to be with the adventurer, hehe!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wait, this is not fun!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, the string is broken</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I have gained a lot, you can exchange it for a few bottles of good wine.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>you've gone too far</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, hey~</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't try to escape?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh, don't stare at me and fight.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Have you ever seen Cecilia flowers? That is a white wild flower that blooms silently on the top of a quiet cliff. In my heart, it is the most beautiful flower in all Tiwat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Um... if you want to go over, give me an apple.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_MONDSTADT_BARBATOS_Z_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I want to travel the whole world, want to be together.</Text>
		</Row>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
