<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Tue Jun 25 22:30:07 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qu Yuan, you are a great poet and a loyal patriot. You moved heaven and earth with your words of Li Sao and moved gods and ghosts with your loyalty. Now, you will shoulder the responsibility of reviving the country, expanding the territory and writing a new legend.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qu Yuan: The Three Kingdoms</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Li Sao</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After you build or conquer a city, it enters the &quot;Fill in the blanks&quot; state: within five rounds, the city's name is changed to half a sentence of &quot;Li Sao&quot;, and the player needs to change the city's name to the corresponding other half of the &quot;Li Sao&quot; poem within the specified time (at the beginning of the round, the AI ​​player has a 15% chance of answering correctly). [NEWLINE]At the beginning of the round, if the answer is correct, the city will immediately complete the current production content, gain +20% [ICON_FOOD][ICON_Production][ICON_SCIENCE][ICON_Culture][ICON_Faith][ICON_Gold] total output, +1 [ICON_Amenities] amenity, and have a chance to gain 1 builder. [NEWLINE]If you fail to answer correctly within the specified time, the city will lose 1 [ICON_Amenities] amenity. If the city has at least two people, the city residents may rebel because you failed to answer the &quot;Fill in the blanks&quot; correctly. [NEWLINE]Note: Cities can enter the &quot;Li Sao Fill in the Blanks&quot; state repeatedly. The last correct but unanswered questions will be directly settled, and the unanswered questions will be overwritten. [NEWLINE]You own the featured project &quot;{LOC_PROJECT_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN_HYLS_NAME}&quot;[NEWLINE]Every 10 turns, a random city of yours will enter the &quot;Li Sao Fill in the Blanks&quot; state.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN_HYLS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Carrying forward Li Sao</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN_HYLS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_LEADER_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN_NAME} leader's unique project. Once completed, a random city of each major civilization will enter the &quot;Li Sao Filling in the Blanks&quot; state.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_YING" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ying</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN_TSLH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chain</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Quest</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_SANGUOSHA_QU_YUAN2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You can find a chain of iron chains each round. The first attack on an enemy unit in each round will automatically trigger the &quot;chain chain&quot; effect, and all enemy units connected to the target will be damaged by this attack. At the end of the round, if you did not trigger the &quot;chain chain&quot; effect in this round, the chain will be automatically recast, and you will get [ICON_Gold] coins equivalent to one third of your current [ICON_Science][ICON_Culture] value.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
