<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun May  7 16:55:38 2023-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;You are exactly this kind of person: you will be attracted at first, but the longer you get along, the more you want to stay away.&quot; [NEWLINE] &quot;Thirteen Heroes Chasing Fire&quot; from the anti-Honkai organization of the former civilization has almost infinite Lifespan and unlimited self-recovery ability, spanning countless years, silently fulfilling their duties, in the name of Chiyuan, guarding China, and giving fire to civilization.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Floating life is nothing but success after failure.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't be afraid, I'm with you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Founded by Qin Suyi, the seventh disciple of Taixu's seven apprentices, and her husband &quot;Mr. Chuan&quot;, it is not considered a top sect, but the Twelve Routes of Recalling Heart Sword Art, which is inherited from Taixu's sword qi, is also unique. The identities of Qin Suyi's Seven Disciples of Taixu were made public, and there was an endless stream of people coming and going, but no one saw Qin Suyi make a move again. It is said that his martial arts skills have reached the peak.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_WUSHUANGMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Created by Su Mei, the second disciple of Taixu Seven Disciples, under the management of this &quot;Wushuang Fairy&quot;, it has become a giant in the world. There is a saying: It is better to offend the living king than to provoke Wushuang Lang/Mother. Of course, the real danger is the woman who lives behind the scenes of Wushuangmen: Sumei, who is extremely beautiful and full of wisdom.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_CANGXUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cang Xuan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_DANZHU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Danju</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_LINZHAOYU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lin Chaoyu is the head of the Taixu Seven Swords, holding the Xuanyuan Sword - Qingchenliu, and can easily defeat the world's second Yan Shiluo when he was young. Zhao Yu, who was brought back to Taixu by Chi Yuan in 1446, began to practice &quot;Taixu Zhenjue&quot; as a maid. In 1458, he co-founded the Taixu Sword School with Chi Yuan and his second younger sister Su Mei. In 1476, the Seven Swords of Taixu succeeded in killing his master, and Lin Chaoyu rebuilt his sect in Taixu Mountain after the fire, and quickly became one of the six schools of martial arts. Lin Zhaoyu is gentle and rarely loses his composure, and seems to only have complaints about his second apprentice, Su Mei. In 1496, because Chiyuan returned to Zhaoyu, he met with Sumei again.
(To be continued, the pigeon record has not been updated for a long time).</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_SUMEI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Su Mei is the second of the Taixu Seven Swords, and she holds the Xuanyuan Sword - Wushuang. There are rumors in the world: &quot;It is better to offend the living Hades than to provoke Wushuang Niang/Lang&quot;. Sumei is famous for her beauty and wisdom. She is good at scheming. She personally planned and led the Taixu Transformation in 1476 and successfully killed the Chiyuan Immortal. After killing the teacher, Su Mei noticed that the immortal's coffin had changed, and was alerted that the immortal was not dead, so she went to southern Xinjiang to establish Wushuangmen alone. Although the Wushuangmen under Sumei's rule is not as prestigious as the Taixu Sword Sect, it is still an important giant. In 1496, for Chiyuan's return to the mortal world, she visited Taixu Mountain alone and asked her senior sister Lin Chaoyu for the Taixu Sword School. (to be continued, reminder to update the pigeon record).</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JIANGWANXI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Wanxi is the third of the Taixu Seven Swords, holds the Xuanyuan Sword - Feng Qingyang, and is the sister of the fourth sword Jiang Wanru. In 1461, the Jiang sisters who were prepared to be saintesses by Yan Shiluo, the leader of the Demon Cult, were rescued after Lin Chaoyu defeated Yan Shiluo and joined the Taixu Sword Sect. In 1476, he chose to participate in the killing of teachers in order to rescue his sister who might have gone mad. (This is also a collection of tragedies, who would have thought that the Seven Swords of Taixu would turn into a dead man).</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JIANGWANRU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Wanru is the fourth of the Taixu Seven Swords, holds Xuanyuan Sword - Luo Wuzhuo, and is the younger sister of the third sword Jiang Wanxi. In 1461, the Jiang sisters who were prepared to be saintesses by Yan Shiluo, the leader of the Demon Cult, were rescued after Lin Chaoyu defeated Yan Shiluo and joined the Taixu Sword Sect. In 1476, due to the commandment that Chi Yuan must be killed if she enters the devil, Jiang Wanru was unwilling to accept her fate and participated in the murder of a teacher under Su Mei's leadership. (Speaking of why the two sisters are so good, they are obviously the fuse, but they don't have much role in the show)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_CHENGLINSHUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cheng Lingshuang is the fifth of the Taixu Seven Swords. The Xuanyuan Sword he held was lost after killing his master, and he is known as the &quot;Zizai Sword&quot;. Cheng Lingshuang joined the Taixu Sword Sect at the age of two, comprehended the fourth level of Jianxin at the age of 13, and realized the Shen Yun after sixteen months, but Ling Shuang failed to comprehend the third level of Taixu - Sword Intent. Cheng Lingshuang is extremely talented. For five thousand years, only Chiyuan, who is a fairy, has mastered the Taixu God. Now Cheng Lingshuang has cultivated the supreme and free sword god with a mortal body. Jianghu said, &quot;He is a natural man, a sword that is unparalleled in the world.&quot; In 1476, Cheng Lingshuang, the sword god, was the only successful sword in the hands of the seven disciples, and the battle of killing masters also came to an end after Cheng Lingshuang's sword god destroyed the brains of the immortals. After killing his master, the seven disciples separated. Cheng Lingshuang was born with a sword, walked the world, went through 17 competitions, and won every time with a sword. After that, Ling Shuang entered the bamboo forest in southern Hunan, and has been practicing in seclusion since then. In 1486, under the entrustment of Qin Suyi, the seventh junior sister, Ling Shuang accepted his daughter Li Sushang as his apprentice and established their small sect - Supreme Zizaimen. Because Cheng Lingshuang has cultivated to be a sword god, and her nature is pure, her personality is indifferent, her emotions are restrained, and her worldly reputation, common sense, human feelings... In her opinion, she doesn't care about it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_MAFEIMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ma Feima is the sixth of the Taixu Seven Swords, and holds the Xuanyuan Sword-Chi Jueying. His real name is Ma Yanqing, and he is known as &quot;Zhuju Sword&quot;. Ma Feima joined the Taixu Sword Sect at the age of six, and was taken care of by Lin Chaoyu and Su Mei when he was young, so Ma Feima has a very good relationship with them. After killing his teacher in 1476, Ma Feima went south with Su Mei, and then returned alone to Lin Chaoyu's rebuilt Taixu Sword Sect and helped him rebuild. In 1478, Ma Yanqing married Lin Chaoyu, but on the wedding day, she abandoned her real name and changed her name to &quot;Ma Feima&quot;, claiming to be ashamed of her old name. Since then, Ma Feima has become more mad and uninhibited. He once went deep into the northern wilderness alone, galloping with a group of horses with his feet, and spread the reputation of &quot;chasing a horse from a hundred miles&quot;. Everyone in the world knows that the deputy head of Ma on Taixu Mountain is polite and gentle. But when he went down the mountain, he could do whatever he wanted, recklessly and frivolously, and he was invincible all over the Central Plains. Ma Feima himself also created Taixu Zhenjue and Wushuang Nine Revolutions, both of which are first-class martial arts in the world. Taixu Zhenjue is also considered to be the true swordsmanship of immortals. For Ma Feima, he doesn't talk about how to behave, but only talks about martial arts attainments. He is really a master of a generation.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_QINSUYI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qin Suyi is the last of Taixu's Seven Swords, holding the Xuanyuan Sword - Mo Ranxiang, also known as &quot;Ranxiang Sword&quot;. Qin Suyi was born in Donghai, originally an orphan girl, but was accepted by Chi Yuan as the last disciple in 1467. Due to the loss of past memories, Qin Suyi is extremely insecure and inseparable from her seniors. In 1476, for unknown reasons, he participated in the killing of teachers. After 1476, Qin Suyi lived in seclusion. Three years later, Qin Suyi, who returned to the arena, was rescued by &quot;Mr. Sichuan&quot; Li Shen when he was besieged. After Li Shen learned that Qin Suyi was one of the Seven Swords of Taixu, he used love as a sword, successfully married Qin Suyi, and cultivated the sword spirit of Taixu. Unfortunately, his talent was limited and he was unable to cultivate the sword heart. In 1481, the two had a daughter, who was only two catties at birth, and grew up healthily under the careful care of Qin Suyi and his maid. Qin Suyi combined Taixu Sword Qi with Li Shen's Chuiyan Thirteen Swords to create &quot;Recalling the Heart Sword Art&quot;. But when the daughter who pinned her expectations could not meet her own requirements anyway, Qin Suyi and her daughter went to the desert to ask Cheng Lingshuang to teach Li Sushang, and at the same time gave her his Xuanyuan Sword to express his expectations. In 1496, Chiyuan came back to the world, Yijian Villa was destroyed by fire, and Qin Suyi disappeared.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chiyuan is not only synonymous with immortals on the land of China, but also immortal and beautiful. The common people regard her as the guardian of China; and among the rivers and lakes, she is recognized as the number one martial artist for thousands of years. The age of the Immortal can no longer be tested. It is only known from some lost ancient books and some folk myths that the Immortal seems to have walked on the land of Shenzhou as early as the Xuanyuan Year. Immortal Chiyuan does what she wants and does not follow common sense. She often travels around the world, slaying demons and demons. Sometimes she turns a blind eye to the turmoil in China, but sometimes she actively participates in it. Except for the seven disciples who are close relatives, no one understands the rules and boundaries of how Chiyuan sees things. Immortals have a dull temperament, occasionally accompanied by people, but spend more time alone. In 1458 A.D., Chi Yuan suddenly established a sect in Taixu Mountain, and recruited Lin Chaoyu, an orphan girl who had been with her for many years, as her first disciple, and Su Mei as her second disciple. By 1467, there were seven apprentices under Xianrenzuo, and people in the world called &quot;Seven Swords of Taixu&quot;. In 1475, the Immortal alone repelled the Heavenly Mandate army carrying the Key of Revelation and the Key of Restraint, and blocked the Valkyrie troops that were sweeping across Europe and Asia from the Ming Empire. The next year, after the Taixu Incident, Mount Taixu was turned into scorched earth, and Seven Swords kept silent about the whereabouts of the immortal. Everyone in the world said that the immortal had completed his merits and virtues and returned to the immortal class. In fact, the Seven Disciples teamed up to design a sneak attack on the immortal and destroy the immortal's body. But immortals are immortal, during those twenty years of death, this immortal body was repairing itself all the time. In 1496, the fairy who had been away from the world for twenty years woke up in the body that had broken out of the cocoon and become a butterfly. (It is completely the description of the immortals in China, some of which have been covered up by history, so just write the historical records)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_LISUSHANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Li Sushang is the young owner of &quot;Yijian Villa&quot; in central Sichuan, and the only daughter of Qin Suyi, the seventh disciple of &quot;Ranxiangjian&quot; under the Chiyuan real person. Sushang was only two catties and three ounces when he was born, and the weight of the same sword was almost the same. Under the careful care of Qin Suyi and his maid, he got rid of the risk of early death. The &quot;Little Banxian&quot; in the rivers and lakes said at Sushang's 100-day banquet that he was &quot;born with a sword, and he will climb to the top of the martial arts in the future.&quot; Since then, Qin Suyi has high expectations for his daughter. At the age of five, Sushang accompanied her mother to visit the retired &quot;Freedom Sword&quot; Cheng Lingshuang, and worshiped him as a teacher at the request of her mother, and at the same time received her mother's expectations and the ancient sword Xuanyuan. Su Shang has become an idiot after practicing martial arts, and she has a straightforward and free and easy personality. She is an innocent girl on weekdays. Since I grew up in the desert, my master is also a pure person by nature. Until the first time I tried the sword at the age of fifteen, the girl still didn't know what a lie was, but because of this, the girl always abided by the precepts of justice in her heart. When she tried the sword for the first time, the immature girl did not have the consciousness to fight, did not have the consciousness to test the sword, and did not have the consciousness to kill. Although such a girl easily defeated Eagle, the leader of the desert bandit, in martial arts, she was also defeated by all means. Fortunately, Otto, a Rakshasa who came here by chance, helped her to complete the sword test. Later, together with Otto, they face &quot;Hundred Miles Chasing Horses&quot; Ma Feima, who is also Sushang's Sixth Master Uncle.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_CANGXUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cangxuan, Danzhu and Chiyuan are close friends. In folk mythology, Cangxuan loves things of gold and iron, and created many wonderful ideas with them. It is said that Cangxuan and Danzhu specially made a puppet for the immortal, which is shaped like a girl and has no danger to the real person. They hope to use this puppet to replace the immortal who accompanied them and Danzhu. For the fairy, when she is parting from life and death, does she feel sad for the world where everything is like floating? Since the legend of the Tang Dynasty, this puppet does not seem to appear with the immortals anymore, and the three thousand years of companionship have also been exhausted.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_CANGXUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Sorry, I left this kind of thing to you alone.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_RESOURCES_PAGE_RESOURCE_CANGXUANZHISHU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cangxuan's book is Cangxuan's creation, and its essence is a kind of immortal wonder, which is beyond common sense like the Xuanyuan sword that changes according to the user's will. According to records, the immortals call it Xiaoxuan, who can be spoken to people. She looks like a naive girl. Generally, she sits on the yin and yang sphere, and the gossip appears around her body, and she is inseparable from the immortal. However, there are no records since the Tang Dynasty. It's a pity that the fairy magic can't last forever. [NEWLINE]&quot;No Chito...you never let people down. You do a lot for others and everyone sees it&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_RESOURCES_PAGE_RESOURCE_CANGXUANZHISHU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;No, Chiyuan...you will never let people down. You have done a lot for others, everyone can see it, I am disappointed in myself...want to use our expectations to override your mission, destroy The doctor's plan, trying to keep the unimportant things in your heart... I am very happy to live with you, but I regret that I can't be with you forever... A thousand years is a long time, but for me I can't say enough... My battery will fail one day, and the memory will cool down. I will fall into a deep sleep... But I will not leave you, Akite. I will wait forever, waiting for the people who can save you Appear...Even if you are willing to sacrifice yourself for the world, there must be someone who values ​​you more than this world, such people will definitely appear. Chiyuan, you will not be alone.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_DANZHU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Danzhu, Cangxuan and Chiyuan are close friends. During the reign of Xuanyuan, it was recorded that there were many clay puppets in Danzhu's house, all of which were said to be based on the Chiyuan Immortal. When the immortal asked about this, Danzhu just said, &quot;Don't look down on handicrafts!&quot; Feeling that life is short, Danzhu worked with Cangxuan to create such a magical thing as the Cangxuan Book, hoping that after a hundred years of life, This puppet can replace himself and Cangxuan to accompany the immortal. If he knows that this puppet has accompanied the immortal for thousands of years, he doesn't know what his mind is.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_DANZHU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;I want to pass on your story, and I hope everyone can like you.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_WUSHUANGMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Disciple of Wushuang Sect, who acts secretly and is good at sneak attacks</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A disciple of Yijian Villa, he is upright and has a great reputation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TAIXU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword School</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TAIXU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword School</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_TAIXU_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Floating life</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_TAIXU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Mountain</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_TAIXUJIANPAI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword School</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_TAIXUJIANPAI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The power of the Taixu Sword Sect is fascinating[NEWLINE]Holy lands and barracks get +100%[ICON_Production]productivity bonus[NEWLINE]Production of swordsman units get +100%[ICON_Production]productivity bonus[NEWLINE]Conscription costs from the city-state[ ICON_Gold] Gold - 50%</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_DISTRICT_MENPAI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Holy land of martial arts</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_DISTRICT_MENPAI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Under the circumstances that the Taixu Sword Sect can't hide from the world, its scattered disciples, even individuals, can be independent. The sect it founded can be called the Holy Land of Martial Arts[NEWLINE]Has a relatively balanced belief value and money output[NEWLINE] After creating the corresponding sect, unique disciples can be produced, and the sects are mutually exclusive</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_UNIT_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Disciple of Yijian Villa</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_UNIT_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Have lower culture cost and more diverse functionality</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_UNIT_WUSHUANGMEN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unparalleled Disciple</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_UNIT_WUSHUANGMEN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Possess stronger combat effectiveness, but there is a risk of becoming obsessed</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Front</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Front U4396</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Front I810975</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front D114514</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front Y100037797</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front B10914062</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front W10031035</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front K423</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front line</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front M20161014</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Front I1207</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front H0818</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu front O0413</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_14" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Front Y1018</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TAIXUCITY_NAME_15" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Front O0209</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cang Xuan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Danju</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cangxuan Book</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ji Xuanyuan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_JIANSHU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>fencing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_JIANSHU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Influenced by the Taixu Sword Sect, all the people under its protection practice swords, respect the sword, and gain something over the years.[NEWLINE]Swordsmen get an extra +5[ICON_Strength] combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BELIEF_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>red kite</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BELIEF_CHIYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Immortal Chiyuan protects the people, and the people of Shenzhou are very grateful[NEWLINE]Every three believers provide +1[ICON_Faith]faith value</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BELIEF_RENXIA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>chivalry</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BELIEF_RENXIA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Immortal Chiyuan and the Seven Disciples of Taixu to slay demons and eliminate demons, the people of Shenzhou resolutely devoted themselves to this great cause. Unlocking the disciples of Yijian Villa[NEWLINE]Melee promotion units will get an additional +5[ICON_Strength] Combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] movement power, and get 50% of the combat power of the unit after the faith value [ICON_Faith]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BELIEF_WULIN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>martial arts</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BELIEF_WULIN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Knights use martial arts to control chaos, and only military power is paramount. Now that the world is in chaos, although I don’t have the guts to directly attack the imperial city, but I do have the ability to kill two corrupt officials who are fish and meat. Unlock Wushuangmen disciple [NEWLINE] close combat The promoted unit will get an additional +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power, and the attacking area wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_WUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>prestige</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_WUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The supreme freedom door is famous, the attack will repel the enemy, +5 extra [ICON_Strength] combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yijian Villa</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Founded by Qin Suyi, the seventh disciple of Taixu's seven apprentices, and her husband &quot;Mr. Chuan&quot;, it is not considered a top sect, but the Twelve Routes of Recalling Heart Sword Art, which is inherited from Taixu's sword energy, is also unique.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_WUSHUANGMEN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>no double door</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_WUSHUANGMEN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Created by Su Mei, the second disciple of Taixu Seven Disciples, under the management of this &quot;Wushuang Fairy&quot;, it has become a giant in the world. There is a saying: It is better to offend the living king than to provoke Wushuang Lang/Mother. Its superior martial arts unparalleled nine-turn is amazingly powerful, but I don't know what price needs to be paid behind this powerful power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_WUSHANGZIZAIMEN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Supreme freedom door</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_WUSHANGZIZAIMEN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Created by Cheng Lingshuang, the fifth apprentice of the seven apprentices of Taixu, since the immortal Chiyuan &quot;Ascension&quot;, it has lived in seclusion with the most powerful &quot;Zizai Sword&quot; in the world. [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Red Kite Immortal</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_RUMOBIZHU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>be damned</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_RUMOBIZHU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The red line drawn by Immortal Red Kite——Being a demon must be punished[NEWLINE]Even her direct disciples are no exception[NEWLINE]When the combat unit faces barbarians and heretics, it will have an additional +7[ICON_Strength] combat power and the unit will not Reduced combat strength due to injury[NEWLINE]When war was declared in ancient times, the whole unit +5[ICON_Strength]combat strength+1[ICON_MOVEMENT]movement for ten rounds[NEWLINE]Under the influence of Shenyin, the cities captured by Taixu Mountain will be directly Razed to the ground, the captured unit will be killed directly, and the god sound will be eliminated after having the history record</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_QITU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Seven Swords</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_QITU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seven Amazing Talents</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MENPAI_APPEAL_BREATHTAKING" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If the mountain is not high, there will be immortals; if the water is not deep, there will be dragons. [NEWLINE]Build a martial arts holy land on a land with at least 4 points of charm, and you will get 4 points of [ICON_Housing] housing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MENPAI_APPEAL_BREATHTAKING_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If the mountain is not high, there will be immortals; if the water is not deep, there will be dragons. [NEWLINE]Build a martial arts holy land on a land with at least 2 points of charm, and you will get 2 points of [ICON_Housing] housing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MENPAI_APPEAL_BREATHTAKING_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The breeze blows the hills~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MENPAI_APPEAL_BREATHTAKING_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Troublesome people come out of poor mountains and bad waters[NEWLINE]Building a martial arts holy land on a plot with at least -2 charm points, you will get 1 point [ICON_Housing] housing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MENPAI_APPEAL_BREATHTAKING_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Troublesome people come out of poor mountains and bad waters[NEWLINE]Building a martial arts holy land on a land with at least -6 points of charm, you will get 2 points of [ICON_Housing] housing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_FOOD1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +1 for extra food from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_FOOD2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +1 for extra food from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_FOOD3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +1 for extra food from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_FOOD4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +1 for extra food from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_FOOD5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +1 for extra food from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_GOLD1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 bonus money from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_GOLD2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 bonus money from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_GOLD3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 bonus money from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_GOLD4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 bonus money from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_GOLD5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 bonus money from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_PRODUCTION1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 extra production from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_PRODUCTION2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 extra production from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_PRODUCTION3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 extra production from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_PRODUCTION4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 extra production from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MOUNTAIN_PRODUCTION5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Self-sufficient, +2 extra production from neighboring mountains</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_CHIYUAN_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Floating life calendar, nothing but success after failure</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ERA_LEADER_CHIYUAN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Taixu Sword Sect founded by Immortal Chiyuan, the martial art of the township is the world-leading Taixu Sword Qi, recognized as the supreme martial arts. The seven disciples under the Chiyuan Immortal Seat, known as the Seven Swords of Taixu, six women and one man, each wield a Xuanyuan Sword, are all extremely talented people.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_CHIYUAN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;You are exactly this kind of person: you will be attracted at first, but the longer you get along, the more you want to stay away.&quot; [NEWLINE] &quot;Thirteen Heroes Chasing Fire&quot; from the anti-Honkai organization of the former civilization has almost infinite Lifespan and unlimited self-recovery ability, spanning countless years, silently fulfilling their duties, in the name of red kite, guarding China, and giving fire to civilization</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_RUMOBIZHU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>be damned</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_RUMOBIZHU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When facing barbarians and heretics, additional +7 [ICON_Strength] combat power, and will not reduce combat power due to injuries</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_WUSHUANGMEN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unparalleled Disciple</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_WUSHUANGMEN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Has higher combat power and maneuverability, and can perform hidden weapon attacks with a range of [ICON_Range] 1</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Disciple of Yijian Villa</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Have lower culture cost and more diverse functionality</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_WUSHUANGMEN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>no double door</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_WUSHUANGMEN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Disciples of Wushuangmen are both good and evil, inquiring about news in the shadows and attacking enemies [NEWLINE] can only be discovered by surrounding units, +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power when attacking injured enemies</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_LINZHAOYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_SUMEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Recalling the Heart Sword Art No. 1</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The first way to teach Yixin swordsmanship, the swordsmanship becomes more and more fierce, and the shots are more disciplined, gaining an additional +3 [ICON_Strength] combat power, and can move after attacking</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Recalling the Heart Sword Art Second Route</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The second way of Yixin swordsmanship is awarded, the swordsmanship becomes more fierce, the body method becomes more flexible, and gains an additional +3 [ICON_Strength] combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic mobility</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Recalling the Heart Sword Art Third Way</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The third way of Yixin swordsmanship is awarded, the swordsmanship becomes more fierce, and the sense becomes more acute, gaining an additional +3 [ICON_Strength] combat power +1 basic vision</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Fourth Way of Recalling Heart Swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Obtained the fourth way of Yixin swordsmanship, the swordsmanship becomes more fierce, the lightness kungfu becomes more proficient, and gains an additional +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power, ignoring the loss of movement power of the land</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_5_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Fifth Way of Recalling Heart Swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_5_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The fifth path of Yixin swordsmanship was awarded, the swordsmanship became more and more fierce, the lightness kung fu reached the limit, gained an additional +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power, and ignored the cliffs</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_6_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Recalling the Heart Sword Art Sixth Route</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_6_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Received the sixth path of Yixin swordsmanship, the swordsmanship becomes more and more fierce, comrades in arms are inseparable, get an additional +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power + 50% support bonus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_7_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Seventh Way of Recalling Heart Swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_7_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Obtained the seventh path of Yixin swordsmanship, the swordsmanship becomes more and more powerful and proficient, gaining an additional +10 [ICON_Strength] combat power, if the movement power is left, you can attack 1 time</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unparalleled Nine Turns First Turn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Practice Wushuang Nine Turns first turn, improve physical fitness, gain additional +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unparalleled Nine Turns Second Turn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Practice Wushuang Nine Turns Second Turn, improve physical fitness, gain an additional +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power, and still have the strength to move after attacking</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unparalleled Nine Turns Third Turn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Practice Wushuang Nine Turns Third Turn, physical fitness has been greatly improved, and additional +7 [ICON_Strength] combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wushuang Nine Turns Fourth Turn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Practicing the fourth turn of the Wushuang ninth turn, the physical fitness has been greatly improved, and an additional +7 [ICON_Strength] combat power + 2 [ICON_Movement] basic mobility</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_5_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unparalleled nine turn fifth turn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_5_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Practice Wushuang Nine Turns Fifth Turn, greatly improve physical fitness, gain additional +10 [ICON_Strength] combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_6_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unparalleled Nine Turns Sixth Turn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_6_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Practicing Wushuang Ninth Turn Sixth, the physical fitness is greatly improved, and extra +10 [ICON_Strength] combat power +1 extra attack times, each attack causes an additional 25% damage, has the tendency to go mad, and suffers 15 Damage Retaliation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_YOULI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yunyou</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_YOULI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Immortal Chiyuan roams around, slays demons and eliminates demons. After completion, you can unlock related items related to the Seven Disciples of the Void and provide them with a 7% experience bonus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_LINZHAOYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Seven Disciples of Taixu · Lin Zhaoyu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_LINZHAOYU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Slay demons and eliminate demons, accept Lin Zhaoyu as an apprentice[NEWLINE] Lin Zhaoyu is kind to others, recruit great people to get 25% faith value [ICON_FAITH] reduction, each trade route provides an additional +1 faith value [ICON_FAITH]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_SUMEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Seven Disciples of Taixu · Su Mei</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_SUMEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Slay demons and demons, accept Sumei [NEWLINE] Sumei is famous, and each affiliated city-state will provide +2 gold coins [ICON_GOLD] + 2 faith [ICON_FAITH]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_JIANGWANXI_AND_JIANGWANRU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Seven Disciples of Taixu·Jiang Wanxi &amp; Jiang Wanru</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_JIANGWANXI_AND_JIANGWANRU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kill demons and eliminate demons, accept Jiang Wanxi and Jiang Wanru as disciples</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_CHENGLINSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Seven Disciples of Taixu·Cheng Lingshuang</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_CHENGLINSHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Slaying demons and demons, accepting apprentice Cheng Lingshuang [NEWLINE] From now on, he will teach on behalf of the teacher, and give +1 level to all the seven apprentices of Taixu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Seven Disciples of Taixu·Ma Yanqing[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_MAFEIMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ma Yanqing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_QINSUYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Seven Disciples of Taixu·Qin Suyi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_QINSUYI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Slay demons and eliminate demons, accept Qin Suyi as an apprentice[NEWLINE]Qin Suyi carefully teaches her daughter and disciples, Yijian Villa will produce an additional +2 technology value [ICON_SCIENCE]+2 cultural value [ICON_CULTURE] and provide for all Yijian The disciples of the villa formed a legion</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Record of Folding Swords in Shenzhou·Li Sushang</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A girl who has become obsessed with martial arts, she learned Taixu Sword Qi from Ling Shuang since she was a child. She went out to test the sword in order to comprehend the &quot;Sword Intent&quot;, but during this trip, she met a stranger, heard a bad news, and embarked on a dangerous road …</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shenzhou Folding Sword Record·Red Kite</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_CHIYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The woman who died and came back to life in a stone room, only the name &quot;Red Kite&quot; and the vague memory of &quot;Seven People&quot; remained in her broken mind</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_JIANGWANXI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_JIANGWANRU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_CHENGLINSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_QINSUYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu five aggregates</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_LINZHAOYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_LINZHAOYU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lin Chaoyu has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power, regardless of the loss of movement power caused by terrain and rivers, regardless of area control, and can detect invisible units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_LINZHAOYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Form and Content</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_LINZHAOYU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lin Zhaoyu has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power under any circumstances, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_LINZHAOYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Implications</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_LINZHAOYU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Lin Zhaoyu's wish, Xuanyuan Sword turns into Qingchenliu[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength] extra combat power, Qingchenliu will crush the enemy's weapon and make it -5[ICON_Strength] combat strength, use Qingchenliu to attack them unpreparedly, causing extra damage and has a chance to cause higher additional damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_SUMEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_SUMEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Su Meide grants Taixu Sword Qi: [NEWLINE] +15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power, ignores the loss of movement power caused by terrain, ignores area control, and can detect invisible units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_SUMEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Form and Content</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_SUMEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Su Meide grants Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength in any situation, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_SUMEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Implications</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_SUMEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Su Mei’s wish, Xuanyuan Sword becomes Wushuang[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 extra attack times, Wushuang will crush the enemy’s weapon and make it -5[ICON_Strength] combat power, Wushuang is a two-sword offensive and defensive one, Deals 50% more damage when attacking, and reduces damage by 50% when defending against non-lethal damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_SUMEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Soul Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_SUMEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, +15 [ICON_Strength] combat power when defending long-range attacks, +1 extra attack times</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_SUMEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wushuang Nine Turns</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_SUMEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The martial arts jointly developed by Ma Feima and Sumei, strengthens the body and organs with true energy, which can be called reborn[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength]extra combat power+1[ICON_Movement]movement power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_JIANGWANXI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_JIANGWANXI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Wanxi has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: [NEWLINE] +15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power, regardless of terrain loss of movement power, regardless of area control, invisible units can be found</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_JIANGWANXI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Form and Content</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_JIANGWANXI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Wanxi has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power under any circumstances, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_JIANGWANXI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Implications</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_JIANGWANXI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Jiang Wanxi's wish, Xuanyuan Sword turns into Feng Qingyang[NEWLINE]+10 extra combat strength, Feng Qingyang will crush the enemy's weapon, making it -5[ICON_Strength]combat strength[NEWLINE]Feng Qingyang can take away the sound, inadvertently Secretly cast a strange poison in between, causing the enemy to receive 10 fixed damage, and -7 [ICON_Strength] combat power, and need to spend an additional 2 [ICON_Gold] gold coins to find strange objects to suppress the poison every round</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_JIANGWANXI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Soul Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_JIANGWANXI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, +15 [ICON_Strength] combat power when defending long-range attacks, +1 extra attack times</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_JIANGWANRU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_JIANGWANRU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Wanru has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: [NEWLINE] +15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power, regardless of terrain loss of movement power, regardless of area control, invisible units can be found</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_JIANGWANRU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Wanru has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength in any situation, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_JIANGWANRU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Implications</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_JIANGWANRU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Jiang Wanxi's wish, Xuanyuan Sword turned into Luo Wuzhuo[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength] extra combat strength, Luo Wuzhuo will crush the enemy's weapon and make it -5 combat strength, the scriptwriter hasn't said what Luo Wuzhuo can do , inadvertently cast a strange poison, causing the enemy to receive 10 fixed damage, and -2 [ICON_Movement] base movement and -2 base vision</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_JIANGWANRU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Soul Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_JIANGWANRU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, +15 [ICON_Strength] combat power when defending long-range attacks, +1 extra attack times</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cheng Lingshuang was awarded Taixu Sword Qi: [NEWLINE] +20 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power, regardless of the loss of movement power caused by terrain, regardless of area control, and can detect invisible units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Form and Content</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cheng Lingshuang was granted Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength in any situation, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Soul Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, +15 [ICON_Strength] combat power when defending long-range attacks, +1 extra attack times</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_SHENYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Divine Aura</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_SHENYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+40 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength, defense against long-range attacks and an additional +40 [ICON_Strength] combat strength [NEWLINE] Taixu Sword God, available (temporarily set to obtain a nuclear bomb)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_MAFEIMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ma Fei Ma De grants Taixu Sword Qi: [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power, regardless of the loss of movement power caused by terrain, regardless of area control, invisible units can be found and killed After the unit recovers 20 health points to reset the number of attacks, this round will temporarily have an extra +5 combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Form and Content</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_MAFEIMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ma Fei Ma De grants Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power under any circumstances, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Implications</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_MAFEIMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Ma Feima's wish, Xuanyuan Sword turns into Chi Jue Ying[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength] extra combat power, Chi Jue Ying will crush the enemy's weapon and make it -5[ICON_Strength] combat power, Chi Jue Ying can distort light to create Illusion, after attacking, two phantoms of horses and non-horses are created, and the value of life is fixed at 1 at the beginning of each round</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Soul Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_MAFEIMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, +15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power when defending long-range attacks, +1 extra attack times</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wushuang Nine Turns</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_MAFEIMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The martial arts jointly developed by Ma Feima and Sumei, strengthens the body and organs with true energy, which can be called reborn[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength]Extra combat power+1 mobility</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_TAIXUZHENJUE_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Truth of Taixu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_TAIXUZHENJUE_MAFEIMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>According to Lin Zhaoyu's request, Ma Feima simplified Taixu's sword shape, Taiyi, Taichu, Taishi, Taisu, Taiji, repeating and recurring, endless [NEWLINE]+7[ICON_Strength] extra combat strength, and an additional 10 points of recovery after the battle Health, can still be recovered after taking action</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_QINSUYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_QINSUYI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qin Suyi has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: [NEWLINE] +15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power, regardless of terrain loss of movement power, regardless of area control, invisible units can be found</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_QINSUYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Form and Content</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_QINSUYI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qin Suyi has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power under any circumstances, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_QINSUYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Implications</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_QINSUYI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Qin Suyi's wish, Xuanyuan Sword turned into Mo Ranxiang[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength] extra combat strength, Mo Ranxiang will crush the enemy's weapon, making it -5 combat strength, &quot;The Xuanyuan swords of the six of us are all weapons, Seventh Sister’s Excalibur is indeed a pen, why do you think &quot;+2 [ICON_Range] attack distance</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_QINSUYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Soul Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_QINSUYI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, +15 [ICON_Strength] combat power when defending long-range attacks, +1 extra attack times</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_QINSUYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Recalling Heart Swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_QINSUYI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qin Suyi combined the shape of the Taixu sword with the sixteen swords of Chuiyan from Li's family, trying to get rid of the influence of the sword heart [NEWLINE]+7[ICON_Strength] extra combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Recalling Heart Swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+7 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength, Li Sushang has practiced the Twelve Ways of Recalling Heart Swordsmanship thoroughly, which is very beneficial for understanding Taixu Sword Qi, +100% experience gain</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Li Sushang has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: [NEWLINE] +20 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power, regardless of terrain loss of movement power, regardless of area control, invisible units can be found</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Form and Content</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Li Sushang has to grant Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power under any circumstances, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Implications</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Qin Suyi's wish, Xuanyuan Sword turned into Ruoshui[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength] extra combat power, Ruoshui will shatter the enemy's weapon and make it -5[ICON_Strength] combat power, if Li Sushang is near the ocean, lake, or river, he will Harnesses the power of the water flow. After each attack, the number of attacks will be restored and the value of life will be restored according to the damage caused.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Soul Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, +15 [ICON_Strength] combat power when defending long-range attacks, +1 extra attack times</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_SHENYUN_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Divine Aura</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_SHENYUN_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+40 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength, defense against long-range attacks and an additional +40 [ICON_Strength] combat strength [NEWLINE] Taixu Sword God, available (temporarily set to obtain a nuclear bomb)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Heart Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINYUN_CHIYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chikite tries to reshape the broken sword heart [NEWLINE] Chikite +20 [ICON_Strength] Extra Combat Power +1 [ICON_Movement] Basic Movement, ignoring the loss of movement power caused by terrain, ignoring area control, invisible units can be found</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Form and Content</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_CHIYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chiyuan recalls Taixu Sword Qi: Xingyun [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power when defending long-range attacks, can still move after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power under any circumstances, attacking the city wall will cause full damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Implications</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_YIYUN_CHIYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inspired by Chiyuan's wish, Xuanyuan Sword becomes Taixu's Grip[NEWLINE]+10[ICON_Strength] extra combat strength, Taixu's Grip will crush the enemy's weapon, making it -5[ICON_Strength] combat strength</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Sword Qi: Soul Accumulation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_CHIYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+15 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, +15 [ICON_Strength] combat power when defending long-range attacks, +1 extra attack times [NEWLINE] Taixu Sword God, available (set to get a nuclear bomb for now)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_LINZHAOYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lin Chaoyu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_LINZHAOYU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The head of the Taixu Seven Disciples, the holder of Xuanyuan Sword &quot;Qingchen Willow&quot;, nicknamed &quot;Qingchen Sword&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SUMEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sumei</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SUMEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The second disciple of the Taixu Seven Disciples, the holder of Xuanyuan Sword &quot;Wushuang&quot;, nicknamed &quot;Wushuang Fairy&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIANGWANXI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Wanxi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIANGWANXI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The third disciple of the Taixu Seven Disciples, the holder of Xuanyuan Sword &quot;Feng Qingyang&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIANGWANRU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Wanru</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIANGWANRU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The fourth disciple of the Taixu Seven Disciples, the holder of Xuanyuan Sword &quot;Luo Wuzhuo&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_CHENGLINSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cheng Lingshuang</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_CHENGLINSHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The fifth disciple of the seven disciples of Taixu, born with stigmata, the only one who has realized the divine essence in the Seven Swords, named &quot;Zizai Sword&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_MAFEIMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ma Fei Ma</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_MAFEIMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The sixth disciple of Taixu's Seven Disciples, the holder of Xuanyuan Sword &quot;Chi Jueying&quot;, nicknamed &quot;Zhuju Sword&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_QINSUYI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qin Suyi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_QINSUYI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The seventh disciple of the Taixu Seventh Disciple, the holder of Xuanyuan Sword &quot;Mo Ran Xiang&quot;, nicknamed &quot;Dan Xiang Jian&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_QITU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taixu Seven Disciples</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_QITU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The seven apprentices of Taixu come from the same school, advance and retreat together, get 75% siege bonus, spread the prestige of Taixu Sword School after killing units, and exert religious pressure on nearby cities [NEWLINE] Taixu Sword Qi is obscure and difficult to understand, gain experience -60%[NEWLINE]The level of swordsmanship is advancing with the times, and the modern age has an extra +15[ICON_STRENGTH]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_BANMU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>half female</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_BANMU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The first disciple of Taixu Seven Disciples, although his martial arts are not high-strength, but he is like a half-mother to other juniors and sisters, providing 25% experience bonus for Taixu Seven Disciples</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_WUSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Peerless</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_WUSHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wisdom is unparalleled, everything is calculated, beauty is unparalleled, and beauty is peerless, Sumei gets 75% siege bonus, enemy units close to Sumei -5 [ICON_Strength] combat power -2 [ICON_Movement] basic movement</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_JIE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>elder sister</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_JIE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sisters support each other, provide each other with +6 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, cover each other when defending against long-range attacks, and provide additional +6 [ICON_Strength] combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>younger sister</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_MEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sisters support each other, provide each other with +6 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, cover each other when defending against long-range attacks, and provide additional +6 [ICON_Strength] combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABLITY_CHENGLINSHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>comfortable</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABLITY_CHENGLINSHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cheng Lingshuang was unstoppable, ignoring all the walls</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABLITY_ZHUJU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>chasing horses</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABLITY_ZHUJU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ma Feima is eager to die, and will not reduce combat effectiveness due to damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_FENGQINGYANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Strange poison</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_FENGQINGYANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>-7[ICON_Strength] combat power, +2[ICON_Gold] round maintenance gold</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_LUOWUZHAO_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Strange poison</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_LUOWUZHAO_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>-2 [ICON_Movement] base movement, -2 base vision</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_XUEYONG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>blood brave</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_XUEYONG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Blood energy surges, +5 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_ZHEJIAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>folding sword</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_ZHEJIAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The weapon is destroyed by Xuanyuan Sword, -5[ICON_Strength] combat strength</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_RELIGION_TAIXU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>too empty</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Li Sushang</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A girl who has become obsessed with martial arts, she learned Taixu Sword Qi from Ling Shuang since she was a child. She went out to test the sword in order to comprehend the &quot;Sword Intent&quot;, but during this trip, she met a stranger, heard a bad news, and embarked on a dangerous road …</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_CHIYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>red kite</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_CHIYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The woman who died and came back to life in a stone room, only the name &quot;Red Kite&quot; and the vague memory of &quot;Seven People&quot; remained in her broken mind</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_LISUSHANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Martial Crazy/Awakening</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_LISUSHANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Additional +50% experience points</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yijian Villa</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The disciple of Yijian Villa is famous all over the world [NEWLINE] +10 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength when holding on to the area, and will cause religious pressure on the surrounding cities after defeating the unit</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_WUSHUANGMEN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wushuang Nine Turns</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_YIJIANSHANZHUANG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Recalling Heart Swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_YIZHI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>legacy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_YIZHI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fully realize the five aggregates of Taixu, become the number one in the world! Li Sushang +20 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power, immediately get 2 promotions</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MENPAI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Holy land of martial arts</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MENPAI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Under the circumstances that the Taixu Sword Sect can't hide from the world, its scattered disciples, even individuals, can be independent. The sect it founded can be called the Holy Land of Martial Arts[NEWLINE]Has a relatively balanced belief value and money output[NEWLINE] After creating the corresponding sect, unique disciples of the sect can be produced</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_RENXIA_MOVEMENT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ren Xia: +1 [ICON_Movement] basic movement power [NewLine] according to the combat power of the defeated unit to obtain 50% of the faith value [NewLine] +5 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_WULIN_STRENGTH_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Martial Arts: +5 [ICON_Strength] Extra Combat Strength [NewLine] Ignores area walls</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LINZHAOYU_BANMU_HEAL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Taught by Lin Zhaoyu, the Taixu Seven Swords gained an additional 25% experience value</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SUMEI_WUSHUANG_MOVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Affected by Wushuang Fairy -2 [ICON_Movement] base movement</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_SUMEI_WUSHUANG_COMBAT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Affected by Wushuang Fairy -5 [ICON_Strength] extra combat strength</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_JIEMEI_JIE_D" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sisters cover each other, +8 [ICON_Strength] extra combat power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_JIEMEI_JIE_A" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sisters cover each other, [ICON_Strength] +8 extra combat power when defending long-range attacks</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_CLASS_DANZHU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Danju</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_DANZHU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Danju</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_CLASS_CANGXUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cang Xuan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_CANGXUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cang Xuan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_RESOURCE_CANGXUAN_OF_BOOK_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Book of Cangxuan, the self-discipline armed doll made by Cangxuan, is loaded with various functions and can make great contributions to the development of civilization, and more importantly, she can bring joy to Hua—but she really very edible</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREATWORK_CHIYUAN_1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>red kite</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREATWORK_CHIYUAN_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>red kite</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREATWORK_CHIYUAN_3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>red kite</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREATWORK_CHIYUAN_4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>red kite</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tinder plan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Execute the fire plan, randomly give five [ICON_TechBoosted] technology Eureka and [ICON_CivicBoosted] culture Eureka, get great prophet and faith value [ICON_FAITH]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_CANGXUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tinder Project: Cangxuan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_CANGXUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Execute the Fire Seed Project, awaken Cangxuan, provide four art slots for the Capital Palace, [ICON_TechBoosted] Technology Eureka +10% [NewLine] and complete the Fire Seed Project·Danzhu at the same time, each time you enter a new era, you will Grant a technology Eureka of the era [ICON_TechBoosted]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_DANZHU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tinder Project: Danju</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_DANZHU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Execute the Fire Seed Project, wake up Danzhu, [ICON_CivicBoosted] culture Eureka +10% [NewLine] and complete the Fire Seed Project · Cangxuan at the same time, each time you enter a new era, you will be given a culture Eureka of that era [ICON_CivicBoosted]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_JIXUANYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inheritance of Tinder: Ji Lin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_JIXUANYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inherit fire, get acquainted with Ji Lin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_LIER_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inheritance of Tinder: Li Er</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_HUOZHONG_LIER_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inherit the fire and get acquainted with Li Er</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIXUANYUAN_YOU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ji Lin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIXUANYUAN_YOU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The ancestor of Shenzhou Taichu, the patriarch of the Xiong clan, the holder of the tenth god key &quot;Xuanyuan Sword&quot;, is still in infancy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIXUANYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ji Lin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIXUANYUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The ancestor of Shenzhou Taichu, the patriarch of the Youxiong clan, the holder of the Tenth God's Key &quot;Xuanyuan Sword&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIXUANYUAN_HEI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jilin·Black</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JIXUANYUAN_HEI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The ancestor of Shenzhou Taichu, the patriarch of the Youxiong Clan, and the holder of the Tenth God's Key &quot;Xuanyuan Sword&quot;, the long years have filled her heart with loneliness and darkness</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_LIER_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Li Er</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_LIER_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The daughter of the general, possesses a different kind of powerful power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_LIER_HONG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Li Er Hong</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_LIER_HONG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The daughter of the general gate possesses a different kind of powerful power, and Dan Li has already controlled her mind</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_CANGXUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cang Xuan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_CANGXUAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Human beings in the pre-civilization era had a twin sister, Dan Zhu, who awakened in Shenzhou thousands of years ago as a girl guarding the Xuanyuan Sword. She was once enshrined as the god of &quot;insight into all things&quot;, but she was actually just a little girl who was greedy for money. That's all</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_DANZHU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Danju</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_DANZHU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Human beings in the pre-civilization era had a twin sister, Cangxuan, who awakened in Shenzhou thousands of years ago as a girl guarding the Xuanyuan Sword. She was once enshrined as the god of &quot;creation of all things&quot;, but in fact she was just a fan of the second dimension That's all</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_JIXUANYUAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xuan Yuan Sword Art</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XUANYUAN_1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xuanyuan Sword Art · Qi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XUANYUAN_1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inherited from the immortal swordsmanship, +7 [ICON_STRENGTH] extra combat power, can still move after attacking</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XUANYUAN_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xuanyuan Sword Art·Hua</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XUANYUAN_2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inherited from the immortal swordsmanship, +7 [ICON_STRENGTH] extra combat power, one more attack times</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XUANYUAN_3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xuanyuan Sword Art·Shou</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XUANYUAN_3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Inherited swordsmanship from immortals, +5[ICON_STRENGTH] extra combat power, +10[ICON_STRENGTH] extra combat power when occupying an area or defending</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XUANYUAN_4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xuanyuan Sword Art·Open</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_XUANYUAN_4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The swordsmanship inherited from the immortals is enough to destroy landslides, +10 [ICON_STRENGTH] extra combat power, ignoring the walls of the area</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CANGXUAN_DISTRICT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cangxuan has a business mind, and built houses in advance, so that the city can build an additional area regardless of the conditions, and create the book of Cangxuan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_SHIBAO_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fu Hua</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_SHIBAO_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Herrscher of Knowledge</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_SHIBAO_SHORT_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Herrscher of Knowledge</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_SHIBAO_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Long live Lady Herrscher of Knowledge!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's hard for me to recite poems</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The cultural output of this civilization is -5%[ICON_CULTURE], the Herrscher of Knowledge will not be framed[NEWLINE]When Fu Hua, the Herrscher of Knowledge takes office, control all enemy units within three squares of the city[NEWLINE] Units trained in the city will get 50% extra experience in battle[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>All kinds of weapons, all kinds of strength</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Units trained in this city will gain an additional +7 combat strength [ICON_STRENGTH] and will not lose combat strength due to damage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sword, sword, halberd, axe, hook and fork</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Production units in this city will increase +25% productivity[ICON_PRODUCTION], and the resources consumed to upgrade units produced here will be reduced by 50%[ICON_PRODUCTION]The strategic resources stored in the city will be +1 every round</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>come and go without trace</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The units produced in this city will ignore the loss of movement power of the land, and can still move after attacking, and +2 [ICON_MOVEMENT] base movement power</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_5_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shadow of the sword and the light of the sword are not what I want</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_5_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The unit produced in this city will be captured as a producer after defeating the combat unit, and after the unit is defeated, gold coins will be obtained according to 80% of the enemy's combat power [ICON_GOLD]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_6_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The world is a sea of ​​suffering</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SHIBAO_6_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This city will ignore religious pressure, and get different productivity [ICON_PRODUCTION] bonuses or debuffs according to satisfaction [NEWLINE] Cause 6 points of loyalty pressure and double religious pressure for this city and surrounding cities every round</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_TAIXU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Taixu Sword Sect founded by Immortal Chiyuan, the martial art of the township is the world-leading Taixu Sword Qi, recognized as the supreme martial arts. The seven disciples under the Chiyuan Immortal Seat, known as the Seven Swords of Taixu, six women and one man, each wield a Xuanyuan Sword, are all extremely talented people.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_LINZHAOYU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_SUMEI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_JIANGWANXI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_JIANGWANRU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_MAFEIMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_QINSUYI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINYUN_LISUSHANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The state of mind melts into the lake until the water stops, the lake of the heart freezes to be dust-free, the ice of the heart is transparent to become a mirror, and the heart-qi is invisible to be empty. Those who have cultivated the sword heart can regard the heaven and the earth as the dantian, and turn the flesh into the meridian. Qi is regarded as the origin of martial arts, and there is no need to hide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_LINZHAOYU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_SUMEI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_JIANGWANXI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_JIANGWANRU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_MAFEIMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_QINSUYI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_XINGYUN_LISUSHANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The shape aggregates of the five aggregates of Taixu have four elements of guarding, transforming, enlightening, and opening, with a total of twenty-one forms. There are three forms of opening sword: crescent moon, broken sea, and split sky; there are six forms of sword transformation: falcon, black falcon, swift, rattan sparrow, cloud eagle, and moon heron; and six forms of guarding sword: weeping willow, orchid, and strength Bamboo, black chrysanthemum, pure lotus, green pine, and the sword shape have six styles: rock breaking, chaotic thunder, thunderbolt, landslide, instant dust, and shocking wind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIYUN_LINZHAOYU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The implication of the five aggregates of Taixu requires the Xuanyuan Sword to be practiced, but the mind and heart of Xuanyuan Sword are interlinked, and the meaning of the sword is self-contained</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIYUN_SUMEI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The implication of the five aggregates of Taixu requires the Xuanyuan Sword to be practiced, but the mind and heart of Xuanyuan Sword are interlinked, and the meaning of the sword is self-contained</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIYUN_JIANGWANXI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The implication of the five aggregates of Taixu requires the Xuanyuan Sword to be practiced, but the mind and heart of Xuanyuan Sword are interlinked, and the meaning of the sword is self-contained</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIYUN_JIANGWANRU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The implication of the five aggregates of Taixu requires the Xuanyuan Sword to be practiced, but the mind and heart of Xuanyuan Sword are interlinked, and the meaning of the sword is self-contained</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIYUN_MAFEIMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The implication of the five aggregates of Taixu requires the Xuanyuan Sword to be practiced, but the mind and heart of Xuanyuan Sword are interlinked, and the meaning of the sword is self-contained</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIYUN_QINSUYI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The implication of the five aggregates of Taixu requires the Xuanyuan Sword to be practiced, but the mind and heart of Xuanyuan Sword are interlinked, and the meaning of the sword is self-contained</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIYUN_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The implication of the five aggregates of Taixu requires the Xuanyuan Sword to be practiced, but the mind and heart of Xuanyuan Sword are interlinked, and the meaning of the sword is self-contained</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIYUN_LISUSHANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The implication of the five aggregates of Taixu requires the Xuanyuan Sword to be practiced, but the mind and heart of Xuanyuan Sword are interlinked, and the meaning of the sword is self-contained</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_SUMEI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The soul aggregate of Taixu's five aggregates is the essence of swordsmanship. The way of the sword is ever-changing, and the sword itself is nothing but a support. After comprehending the soul, all kinds of weapons in the world are like swords, and you don't have to stick to the shape of the sword. Only when you reach this level can you call it a master of swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_JIANGWANXI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The soul aggregate of Taixu's five aggregates is the essence of swordsmanship. The way of the sword is ever-changing, and the sword itself is nothing but a support. After comprehending the soul, all kinds of weapons in the world are like swords, and you don't have to stick to the shape of the sword. Only when you reach this level can you call it a master of swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_JIANGWANRU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The soul aggregate of Taixu's five aggregates is the essence of swordsmanship. The way of the sword is ever-changing, and the sword itself is nothing but a support. After comprehending the soul, all kinds of weapons in the world are like swords, and you don't have to stick to the shape of the sword. Only when you reach this level can you call it a master of swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The soul aggregate of Taixu's five aggregates is the essence of swordsmanship. The way of the sword is ever-changing, and the sword itself is nothing but a support. After comprehending the soul, all kinds of weapons in the world are like swords, and you don't have to stick to the shape of the sword. Only when you reach this level can you call it a master of swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_MAFEIMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The soul aggregate of Taixu's five aggregates is the essence of swordsmanship. The way of the sword is ever-changing, and the sword itself is nothing but a support. After comprehending the soul, all kinds of weapons in the world are like swords, and you don't have to stick to the shape of the sword. Only when you reach this level can you call it a master of swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_QINSUYI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The soul aggregate of Taixu's five aggregates is the essence of swordsmanship. The way of the sword is ever-changing, and the sword itself is nothing but a support. After comprehending the soul, all kinds of weapons in the world are like swords, and you don't have to stick to the shape of the sword. Only when you reach this level can you call it a master of swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The soul aggregate of Taixu's five aggregates is the essence of swordsmanship. The way of the sword is ever-changing, and the sword itself is nothing but a support. After comprehending the soul, all kinds of weapons in the world are like swords, and you don't have to stick to the shape of the sword. Only when you reach this level can you call it a master of swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_HUNYUN_LISUSHANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The soul aggregate of Taixu's five aggregates is the essence of swordsmanship. The way of the sword is ever-changing, and the sword itself is nothing but a support. After comprehending the soul, all kinds of weapons in the world are like swords, and you don't have to stick to the shape of the sword. Only when you reach this level can you call it a master of swordsmanship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_SHENYUN_CHENGLINSHUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The god is extremely changeable. There is also a sword without a sword, and with a deified sword, the sword energy is self-contained, which is the power of the gods. The god is extremely changeable, and everything is wonderful in terms of words, and he cannot be questioned in form. Neither form nor form is needed, the sword fills space, the sword is space. So everywhere, everywhere</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_SHENYUN_CHIYUAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The god is extremely changeable. There is also a sword without a sword, and with a deified sword, the sword energy is self-contained, which is the power of the gods. The god is extremely changeable, and everything is wonderful in terms of words, and he cannot be questioned in form. Neither form nor form is needed, the sword fills space, the sword is space. So everywhere, everywhere</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_SHENYUN_LISUSHANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The god is extremely changeable. There is also a sword without a sword, and with a deified sword, the sword energy is self-contained, which is the power of the gods. The god is extremely changeable, and everything is wonderful in terms of words, and he cannot be questioned in form. Neither form nor form is needed, the sword fills space, the sword is space. So everywhere, everywhere</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_MAFEIMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The content of the martial arts jointly developed by Ma Feima and Sumei has nothing to do with Taixu Sword Qi. In Wushuang Nine Transformations, the dantian is used as a medicine guide, and the meridians are used as a medicine tripod, which draws the true energy to travel throughout the body, strengthening the body and organs. There are nine levels of internal energy, called &quot;Nine Turns&quot;. Every time one breaks through one level, one is reborn, and one's skills are greatly improved. However, none of the sect's disciples can practice it to level six, and all of them lost their minds and died.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_SUMEI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The content of the martial arts jointly developed by Ma Feima and Sumei has nothing to do with Taixu Sword Qi. In Wushuang Nine Transformations, the dantian is used as a medicine guide, and the meridians are used as a medicine tripod, which draws the true energy to travel throughout the body, strengthening the body and organs. There are nine levels of internal energy, called &quot;Nine Turns&quot;. Every time one breaks through one level, one is reborn, and one's skills are greatly improved. However, none of the sect's disciples can practice it to level six, and all of them lost their minds and died.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_WUSHUANGJIUZHUAN_1_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wushuang's ninth turn, sixth turn, is almost insane. The content of the martial arts jointly developed by Ma Feima and Su Mei has nothing to do with Taixu Sword Qi. In Wushuang Nine Transformations, the dantian is used as a medicine guide, and the meridians are used as a medicine tripod, which draws the true energy to travel throughout the body, strengthening the body and organs. There are nine layers of internal energy, called &quot;Nine Turns&quot;, every time you break through a layer, you will be reborn, and your skills will be greatly improved</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITPROMOTIONS_PAGE_PROMOTION_YIXINJIANFA_1_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The seventh path of Yixin swordsmanship, the limit that disciples of Yijian Villa are allowed to learn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_MENPAI_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In the real rivers and lakes, people practice martial arts, practice true qi, fight for righteousness, slay demons and eliminate demons. The six major martial arts sects are even more famous. The seven disciples of Xu went down the mountain to roam the rivers and lakes, which brought a lot of anecdotes to this world, and the sect founded by them, which has the supreme magic skills inherited from the Taixu Sword School, can be called the Holy Land of Martial Arts</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
