<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun Dec 29 18:54:23 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_IBERIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Iberia is a coastal country located at the southern end of Terra. It is conservative and closed due to religious influence. It is one of the few coastal countries in Terra. It was once known as the Golden Kingdom. In the past, it was often associated with enthusiasm, vitality, luxury, and sunshine on the coast. In recent years, it has gradually become quiet.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_IBERIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>With the help of the Argors, known as &quot;islanders&quot;, Iberia's technology continued to develop and it became a great power on the Terra continent. Iberia then continued to develop towards the ocean, with tens of thousands of ships forming a huge fleet that roamed the sea. Sleeping under the golden city. They also used drilling to exploit marine resources and even built many fortresses on the sea for this purpose. Every night, thousands of lighthouses on the seashore guided the ships. In order to make Iberia stronger, the Argors captured a large number of people from the land, and many of them eventually stayed there forever.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_IBERIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Iberia's national strength continued to grow, and after conquering Bolivar, it gradually entered its golden age. But the good days of the golden age did not last. In 1038, the &quot;Great Silence&quot; broke out in Iberia. The ocean fell into an unprecedented calm, the coast became strange, and the violent ebb tide and irregular waves announced the coming of disaster.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_IBERIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>With the arrival of the &quot;Great Silence&quot;, Iberia's coastal cities suffered great damage, resulting in a technological gap and the abandonment of most technological products. The destruction of the energy system also made it impossible for those lighthouses to light up normally. Now Iberia has tightened restrictions on foreign entry and severely cracked down on &quot;islanders&quot;.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_IBERIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Iberia implemented a system of combining politics and religion to strengthen religious control over the people. Iberian religion strictly followed the Lateran doctrine, and many bishops carried out missionary activities in various parts of the country. Iberia was often discussed together with the Lateran because of its long-standing religious connection. Iberian religion was once directly under the Lateran Pope, but gradually separated and eventually established the &quot;Iberian State Church&quot; and became independent.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_IBERIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Andorn, a Sakota living in Tidestone Town, Iberia, was deeply disappointed with Lateran's inaction in the face of the Iberian disaster, and founded the heretical organization &quot;The Wayfinder&quot;. After the &quot;Great Silence&quot;, the State Church gradually evolved into the Inquisition, becoming a tool of pure religious oppression. Some members of the Deep Sea Church also disguised themselves as bishops under the guise of the State Church to secretly infiltrate the &quot;Sea Heirs&quot; ideology, achieve assimilation with the &quot;Sea Heirs&quot;, and expand the organization's foundation.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CARMEN_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Carmen</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CARMEN_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Carmen</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CARMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The full name is &quot;Carmen iberia&quot;, Dario's teacher, one of the nine saints of the Iberian Inquisition, the only saint still alive, and his age is beyond imagination.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CARMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The former high-ranking official of the Iberian State Church, after the Great Silence swept Iberia, rejected the Pope status bestowed by the Iberian royal family, and immediately took the lead of 12 relevant people to transform the State Church into the Inquisition. Nine main members, including Carmen, were canonized as &quot;saints&quot;, and all of them changed their last names to &quot;Iberia&quot;. The Inquisition also became the highest authority representing Iberia. Through Kal'tsit's mediation, he and Gloria, who represented Agor, temporarily put aside their prejudices, and jointly participated in the operation to restart the Eye of Iberia and search for the Stutifila (also known as the Fool). Afterwards, he and Gloria explained their situation and cooperation to each other, and accepted Jordi as an apprentice.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CARMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_CARMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_IRENE_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Elini</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_IRENE_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Elini</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_IRENE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Elini, former Iberian Inquisitor, student of Grand Inquisitor Dario. She is very knowledgeable about Iberian history, law, human geography, etc. After the &quot;Fool&quot; incident, she resigned from her position as an Inquisitor. With Kal'tsit's personal recommendation, she now signs a cooperation agreement with Rhodes Island as a messenger of the Inquisition to prepare for the threat from the ocean.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_IRENE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A former member of the Iberian Inquisition, she studied under Grand Inquisitor Dario, knew Iberian scriptures and laws by heart, and was skilled in swift swordplay - if you had met her in Iberia, she would have held her head high and proudly introduced herself like this.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_IRENE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After Elini came to Rhodes Island, she never took the initiative to talk about her past identity, or rather, she seemed to have quickly accepted the change of identity.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_IRENE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>All of Elini's files were handled by Kal'tsit. Without going through any tedious procedures, Elini was registered as a Rhodes Island operator. Elini was then assigned to the Iberia Special Operations Group and was temporarily not involved in general missions. But apart from work, Elini would eat and sleep with other operators normally, actively learn combat skills that she had not yet mastered, abide by Rhodes Island's rules and regulations more strictly than others, and spend all her leisure time in the library. Elini occasionally sighed, which reminded her of her days as an apprentice in the Inquisition. Elini's efforts have paid off. After she came to Rhodes Island for a while, not to mention the internalized knowledge, the improvement in combat skills and comprehensive physical fitness test scores alone was enough to make the instructors and the reserve operators of the same period look at her differently.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_IRENE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Everything Elini does is in line with what she said: &quot;My identity does not determine who I am, but what I do determines who I am.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_IRENE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It was also after a long period of time that most of the operators of Rhodes Island finally realized that although she always looked very serious and stern, Elini was definitely not someone who would reject the friendship of others. She would definitely lend a hand to those who asked her for help, and would also generously recommend the music of the Golden Age of Iberia to those who loved music. There were also a few times when someone noticed that in some happy occasions, Elini watched Goletia dancing from a distance, with a faint expression of eagerness on her face.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LUMEN_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>lumen</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LUMEN_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>lumen</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LUMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lumen, introduced by Abyss and Kal'tsit, is now serving as Rhodes Island's Iberian Operator, assisting Rhodes Island in carrying out medical care for infected people in Iberia. At the same time, Lumen will also attend a series of meetings between Rhodes Island, Agor, and the Inquisition, and make suggestions based on his own perspective, and work with all parties to find a way to cooperate and face the future.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LUMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Operator Lumen, whose real name is Jordi Fontanarossa, was born in a declining town called Granfaro in Iberia and has long worked as a caretaker at the local chapel. Perhaps because the person who took care of him was the mayor of the town, Lumen's identity as an Agor Islander did not cause him any real trouble for a long time, which was very rare in Granfaro, a place that was under the core control of the Inquisition.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LUMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>But it is more likely that Liuming's peaceful life should be attributed to himself. Regardless of his professional identity, this operator has an innate affinity. He will pay close attention to the demands of everyone around him and lend a hand when the time is right. Even if he cannot really help due to his limited ability, Liuming is very happy to act as a gentle companion. What's more rare is that he has no idea how valuable his attitude of getting along with others with sincerity is.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LUMEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We should be thankful that such a quality can be born in Iberia where life can be considered harsh.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
