<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun May  7 00:47:35 2023-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Year</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>inflammation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_YAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>inflammation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_HONG_LU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There is an oven</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_HONG_LU_NAME_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+50% when executing city projects [ICON_Production] Productivity[NEWLINE] Provides a special area - Oven, which will unlock a series of special items [NEWLINE] (For details, please check in Encyclopedia-Resources-Strategy-Mother Pepper )</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_YAN_WU_JING_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Disheng Hardware</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_YAN_WU_JING_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mineral resources provide additional +1 [ICON_Production] productivity, +1 [ICON_Culture] culture [NEWLINE] and strategic resources belonging to mineral resources unlock the corresponding technology and get several copies for free every round</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>oven</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Initially unlocked, the construction cost is low, and it can provide a lot of [ICON_Production] productivity for the city[NEWLINE] After completion, it will provide +3 [ICON_RESOURCE_PEPPER_MOM] Pepper Mom every round to perform special projects [NEWLINE] At the same time, the city can ignore [ICON_Citizen] after the area is completed Population builds an additional district.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_DISTRICT_NIAN_FILM_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>film studio</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_DISTRICT_NIAN_FILM_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Replace the theater, the cost is half of the normal area, and provide +1 charm for adjacent cells by[NEWLINE] (limited to one execution per item)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_FU_SHENG_TING_FENG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>floating life listening to the wind</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_FU_SHENG_TING_FENG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the screening, a small amount of [ICON_Culture] cultural output will be provided. After the screening, [ICON_DISTRICT_NIAN_FILM] film studios in all cities will have +3 [ICON_Culture] culture; the city that completed the project will have +6 [ICON_Culture] culture and [ICON_Culture] cultural output +10% and get a souvenir</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MENG_YUAN_ZHI_DI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Land of Dreams</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_MENG_YUAN_ZHI_DI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the screening, a small amount of [ICON_Culture] cultural output will be provided. After the screening, a [ICON_GreatWriter] great writer, a [ICON_GreatArtist] great artist and a [ICON_GreatMusician] great musician will be obtained; all cities will get [ICON_GreatPerson] great person points +50 %, at the same time your civilization sponsors [ICON_GreatPerson] great people need to spend 20% less [ICON_Gold] and get a souvenir</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_LING_HAO_TE_GONG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Agent Zero</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_LING_HAO_TE_GONG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the screening, a large amount of [ICON_Gold] gold coins will be produced, and after the screening, melee units will be provided with the effect of ignoring the debuffs of river [ICON_Movement] and hilly [ICON_Movement] and +5 [ICON_Strength] attack power; spy cap +5, And the spy can be promoted to [ICON_Promotion] as an agent at the beginning, and get souvenirs at the same time</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_XIANG_XIAN_JIE_GOU_ZHE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>quadrant deconstructor</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_XIANG_XIAN_JIE_GOU_ZHE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the screening, a small amount of [ICON_Science] technology output will be provided. After the screening, [ICON_DISTRICT_NIAN_FILM] film studios in all cities will have +6 [ICON_Production] productivity and [ICON_Science] technology. Tech gets [ICON_TechBoosted] Eureka Boost, +20% [ICON_Science] Tech for cities with a population of 10 [ICON_Citizen] and 4 [ICON_District] specialization districts, and gets a souvenir</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>According to legend, in the distant past, within the vast territory of the Great Yan, there were gods.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A certain emperor of Yan looked at his prosperous and prosperous land, but suffered from natural disasters and man-made disasters. He felt deeply sympathetic and thought hard for a long time. The true dragon who has been controversial in history was a young man at the time, full of enthusiasm. As Emperor Dayan, he said something like this to his confidants——</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Since the whole world, is it the land of the king, and the shore of the land, is it the king's ministers. Then why are those high and wild creatures unwilling to obey the wishes of the people of Dayan and protect the land of the people of Dayan? You should know that the &quot;immortals&quot; in folklore or history in some countries are not just philosophical concepts. But they are not really so &quot;high above&quot;.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The real dragon found one of them among the mountains and deep pools, an arrogant and disdainful god, and he devoted all his strength to conquer by himself. Following the order of the real dragon, how many horrifying strangers also joined in this horrifying hunt. Unexpectedly, the rising thing that the real dragon first saw, it absurdly betrayed its own kind and relatives, it divided its power, and participated in this rare hunt.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After the big hunt, Dayan killed several &quot;gods&quot; who dared to offend the real dragon, and expelled all the beings who did not want to bow to the real dragon. Blood flowed into rivers, and corpses were buried for thousands of miles. Dayan paid a painful price. The controversy over the real dragon also began. But he himself didn't care at all, and this career lasted the real dragon's life.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When he was very old, he found the last one that still stayed on the land of Yan Kingdom, the oldest and tallest thing that had helped the real dragon and betrayed his relatives. This traitor has already suffered its due retribution. Before leaving Great Flame, its arrogance was thwarted by its fellow clansmen, exposing its arrogance to the emperor's masters—in short, the merits and demerits are balanced, and the real dragon spares it from death , but it must surrender to Dayan. Establish a heart for the world, establish a life for the living and the people, inherit the knowledge of the past saints, and create peace for all generations.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>From then on, Dayan Guozuo was only in the hands of the real dragon, and only in the hands of the people of Dayan.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_YAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The leader character of this module comes from the game &quot;Tomorrow's Ark&quot; produced by Yingjiao Network, and uses some art materials of the game.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_YAN_LOCATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>inflammation</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_YAN_SIZE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>this place was wiped</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_YAN_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>unknown</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_YAN_CAPITAL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The easternmost country on the continent of Terra</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_YAN_NIAN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_SUBTITLE}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Okay, let's go, let's have hot pot together</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What? Let's talk after you beat me in betting, craps, wrestling, etc.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seeing how bored you are...here, here is this toy for you. at work? Isn't work just boring? You have to watch closely, this little puppet will disappear if you don't pay attention.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, idle, I want to go shopping... Never mind, I want to go out! ......Um? Why don't you change your shoes? Of course you have to follow me, otherwise.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Why did you fall asleep again? Get up, go shopping with me, hurry up.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Going to war is something that cannot be avoided in any era.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How can life and death be handed over?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Attacking the Shield of the Son with the Spear of the Son will cause a big explosion!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>not bad! In you, I see a glimmer of hope for you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This small dish is not enough to fill the teeth.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Eh, no more.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>anyone there? The employees of your company told me that the living conditions here are very good, with free board and lodging, and various forms of entertainment... Idle people are not allowed to enter? Hey, don't be like this, just save face.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Why should I waste my time with you shoddy creations?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Craftsmen who forge weapons must bear the blood they bring. [NEWLINE] (condemns you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>anyone there? The employees of your company told me that the living conditions here are very good, with free board and lodging, and various forms of entertainment... Idle people are not allowed to enter? Hey, don't be like this, just save face.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>yes yes you are a good fit as a reserve in my movie</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>you are kind of interesting</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hello, are you interested in starring in my movie?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>People, like utensils, have their own character. You seem to be worthy of my forging a weapon.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_REASON_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Nian's favor for you has increased)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>oh? Shall I do it myself?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_REASON_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Nian's favor for you has decreased)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My sword can cut apart the existence value of the enemy as well as the flesh.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey, what a hassle</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My dreams have become blurred</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well, these things don't mean anything to me</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>hahaha, of course</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>hahaha, of course</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't move! I'm making ornaments, be careful!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let's go, let's go shopping</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ming Wang Shengdi, who can go to the army?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Haha, it's a pleasure to get along with you</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It feels like giving these things to you is a waste.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I only have eleven siblings. I'm not here to ask for help, who can help us in this situation? [NEWLINE] (Swap capital location)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Year</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There are beasts like a chalky belly, like a big cauldron, its nine horns look like red copper, it lasts for a long time, and its color changes for a few days. [NEWLINE]...[NEWLINE] The Corroded Ware of the Destroyed Country of False Mould, Eternal Era, Rust Like a Dream, Like Electricity, Without a Trace[NEWLINE]Many parts have been blurred and cannot be read</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A dagger of simple design. It is said that the edge of a dagger will disappear if it is used for a cause such as murder.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Years old, unemployed, familiar with various metal crafts, possessing profound knowledge of metallurgy that does not match his identity. Currently in Rhode Island as a visitor and occasionally advising on metalworking projects in Rhode Island. Claims to be good at audio-visual entertainment, and often provides some audio-visual products that Rhode Island operators generally don't like.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Insisted on entering Rhode Island as a visitor in 2009 and refused to undergo medical testing. After a series of competitions such as betting on alcohol, rolling dice, and wrestling, the matter of collecting physiological data was finally settled. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE] &quot;It's a pity that Gavial lost in rock climbing in the end! She was almost forced to go for a medical examination. I didn't expect Gavial to really contribute to the medical department. Come on, Gavial! You can do it next year!&quot; [NEWLINE] ——Medical Operator Fu Rong</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When did they come to Rhodes Island in 2010, most of the operators can't remember clearly. Surprisingly, Dr. Kelsey did not drive away the visitors as usual. Dr. Kelsey hurried to the operating room after dropping the sentence &quot;Let her do what she wants.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Amiya and Nian have a friendly relationship, but most of the time, the two rarely meet. This may be because Amiya has been working, but Nian has been resting, or on vacation, or even...doing nothing all day long. Because Nian is not an employee of Rhodes Island, the operators of Rhodes Island are not good at evaluating her behavior. [NEWLINE] Fortunately, Nian has no habit of interfering with other people's work, and most of the time she just enjoys herself, which makes many operators turn a blind eye to her. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE] &quot;No habit of interfering with other people's work&quot;? She persuades others to go to work and play mahjong. Does anyone stop her? [NEWLINE] —— Rhodes Island Operator Yato</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although her attitude is a bit bad, Nian is still a kind-hearted person, and she can even be described as enthusiastic in front of the engineering operators. [NEWLINE] The annual meeting is very devoted to discussing the similarities and differences of various materials with the engineering staff, and participating in the design and experiment of new alloys. Once structural issues were involved, she would even stay up with the engineering operators for several days. At least, among the engineering operators, Nian is insulated from the word &quot;idle&quot;. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]While watching Nian and the weapon designers arguing over the blueprints, the author speculates that maybe Nian is just more used to spending time on hobbies rather than ordinary daily work. However, when the position of Rhodes Island engineering operator was recommended to her, she still refused. [NEWLINE] It must be pointed out that Nian treats practitioners in the metal processing industry much more gently than she treats other people. Generally, only the reserve actors in the so-called &quot;independent films&quot; she plans to shoot can enjoy such treatment. Why?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Nian's forging skills are very superb, unmatched in the execution of projects, and Nian's forging skills are used reasonably; Correspondingly, Nian is also a director of (bad movies), and currently there are four new works that are being screened. Use these advantages to win.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The ability of the year can bring a lot of [ICON_Production] productivity bonuses to the city. Reasonable planning of the [ICON_District] area can allow you to get a lot of [ICON_Production] productivity in the early stage of the year. Use these [ICON_Production] productivity to implement the characteristic projects of the year and continue To expand the advantages, with the blessing of high productivity, no matter whether it is victory in conquest or victory in technology, it is not a problem. At the same time, as a well-known (not) director, Nian should not be underestimated (guilty) in terms of [ICON_Culture] culture, maybe if he develops it well, Nian director also has the possibility of cultural victory.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>{LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_YAN_NIAN_QUOTE}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_YAN_NIAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>who can go to the army</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_YAN_NIAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Likes civilizations that pursue peace and dislikes civilizations that wage war.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_YAN_NAME_RHODESISLAND" Language="en_US">
			<Text>rhode island</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hui Qishan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shang Shu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gou Wu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>evening castle</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiang Qi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yumen</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mi Chu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zhu Hua</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_CIVILIZATION_YAN_NAME_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Longmen</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>evening</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>make</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shigetake</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Clos</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>hot melt</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>nothing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Saga</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lin Yuxia</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>List</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Huaihu</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>star bear</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shi Huaiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>mudstone</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_14" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tequila</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_15" Language="en_US">
			<Text>puppet</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_16" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Amiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_17" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Aiyafala</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_18" Language="en_US">
			<Text>first snow</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_19" Language="en_US">
			<Text>piano willow</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_20" Language="en_US">
			<Text>leonhardt</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_21" Language="en_US">
			<Text>texas</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_22" Language="en_US">
			<Text>white-faced owl</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_23" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yankee</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_24" Language="en_US">
			<Text>water moon</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_YAN_NAME_25" Language="en_US">
			<Text>THRM-EX</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_Production_Extra1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Science] Science from every two adjacent regions.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_Production_Extra2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production from every two adjacent regions.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_CLOSE_HONG_LU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production from each adjacent oven.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_CLOSE_INDUSTRIAL_ZONE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production from each adjacent Industrial District.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_CLOSE_GOVERNMENT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production from each adjacent Town Square.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_CLOSE_AQUEDUCT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production from each adjacent aqueduct.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_IMPROVEMENT_MINE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production from each adjacent mine.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_IMPROVEMENT_QUARRY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num}[ICON_Production] Production from each adjacent quarry.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_FEATURE_GEOTHERMAL_FISSURE_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Science] Science comes from every adjacent geothermal fissure.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_FEATURE_GEOTHERMAL_FISSURE_PRODUCTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production from each adjacent Geothermal Fissure.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_FEATURE_VOLCANIC_SOIL_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Science] Science from each adjacent volcanic soil.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_FEATURE_VOLCANIC_SOIL_PRODUCTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production from each adjacent Volcanic Dirt.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There is an oven in the sky, hardware is born in the earth, and the cloud is cleared by the coldness of Huiye.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_NIAN_FILM_CLOSE_NIAN_FILM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Culture] culture from each adjacent year movie studio.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_NIAN_FILM_CLOSE_GOVERNMENT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Culture] culture from each adjacent town square.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_NIAN_NIAN_FEATURE_PAMUKKALE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Culture] culture from each adjacent Pamukkale cell.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_NIAN_FILM_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dear viewers and friends, thank you for your attention and support to the Nian Film Studio. [NEWLINE]We are very honored to announce here that the four new works of the director of the year have been screened. [NEWLINE]Let's walk into the fairy-tale &quot;Land of Dreams&quot; together, &quot;Floating Life Listening to the Wind&quot; by the pine and bamboo forest; while &quot;Quadrant Deconstructor&quot; passes through the night, the figure of &quot;Agent Zero&quot; will also blend into the city In the midst of all our efforts, we only aim to bring the perfect artistic experience to your eyes. [NEWLINE]Come on, don't miss out. Everything, all in the movie studio!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_RESOURCE_PEPPER_MOM_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mama Pepper</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_RESOURCES_PAGE_RESOURCE_PEPPER_MOM_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mother's taste, real ingredients, spicy to overbearing, even more after trying, Southwest specialty, ingenuity inheritance-Chili Mom! [NEWLINE]A special drink from a certain southwestern mobile city-state in Yan Kingdom. It tastes spicy and is said to be a kind of seasoning.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_RARE_METALS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rare Metal Identification</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_RARE_METALS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When the project is in progress, a small amount of [ICON_Gold] gold coins will be provided every round. After completing the project, all mineral resources will have an additional +1 [ICON_Science] Technology, +1 [ICON_Gold] Gold, +1 [ICON_Production] Productivity</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_PLASTIC_WORKING_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>metal plastic processing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_PLASTIC_WORKING_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When the project is in progress, a small amount of [ICON_Gold] gold coins will be provided every round. After completing the project, cities with [ICON_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU] ovens get +15% [ICON_Production] production, and if the city also has [ICON_DISTRICT_INDUSTRIAL_ZONE] industrial zones, they get an additional +10% [ICON_Production] production</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_FORGING_TEMPERATURE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Increase forging temperature</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_FORGING_TEMPERATURE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When the project is in progress, a small amount of [ICON_Gold] gold coins will be provided every round. After completing the project, the adjacency bonus of the oven [ICON_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU] +100%</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_METAL_CASTING_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>metal casting</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_METAL_CASTING_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When the project is in progress, a small amount of [ICON_Gold] gold coins will be provided every round. The adjacency bonus of the Oven [ICON_DISTRICT_NIAN_HONG_LU] also gives [ICON_Gold] gold upon completion of the project, and an additional +33% [ICON_Production] Production when performing city projects</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_DUN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>cast shield</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_DUN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After completing the project, the city gets a stronger [ICON_Fortified] external defense, all cities +4 [ICON_Culture] culture, and unlocks subsequent projects</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_DUN_A_NOTIFICATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+10 [ICON_Fortified] External Defense</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_DUN_A_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forged Shield (unit [ICON_Fortified] Defense)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_DUN_A_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Every time this item is completed, +3 [ICON_Fortified] defense for all combat units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_DUN_FY_A_NOTIFICATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Fortified] Defense</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_DUN_B_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forged Shields (Building [ICON_Production] Production)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_DUN_B_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Every time this project is completed, build buildings for all cities +30% [ICON_Production] Production</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>casting</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After completing the project, provide 2 [ICON_VIEW_TRADE] trade routes and 3000 [ICON_Gold] gold coins, and unlock subsequent projects</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_A_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Castings (build [ICON_Charges] times)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_A_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When the project is in progress, a small amount of [ICON_Gold] gold coins will be provided every round. Each time the item is completed, it adds a [ICON_Charges] charge to the builder</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_B_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mint (city [ICON_Gold] gold production)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_B_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When the project is in progress, a lot of [ICON_Gold] gold coins will be provided every round. Every time the project is completed, the city's [ICON_Gold] gold coin production +15%</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_C_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Casts (city [ICON_Citizen] development speed)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_C_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Every time this project is completed, the city's [ICON_Citizen] population growth rate and [ICON_Food] food +20%, and provide 4 [ICON_Housing] housing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_D_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forge (City [ICON_Amenities] Amenities)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_WU_D_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Every time this project is completed, the city +2 [ICON_Amenities] amenity</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>cast soldiers</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_Movement] movement and vision to all units upon completion of the project, and unlocks follow-up projects</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_A_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forge (unit [ICON_Promotion] promotion)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_A_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After completing the project, all units will receive 1 [ICON_Promotion] promotion, limited to 1 completion</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_B_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forge (unit [ICON_Strength] attack power)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_B_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Every time this item is completed, +3 [ICON_Strength] attack power for all combat units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_GJ_B_A_NOTIFICATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num}[ICON_Strength] Attack Strength (from Forge)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_C_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Forge (unit [ICON_Production] Production)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_ZHU_BING_C_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Production of combat units for all cities +20% [ICON_Production] Productivity per completion of the project</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_FU_SHENG_TING_FENG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[COLOR_LIGHTBLUE]Floating Life Listening to the Wind[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_FU_SHENG_TING_FENG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the screening, a small amount of [ICON_Culture] cultural output will be provided. After the screening, [ICON_DISTRICT_NIAN_FILM] film studios in all cities will have +3 [ICON_Culture] culture; the city that completed the project will have +6 [ICON_Culture] culture and [ICON_Culture] cultural output +10% and get a souvenir</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_MENG_YUAN_ZHI_DI_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[COLOR:ResScienceLabelCS]Dreamland[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_MENG_YUAN_ZHI_DI_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the screening, a small amount of [ICON_Culture] cultural output will be provided. After the screening, a [ICON_GreatWriter] great writer, a [ICON_GreatArtist] great artist and a [ICON_GreatMusician] great musician will be obtained; all cities will get [ICON_GreatPerson] great person points +50 %, at the same time your civilization sponsors [ICON_GreatPerson] great people need to spend 20% less [ICON_Gold] and get a souvenir</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_LING_HAO_TE_GONG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[COLOR:Red]Agent Zero[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_LING_HAO_TE_GONG_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the screening, a large amount of [ICON_Gold] gold coins will be produced, and after the screening, melee units will be provided with the effect of ignoring the debuffs of river [ICON_Movement] and hilly [ICON_Movement] and +5 [ICON_Strength] attack power; spy cap +5, And the spy can be promoted to [ICON_Promotion] as an agent at the beginning, and get souvenirs at the same time</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_XIANG_XIAN_JIE_GOU_ZHE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[COLOR:ScienceDark]Quadrant Deconstructor[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_NIAN_XIANG_XIAN_JIE_GOU_ZHE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the screening, a small amount of [ICON_Science] technology output will be provided. After the screening, [ICON_DISTRICT_NIAN_FILM] film studios in all cities will have +6 [ICON_Production] productivity and [ICON_Science] technology. Tech gets [ICON_TechBoosted] Eureka Boost, +20% [ICON_Science] Tech for cities with a population of 10 [ICON_Citizen] and 4 [ICON_District] specialization districts, and gets a souvenir</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_NIAN_LING_HAO_TE_GONG_C_STRENGTH_NOTIFICATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num}[ICON_Strength] Attack Strength (from Agent Zero)</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
