<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Mon Dec 30 00:35:01 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MarkOfHuiMing_Culture" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from neighboring {LOC_IMPROVEMENT_MARK_OF_HM_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MarkOfHuiMing_Faith" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_FAITH] Faith from adjacent {LOC_IMPROVEMENT_MARK_OF_HM_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MarkOfHuiMing_Science" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_SCIENCE] Science value comes from adjacent {LOC_IMPROVEMENT_MARK_OF_HM_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MarkOfHuiMing_Gold" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold from neighboring {LOC_IMPROVEMENT_MARK_OF_HM_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MarkOfHuiMing_Production" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_PRODUCTION] Productivity from neighboring {LOC_IMPROVEMENT_MARK_OF_HM_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GuardDepartment_Culture" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from neighboring {LOC_DISTRICT_GUARD_DEPARTMENT_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GuardDepartment_Faith" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_FAITH] Faith from neighboring {LOC_DISTRICT_GUARD_DEPARTMENT_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GuardDepartment_Science" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_SCIENCE] Science value comes from neighboring {LOC_DISTRICT_GUARD_DEPARTMENT_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GuardDepartment_Gold" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_GOLD] Gold from neighboring {LOC_DISTRICT_GUARD_DEPARTMENT_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GuardDepartment_Production" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Num} [ICON_PRODUCTION] Productivity from neighboring {LOC_DISTRICT_GUARD_DEPARTMENT_NAME}</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LINYX_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lin Yuxia</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LINYX_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lin Yuxia</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LINYX_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>President of the Longmen Youth Entrepreneurs Association, visiting lecturer of social relations at Longmen Union University, rotating spokesperson of the Longmen Chamber of Commerce, administrative consultant of the Longmen Market Supervision Bureau... This series of positions are all on Lin Yuxia's resume.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LINYX_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Faced with such a file, we certainly cannot play dumb.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LINYX_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although we have never had direct contact, we all know more or less what kind of dangerous person &quot;Gray Lin&quot; is. Although that gentleman has given some care to Rhodes Island in previous indirect contacts, now his daughter came to us directly and proposed to establish a drug purchase channel between the slums and Rhodes Island, and to consider further cooperation such as bypassing the official dispatch of medical operators, which is a completely different matter. Faced with this headache-inducing cooperation invitation, what finally made us make up our minds was a letter sent by Operator Chen. Apart from those words with personal emotions, the meaning expressed in the letter is very clear-she is willing to trust Miss Lin Yuxia from a personal perspective, and is willing to recommend this cooperation to Rhodes Island as an operator.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LINYX_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;Trust can be betrayed, but interests cannot. When it comes to treating infected people, my interests are aligned with Rhodes Island's.&quot; Ms. Lin Yuxia made this frank explanation about the cooperation. In any case, Rhodes Island's position as a medical company and its ideal of working to resolve conflicts among infected people will not change. As she said, we have no reason to refuse for the time being.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LEE_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Old Carp</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LEE_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Old Carp</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LEE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A middle-aged man who seems to be casual and undisciplined. His nominal job is a private detective. He is proficient in all the basic detective skills such as tracking, disguise, negotiation, and reasoning, but the skills that Lao Li uses most often are making tea and cooking. Many operators have commented that he &quot;has a temperament that makes others lose their motivation just by being with him.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LEE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lao Li is not based in Rhodes Island all the time. He occasionally comes to visit several children in the office under the guise of interviewing with the doctor. After confirming that everyone is living well, he hands over all his work to them and then leaves leisurely. For the logistics department of Rhodes Island, the days when Lao Li comes are festive and grand moments. The reason is simple: after eating the dishes made by Hong, every logistics operator is very curious about the level of Lao Li's cooking skills, and they all look forward to the legend of the food world in Longmen Alley to teach them a thing or two. Only a few times has Lao Li demonstrated his skills in the Rhodes Island cafeteria. It is no exaggeration to say that the whole cafeteria was boiling at that time.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_LEE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;I really don't understand why he opened a detective agency instead of a restaurant. Does he have a grudge against Longmen Coin?&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_DUSK_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>evening</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_DUSK_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>evening</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_DUSK_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;There is a beast of green color, shaped like mountains. There are 11 of them. It wears the moon and is covered with smoke. The clouds are faint and the color of dusk can be seen. Its beard is indigo like a forest, and its bones are steep like stones. It is said that the stars hide the snow and the moon is dim and bright. People are clear or turbid, and their colors are good or bad. It is difficult to hurt with five weapons and difficult to prevent with five fires. Its flesh and blood are burned, and the ink fountain flows. The fog is gone and the smoke is gone. Two poems are unrestrained. However, the beast is difficult to control. It is easy to change from morning to night, and it disappears suddenly. Its shape is also false, and its thing is also false. The pen is used to close the scroll, as if it is drunk or crazy, and it is burned out in one night.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
