<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun Dec 29 18:16:40 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LATERANO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Laterano, or the city of Laterano, is a theocratic state located in the central part of Terra. It borders Syracuse, Victoria and Leitania to the north, Iberia to the south, and Rembil to the east.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LATERANO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In the distant past, the Tikaz tried to seek power from under the earth. But the Tikaz at that time could not control such power. Many Tikaz died at the excavation site, and the original Sakta fled the excavation, which was both self-saving and suicide.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LATERANO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thousands of years ago, when Sakota was homeless, the first generation of saints walked on the earth and were hunted by Ticazes. They received a revelation to &quot;build a city, which is the paradise of Sakota&quot;. So they built the Stone Tower of Revelation, and then built a city around the Stone Tower of Revelation. According to the revelation, they named this city Lateran.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LATERANO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In 1063, Evangelista XI became the new Lateran Pope. [NEWLINE]In 1098, the Pope sent an invitation to the nations of Terra through the Messengers of Nations: a meeting was held in the Lateran, inviting the nations to send envoys to discuss collective security issues. [NEWLINE]In 1099, the Messengers of Nations system was born for 30 years. In March of the same year, the Messengers of Nations scattered across Terra, along with envoys from many countries, went to the Lateran to attend the Summit of Nations. Evangelista XI proposed the &quot;Lateran Proposition&quot; at this meeting, aiming to enable the nations to obtain mutual guarantees of security.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_OP_LATERANO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>On September 29, 1099, the Lateran &quot;He&quot; detected the impending crisis &quot;disaster&quot;, activated the emergency response mechanism to alert the Pope and output a list of qualified people. The Pope canonized the people on the list as &quot;saints&quot; to deal with this crisis.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Plastic Heart</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Arturo Giallo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You stepped into a nightmare. [NEWLINE]In the nightmare, you couldn't make any sound from your throat, and you couldn't see other people's faces. But you heard a familiar voice, warm and bright, like a nursery rhyme from long ago. [NEWLINE]&quot;Arturo, Arturo? Are you feeling better? [NEWLINE]&quot;Are you still feeling bad? Can you tell your mother about your nightmare last night? [NEWLINE]&quot;Arturo, don't be afraid. [NEWLINE]&quot;Don't be afraid of not being able to make any sound from your throat, and don't be afraid of not being able to see other people's faces. [NEWLINE]&quot;Arturo, come, come to your mother. [NEWLINE]&quot;Look, this is a cello. Mom will teach you.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The bow was placed on the strings, playing a silent rain, you know it was rain because the raindrops fell on your face. [NEWLINE]It hurts, it burns, you look for the nursery rhyme, where is she? [NEWLINE]You are pushed, everyone is wearing a veil, they are all far away, but there is a hand strangling your arm. [NEWLINE]&quot;Arturo Giallo, don't be sad.&quot; [NEWLINE]&quot;Your father doesn't blame you, he just can't accept it for a while. [NEWLINE]&quot;Your mother left you this pair of gloves, she hopes you can wear them. [NEWLINE]&quot;If you can't control your music, you will need someone else to control you. Start with these gloves. [NEWLINE]&quot;This is not a punishment, Arturo, this is to protect others, to protect the people around you, to protect the people close to you. [NEWLINE]&quot;Don't hurt them anymore, Arturo.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The silhouette melted into the inky rain, and the burning raindrops merged into an inky sun. [NEWLINE]It hangs over your head, and its black light blinds you. [NEWLINE]&quot;You came too late, Arturo.&quot; [NEWLINE]&quot;You didn't get to see your teacher for the last time, and you didn't get to say goodbye to him properly. [NEWLINE]&quot;You foresaw his death, didn't you? [NEWLINE]&quot;When you knew he had played under that tall tower, his death was already doomed. [NEWLINE]&quot;Unfortunately, even for Emmanuel, fighting against fate still ended up like this. [NEWLINE]&quot;You? What can you do about it? [NEWLINE]&quot;You can't do anything, Arturo.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The inky sun sank. It plunged into the ocean of people without hesitation. [NEWLINE]The noisy ocean finally condensed into a tear, which passed across your cheek and fell into your heart. [NEWLINE]You heard that voice. [NEWLINE]&quot;Don't be afraid, Arturo.&quot; [NEWLINE]The music stopped at this moment.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;I'm sorry, I didn't notice you were here. I only practiced this new piece of music when I was alone. I'm sorry to bother you, but I'm not very good at it yet. [NEWLINE] &quot;In fact, this piece of music is not yet finished. The inspiration for creating it just came to me. This kind of composition method is very new and difficult for me. There has never been such a piece of music created on this earth. [NEWLINE] &quot;So I can guarantee that every part of the music comes from the heart. It is my own melody. [NEWLINE] &quot;But I have already thought of the name of this piece of music. [NEWLINE] &quot;Its name is 'Plastic Heart'.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FEDERICO_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Federico Giallo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FEDERICO_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Federico Giallo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FEDERICO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When we mention the title of &quot;saint&quot;, we may think of the saints of the Iberian Inquisition. Although it was originally just a respectful title taken from the Lateran Church, the title of &quot;saint&quot; has now been digested by Iberia and is well known to the Iberians, becoming a manifestation of their own unique culture.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FEDERICO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>For the Lateran people, &quot;saint&quot; is not a simple and casual title. In all the books related to the history of Lateran, there are records about the first generation of saints who built stone towers and established the holy city. This first group of Sakota led everyone to establish the foundation of Lateran, and after generations of efforts, peace continued for a thousand years. This is how we finally have the Lateran that is far away from the smoke of war and is peaceful.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FEDERICO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Apart from the first group of sages who founded the city-state, only each pope will be canonized as a saint during his tenure. This is not only an honor, but also represents the responsibility of leading all Sakota and the entire Lateran City. For thousands of years, the title of &quot;saint&quot; has been passed down from generation to generation among successive popes without exception - and this tradition that has lasted for thousands of years was broken by the decision of Evangelista XI.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FEDERICO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Federico Giallo became the first person other than the Pope to be elected in the past thousand years. Why was he chosen so unexpectedly? The undertaker was indeed an excellent executor, there was no doubt about that, but the Lateran was not without fighters who were more brave and skilled than him, nor were there any believers who were more devout than him, and there were also many prestigious figures. Everyone had the same question - why Federico? Why a &quot;saint&quot;?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FEDERICO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although the outstanding performance of the undertaker himself, his seemingly completely unaffected calm attitude, and the unique atmosphere of the Lateran reduced the shocking degree of this incident, it cannot be denied that the decision of His Holiness the Pope was completely unreasonable and shocking.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FEDERICO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Why did this wise current pope make such a decision, and what kind of signal did he send? Operator Undertaker told us that the pope once mentioned that a disaster would befall the earth, but what kind of disaster could make the holy city of Lateran, which has been peaceful for a thousand years, take such urgent measures?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ARCHETTO_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hildegard Empty Strings</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ARCHETTO_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hildegard Empty Strings</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ARCHETTO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During her years of travel, Hildegard had visited many city-states on the Terra continent and witnessed various wonders. One day, Hildegard accidentally passed by a small village in Ursus that was almost isolated from the outside world. The residents here never cared about tomorrow and faith, and worked all day just to have a full meal. But here, there was a little girl who knew the past of the Langdon Guard and remembered the teachings of Pope Lateran. It was because her grandfather had fought side by side with the Langdon Guard in his early years. Although the personal experience became a memory of the past, and the memories of the past were simplified into the little girl's bedtime story, her belief in salvation has never changed. In the eyes of the little girl, Hildegard's arrival further confirmed the promise of salvation in the prophecy and teachings. So in that cruel winter, the little girl, on her deathbed, used her most precious and only glass bead as a reward to hire Hildegard to hold a Lateran funeral for her...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ARCHETTO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hildegard prayed quietly for the girl, as the Lateran teachings state: &quot;When the earth passes away, desire also passes away. But he who does the will and the purpose lives forever.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ARCHETTO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Since embarking on the journey, Xidejia has been collecting many stories, traces and even legends left by Langdon Monastery and the guards on this continent, and sorted them out in a notebook. It contains not only the ancient medals purchased from a down-and-out vagrant, but also the strange bedtime stories of the Langdon Guards by the Sarkaz, and even a copy of a taste review of the tumor milk bread by a food critic from Da Yan.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ARCHETTO_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sildenafil was so optimistic, although she had imagined several possibilities for the Langdon Monastery more than once, whether it was forced to close due to poor management, or was destroyed in the war in the chaotic disputes of Terra, the worst thing was that the meaning and function it represented were no longer needed by the world or even Lateran. But even with such worries, even with repeated disappointments and helplessness, she never stopped.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FIAMMETTA_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fiametta</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FIAMMETTA_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fiametta</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FIAMMETTA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Based on the few rare mentions of the Fall of Angels by Fiametta, as well as the clues we have obtained from other channels, the overall picture of that mission can now be roughly outlined.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FIAMMETTA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The special task force that Fiammetta belonged to was assigned by the Pope's Office to carry out a clearing mission to eliminate a group of Sarkaz robbers who had attacked the Sakota caravan many times. The tactical team composed of four elite Lateran soldiers should have easily achieved their intended goal. They followed the traces left by the gang and tracked them all the way to a collapsed ruin around Kazdel. The robbers obviously used this ruin as a bunker, or a defensive fortification. However, the team did not find the enemy in the ruins. The scene here was much weirder and more complicated than they expected. There were a large number of corpses with different degrees of weathering piled up in the ruins. They gathered in front of a closed door. These people seemed to come for something, but none of them found the answer they wanted. The owners of these corpses were of different races, ages, and even eras. The only thing in common was that, in the words of Fiammetta, &quot;they were stuck in their own time.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_FIAMMETTA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There is no accurate and reliable report of what happened afterwards. Fiammetta said that he left the scene at that time because of a false support communication that was later determined to be a gang trap, and did not witness the moment of the incident. As far as we know, after that, one of the team members, Remian, was hospitalized until now, and team member Mostima left Lateran due to the fall of the angel, and team member Fiammetta left later. It is believed that the team leader at that time was a Sakota named Andorn, and now his information does not exist in any official Lateran documents.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_LATERAN_PONTIFICA_COHORS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>An official Lateran organization responsible for multiple tasks including city patrols and combat, using standard axe guns that are uniformly distributed.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_LATERAN_BASILICA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Summit of Nations was held here. Under the cathedral is the burial place of the saints of the Lateran, a stele recording the great achievements of the popes of all ages, and the tomb of the oldest saint of the Lateran. &quot;He of the Lateran&quot; is also in the deepest part of the cathedral.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_REVELATION_TOWER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The landmark building of Lateran is believed to have been built by the first saints themselves. The city of Lateran was founded here a thousand years ago. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When Cecilia sang on the stone tower, the stone tower bell rang once a thousand years.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I can feel the stiffness in your fingers. It seems that you are not used to this kind of relationship. Don't be nervous. I will take you along...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If you want to be my friend, you're not going to be able to do that.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Even without the connection of piano music, you still understand me more and more. But how can I share the joy in my heart with you?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You are indeed the one who understands my heart the most...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How can I convey my feelings to you?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>War itself is not worth playing. But I will listen to every voice on the battlefield, whether they come from heroes or refugees.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I am not interested in means of hurting others, but you are a temptation that I cannot refuse.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The music ends and the audience disperses. How long does the vibration of the strings continue after the performance ends?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>No matter how strong the mind is, it cannot conquer the doomed demise. But since you have conquered me, I expect you to behave differently.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I will prepare a unique concert for them.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I've heard enough of the noise...can you please leave me alone for a while?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>They can't play the same music as me, but they are just as skilled and I hope you will like them.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I will not stop playing even if you ask me to. Trauma is one thing, freedom is another. My life, like all other lives, will end if it stops.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Will you also refuse to listen to…the truest voice of your heart? [NEWLINE] (Condemn you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Arturo, sinner of the Lateran, saint of the later days, guest of honor of the nobles of Leitania. I should have introduced myself with music. Unfortunately, it may be a little rude to play for you rashly, so please forgive my tedious self-introduction.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Maybe we should be a little closer to each other, what do you think?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This way, the distance between us will be further brought closer.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Want to know where I live these days? I can tell you. But you have to tell me, too.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The strings are vibrating…for you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Follow your heart, let me play them...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_REASON_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(You have higher faith and culture output.)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I refuse to play for you, or even listen to the earthly music within you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_REASON_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Your Culture and Faith output is low.)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>No one has ever been as present in my music and thoughts as you have been in my life. So why don't you take my hand and let's go forward together?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rather than war, I would rather play the cloud passing by in the sky.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You haven't satisfied me yet...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't you think it's time to stop this ridiculous show?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Be careful, I don't want your troops getting lost in the music as they pass by.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sorry, they are so loud.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Please don't get me wrong, we are just passing by.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your army's voice does not appeal to me as much as you do to me, please let them go.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The strings are vibrating…in gratitude to you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_OP_VIRTUOSA_LTRN_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Noise) What a shame.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
