<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Fri Oct 18 13:38:33 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_OP_TEMPESTA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>hurricane</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_OP_TEMPESTA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>hurricane</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_OP_TEMPESTA_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hurricane</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_OP_PEMBROKE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pembroke</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Royal Wealth</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The mysterious, lovely and charming royal wealth is now in front of you! ...Oops? Startled? Don't worry, don't worry~ So where are we going next? The legendary coast where treasures are buried? Or the reefs full of wreckage? No matter where, let's hoist the sail and set off~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pirates also have their own rules. Without rules, people’s hearts cannot be united.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Golden Deer</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I caught you~ So, what do you want to know from the Golden Deer? Is it my name, eternal existence, or these cute tentacles~? Oh my, my tentacles have reached the end of the world... Oh~ It seems that there is no end of the world♪ Whatever~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I'm starting to get agitated and uneasy~</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_ON_STRANGER_TIDES_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Strange Tides</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_ON_STRANGER_TIDES_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Initially unlocks {LOC_TECH_CELESTIAL_NAVIGATION_NAME}, and builds port buildings with [ICON_PRODUCTION] +100% productivity. [NEWLINE]Units can enter ocean cells early, and units in water gain +2 [ICON_MOVEMENT] movement at the start of the turn. [NEWLINE]Water cells with storms will gain random output. Units are immune to hurricanes, and hurricanes will occur more frequently.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_BLACK_BART_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Black Baronet</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_BLACK_BART_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Naval units automatically form [ICON_CORPS] fleets/ [ICON_ARMY] armadas when they are promoted to the 2nd/4th time [ICON_PROMOTION]. [NEWLINE]All naval units can perform coastal plundering, and units are rewarded with a large amount of experience points for any plundering. [NEWLINE]After the first port area is built, plundering is strengthened, and coastal plundering does not consume [ICON_MOVEMENT] movement.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_GRACE_OF_THE_SEA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Blessing of the Sea</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_GRACE_OF_THE_SEA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hurricanes double the output of civilization traits. [NEWLINE]Naval units can travel through any of your ports or coastal cities. [NEWLINE]All regions gain the standard adjacency bonus from adjacent coastal or lake tiles. Land regions adjacent to a coast provide +2 output of their own type to all water tiles in that city.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ROYAL_PORT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Port Royal</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_ROYAL_PORT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A Hurricane civilization district that replaces a port and costs less to build. [NEWLINE]This city can build one additional district. Triggers a cultural bomb on neutral territory. [NEWLINE]Each building built gives +100% adjacency bonus. [NEWLINE]If this city has a governor, its infrastructure is immune to natural disasters.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_NAVIGATION_HOME_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sailing Home</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_NAVIGATION_HOME_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Unique building for the Cyclone civilization. Does not replace any buildings. Unlocked in &quot;{LOC_CIVIC_NAVAL_TRADITION_NAME}&quot;. [NEWLINE]Gives an [ICON_GOVERNOR] Governor title. Naval units produced by this city gain +60% experience. [NEWLINE]When built, this port district will provide [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture equal to the adjacent bonus.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SHIP_OF_LINE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sailing Ship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_SHIP_OF_LINE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A unique naval unit of the Hurricane civilization, capable of coastal plundering. It cannot be produced and is only given when a port is built. [NEWLINE]After killing a unit, it has a chance to be captured. After having 1 [ICON_PROMOTION] promotion, it can build a city once in a valid coastal cell. [NEWLINE]After building all levels of buildings in the port for the first time, its [ICON_STRENGTH] combat strength is +15.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODFEAT_GOLDENHIND_ADJACENCY_YIELD_GOLD" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Amount} [ICON_GOLD] Gold from a neighboring coast or lake ({LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_GRACE_OF_THE_SEA_NAME})</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODFEAT_GOLDENHIND_ADJACENCY_YIELD_FAITH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Amount} [ICON_FAITH] Faith from a neighboring coast or lake ({LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_GRACE_OF_THE_SEA_NAME})</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODFEAT_GOLDENHIND_ADJACENCY_YIELD_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Amount} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from an adjacent coast or lake ({LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_GRACE_OF_THE_SEA_NAME})</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODFEAT_GOLDENHIND_ADJACENCY_YIELD_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Amount} [ICON_SCIENCE] Science from adjacent coast or lake ({LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_GRACE_OF_THE_SEA_NAME})</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODFEAT_GOLDENHIND_ADJACENCY_YIELD_FOOD" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Amount} [ICON_FOOD] Food from a neighboring coast or lake ({LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_GRACE_OF_THE_SEA_NAME})</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_MODFEAT_GOLDENHIND_ADJACENCY_YIELD_PRODUCTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_Amount} [ICON_PRODUCTION] Productivity from adjacent coast or lake ({LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_GRACE_OF_THE_SEA_NAME})</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_NAVIGATION_HOME_EXP_BONUS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pirate Discipline</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_NAVIGATION_HOME_EXP_BONUS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+60% combat experience ({LOC_BUILDING_NAVIGATION_HOME_NAME})</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_SHIP_OF_LINE_CAPTURE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hijacking a ship</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_ABILITY_SHIP_OF_LINE_CAPTURE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After defeating the enemy, there is a chance to capture him</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNITOPERATION_GOLDEN_HIND_TRANSPORT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tidal Wave</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The end of the golden age</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Committed to conquering all coasts of the open ocean, likes civilizations with strong navies, and dislikes civilizations that do not develop their navies.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Drake Legend</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Enjoys using navies to explore the world, and likes civilizations that do the same.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Royal Fortune</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bartholomew Roberts</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bartholomew Roberts (May 17, 1682 - February 10, 1722), originally named John Roberts or John Robert, was a famous Welsh pirate. He was also known as the &quot;Black Bart&quot; because of his handsome appearance and gentle manner. [NEWLINE] Roberts was the most successful and legendary pirate in history. He was tall, handsome, never drank, and always dressed gorgeously. He was well versed in the intimidation of pirates and had superb sailing skills. He enjoyed a high reputation among his fleet crew. Although he was not the last pirate of that era, his death marked the end of the &quot;Golden Age&quot; of piracy. Bartholomew Roberts's pirate career was short and violent, unmatched by any other pirate. His motto was &quot;A merry life and a short life.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Born John Robert in 1682 in a small village on the coast of Pembrokeshire, Wales, he began working at sea in 1695 (at the age of 13). It is unknown when he changed his name to Bartholomew or why he added an &quot;s&quot; to his second name. However, there is no record of him in any historical documents, and nothing is known about his life after that until 1718, when it is recorded that he was a crew member on a sloop in Barbados. [NEWLINE] In 1719, Roberts served as third mate on the &quot;Prince&quot;, whose fleet was mainly engaged in the slave trade. In 1719, the ship was intercepted by Howell Davis while trading slaves in Arnold Barb. Roberts joined Davis' pirate group. As both were Welshmen, and Roberts was smart and capable, Roberts soon became Davis' right-hand man. However, soon after Roberts joined, Davis was killed in the Gulf of Guinea in Africa. Roberts was then elected captain and led the pirate group. At this time, it had been less than six weeks since he joined the pirate group.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Roberts, the captain, earned the nickname &quot;Black Bart&quot; in his first action. One day, under the cover of tropical darkness, he led his men back to Principe Island in the Gulf of Guinea, massacred many men on the island, and robbed all valuables. A few days later, he captured a Dutch Guinea merchant ship, and two days later he plundered a passing British ship. Then, the pirates returned to Ano Bab to replenish fresh water and supplies, and voted on whether to go to the Indian Ocean and the East Indies or Brazil next. The final decision was to go to Brazil. [NEWLINE] Their expedition on the other side of the Atlantic proved to be a great success, but Roberts also suffered some setbacks. After about two months of cruising the coast of Brazil, Roberts and his second-in-command, Walter Kennedy of the Rover, were about to abandon their search and head for the West Indies when, crossing the great bay of Los Tortos dos Santos, they encountered a Portuguese fleet of 42 galleys, escorted by two 70-gun warships, about to sail for Lisbon. Roberts quickly seized the nearest ships, and at swordpoint, the captain pointed out the vessel in the fleet that contained the most treasure. With 40 guns and a crew of over 150 men, it was not an easy task to capture, but the pirates did not care. Roberts and his men boarded the ship and found that the hold was filled with 40,000 gold coins and a large number of rare treasures, some of which were specially designed for the King of Portugal. Now, the pirates wanted to take some time to divide the spoils, so Roberts sailed to Devil's Island. On the jutting stretch of coast from Los Tortos dos Santos to Brazil lies one of the most notorious pirate hideouts, filled with the scum of society who would offer any service to sailors who could afford them gold. [NEWLINE]After a few weeks of rest and pleasure, and with most of the sailors having spent their money, the two ships sailed to the mouth of the Suriname River, where they spotted a schooner. Roberts pursued in a fast sloop, while Walter Kennedy waited in the Wanderer. The target ship escaped, and Roberts found himself sailing against the wind, so he returned more than a week later to find Kennedy and the Wanderer's crew gone, along with any remaining loot. But Roberts shrugged off the disaster - after all, they had already squandered most of their money. As if to highlight the incident, he renamed his sloop the Fortune and negotiated a new set of pirate articles with his remaining crew to prevent a similar incident from happening again—the most detailed set of such articles in existence. [NEWLINE] Roberts sailed north in the Fortune, skirting the edge of the Lesser Antilles and hijacking several ships along the way. In February 1720, French pirate Montigny La Paise joined in the piracy spree in the sloop Sea King. They encountered two British naval ships off Barbados. The Sea King's rigging was badly damaged, and La Paise was routed. The Fortune was also damaged, and several crew members were killed or wounded. Roberts broke his promise and attempted to escape, but he had to avoid two French naval ships that were pursuing him from Martinique. From then on, he vowed revenge on the people of Barbados and Martinique, and flew a pirate flag with ABH and AMH under his feet to vent his hatred. [NEWLINE]After quietly repairing his ships in Saint-Domingue, Roberts continued northward, and in early 1720 he sold the captured ships and cargo in New England. Then he sailed into the Newfoundland fishing grounds in search of prey, seizing more than 170 ships. He traded his booty for a French ship, equipped her with 28 naval guns, and renamed her the &quot;Royal Fortune&quot;, which also translates as &quot;Royal Fortune&quot;. He returned to the American coast and captured more ships. Later, when he went to sea again in the summer, it was the Caribbean that suffered, and he successively seized 15 ships from France, Britain and the Netherlands. That September, he launched a brutal six-month campaign throughout the Leeward Islands, raiding St. Kitts and Martinique, plundering at least a hundred ships. One of them was a 52-gun warship carrying the French governor of Martinique. Roberts hanged him from the yardarm of his own ship, then beat and murdered most of the crew. He plundered the ship as his new flagship, naming it the Royal Fortune—a name he used for several ships. [NEWLINE] In just two and a half years, Roberts and his fleet plundered more than 470 ships.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_ROYAL_FORTUNE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In April 1721, Bartholomew Roberts crossed the Atlantic to West Africa and arrived near the mouth of the Senegal River in early June. There, he was pursued by two French ships, but due to their backward weapons and equipment, they were quickly captured by Roberts, who renamed the two ships &quot;Ranger&quot; and &quot;Lite Ranger&quot;. At this time, Roberts sailed to Sierra Leone and captured a large slave ship and the fast sailing ship &quot;Onslow&quot; on the way, which was transporting soldiers to Cape Coast Castle on the Gold Coast. Some soldiers on the ship chose to switch to piracy, but it turned out that ordinary sailors could not compare with the social status of sailors. These novices could only get a quarter of their normal share of the spoils. Roberts renamed the &quot;Onslow&quot; as the fourth ship &quot;Royal Fortune&quot;. [NEWLINE]The plundering spree finally came to an end on February 10, 1722, when the British Royal Navy ship Swallow caught up with the pirates near Cape Lopez, in modern-day Gabon. The Royal Fortune and the Little Ranger were stranded due to their list, but the Swallow's men, under Captain Chaloner Ogle, encountered the Ranger under the command of James Skyre and immediately surrounded him. [NEWLINE]Skyre's leg was blown off by a cannonball, and 10 of his men were killed. Skyre eventually surrendered, and the surviving crew were taken prisoner. [NEWLINE]In the days between the preliminary operations and the main battle, Roberts salvaged a few other ships and plundered another ship before returning to port to rest. Most of the pirates were drunk from the night's drinking. At dawn, the Swallow came into view near the beach. At first, everyone who saw her thought it was Skumm returning on the Ranger, so Ogle was able to strike first and defeat Roberts. [NEWLINE]Once he realized the danger was coming, Roberts immediately prepared for battle and changed into his iconic costume. Johnson (author of A General History of Pirates) described him as &quot;Roberts dressed in gorgeous clothes, holding a sword and two guns hanging from his shoulders.&quot; The pirate captain ordered his ship to sail towards Ogle's ship, hoping to pass him, get into the high seas and escape. However, as the two ships passed each other, the Swallow fired a shotgun from the side at close range, hitting Roberts and blowing his throat, killing the pirate captain instantly. Legend has it that his helmsman, a tough man who killed people, completely ignored the bullets around him and cried like a child while holding his body. The crew knew that his last wish was to be buried at sea to prevent his body from being captured, so the crew closest to him threw his body into the sea. [NEWLINE]After about three hours of fierce boarding battle, the remaining pirates surrendered. The three captured pirate ships were loaded with gold dust worth more than 14,000 pounds. In this way, the largest pirate trial and execution of that era was held in Cape Coast Castle, the British slave trading center in West Africa. 54 pirates were hanged, 37 were sentenced to labor, the rest were acquitted, and 70 African pirates were sold into slavery.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Golden Deer</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Francis Drake</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Golden Hind, formerly known as the Pelican, was a three-masted galleon. Between 1577 and 1579, it served as the flagship of the legendary British explorer and famous pirate Drake, completing the most famous circumnavigation in the history of world navigation. It was later placed in a shipyard in London for public display until 1650, when the ship was dismantled and its remaining intact parts were made into furniture and preserved in various parts of the UK. One of the tables made from the remaining parts of the Golden Hind is now preserved in the library of Oxford University in the UK for future generations to remember.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Golden Hind was a large sailing ship that Francis Drake captained during his voyage around the world between 1577 and 1580. Originally known as the Pelican, it was renamed in 1578 by Sir Christopher Hatton, one of Drake's main sponsors, as a gesture of gratitude for his sponsorship. A full-scale, seaworthy reconstruction is currently underway in London on the south bank of the River Thames.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Queen Elizabeth I provided partial sponsorship to Sir Francis Drake as leader of an expedition that aimed to circumnavigate South America through the Strait of Magellan and explore further coasts. The Queen's support gave Drake official approval, which was beneficial to himself and the Queen and disadvantageous to Spain. This eventually led to the Anglo-Spanish War. Before setting sail, Drake met the Queen for the first time, and the Queen told him, &quot;We will gladly avenge the King of Spain for the injuries sustained by the divers.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The stated aim was to &quot;find out places where ships could pass (that is, passages)&quot;. However, with the informal support of Elizabeth, Drake's Golden Hind became, in effect, a privateer. The design of the Golden Hind was based on the Spanish-built Victoria, the first ship to circumnavigate the globe, described as &quot;a warship in the transition from sail to galleon in the mid-16th century&quot;, weighing about 120 tons. He initially named his flagship the &quot;Pelican&quot;, but renamed it the &quot;Golden Red Stag&quot; when he reached the Strait of Magellan on 20 August 1578, in honour of his patron Sir Christopher Hatton, whose family crest was a golden red deer. He set sail in December 1577 with five smaller ships carrying 164 men, and arrived off the coast of Brazil in early 1578.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>On 1 March 1579, in the Pacific Ocean off the coast of Ecuador, the Golden Hind bombarded and captured the Spanish galleon Nuestra Señora de la Concepción. The galleon contained the largest treasure ever seized by the British: more than 360,000 pesos (equivalent to about £480 million in 2017 purchasing power). The treasure took six days to transfer and included 26 tons of silver, half a ton of gold, porcelain, jewels, coins and jewelry.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>On September 26, 1580, Francis Drake sailed his ship into Plymouth Harbor with only 56 of his 80-man crew remaining on board. The ship was unloaded at nearby Trematon Castle under the supervision of the Queen's Guard. The final treasure also included six tons of cloves from the Spice Islands, which were worth their weight in gold at the time. Elizabeth herself boarded the Golden Hind, which was then based at Deptford on the south bank of the Thames and had requested that it be permanently exhibited as the first &quot;museum ship.&quot; There, she shrewdly asked the French ambassador to grant Drake a knighthood. More than half of the proceeds went to the crown, and the queen's share of the treasure amounted to at least £160,000: &quot;enough to pay her entire government debt, and £40,000 left to invest in a new trading company in the Levant. The return she and other investors had made was more than £47 on every £1 invested, or 4,700%.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After Drake's circumnavigation, the Golden Hind was put on public display at the shipyard at Deptford, London. It remained there from 1580 until around 1650, 45 years after Elizabeth's death, when the ship eventually decayed and broke up. In 1668, the keeper of the Deptford store, John Davis of Camberwell, took the best remaining golden wood and made it into a chair, now known as the Drake Chair, which was presented to the Bodleian Library at Oxford (a replica is now in the Great Hall at Buckland Abbey, Devon, and is now maintained by the National Trust). A table in the Great Hall of the Middle Temple in London, also known as a cupboard, is said to have been made from the planks of the Golden Hind. On the cupboard was placed a scroll of the members of the Inns of Court, on which new members would sign when they were called to the bar. The original ship's lantern was also used to hang over the porch of the Hall of the Inns of Court in the Middle Temple, but was destroyed during World War II.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>After the original Golden Hind was demolished, restoration work began, and at the earliest, at the recommendation of Agatha Christie, a replica of the Golden Hind became part of a children's playground at the 1924 British Empire Exhibition, and its whereabouts are unknown. A replica of the Golden Hind was later built at Peter Pan Playground (now Adventure Island Adventure Park) in Southend, Essex. It was built in 1947 and opened in 1949 with the wax museum. By 1992, declining attendance, coupled with rising maintenance costs and the need for major renovations to the wooden structure, led to its closure in 1997. It was replaced by Blackbeard's replica of Queen Anne's Revenge, which was demolished in 2013.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A replica of the Golden Hind has been permanently moored in the harbour at Brixham Harbour, Devon (GB-TOB 50°23′48″N 3°30′46″W) since 1963, after it was used in the television series Sir Francis Drake, which was filmed in and around Torbay Bay and Dartmouth Bay. The film studios built the replica using a fishing boat converted at a cost of £25,000, without a back porch or gun emplacements. In 1987, the ship sank in heavy seas while being towed to Dartmouth for repairs. A second full-scale replica was completed in 1988 and is visited by thousands of visitors each year. The vessel was built on the basis of a steel barge and has no sailing capability.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_OP_GOLDEN_HIND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In order to reproduce the Golden Hind more realistically, a full-scale reconstruction using traditional methods was built in Appledore, Devon, and launched in 1973. The Golden Hind was the result of three years of research and construction. Since then, she has traveled more than 140,000 miles. In late 1974, she set out on her maiden voyage from Plymouth, arriving in San Francisco on May 8, 1975. In 1979, she went to Japan to film the mini-series Shōgun, after which she completed her circumnavigation of the world and returned to the UK. From 1981 to 1984, she was moored in the UK and became an educational museum. In 1984-1985, she sailed around the British Isles, then crossed the Atlantic to St. Thomas in the Caribbean. In 1986, she sailed through the Panama Canal to Vancouver, becoming the star of the &quot;Seaside Plaza&quot; exhibition at the 1986 World Expo. In 1987, she began a tour of American coastal cities, spending two years on the Pacific coast. In late 1988 she returned via the Panama Canal and continued to visit ports in the Gulf of Mexico and on the East Coast. In 1992 she returned to the UK and spent the next four years visiting ports in Europe. Since 1996 she has been moored at St Mary's Dock, Bankside, Southwark, London, where she is open to the public and hosts a range of educational programmes.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
