<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Sun Jun 23 14:44:21 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_CEYLON_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ceylon</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_CEYLON_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I have been with Hei since I was a child, and I know everything about her, including her experiences before she came to me. Ah, but I can't tell you this easily.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_LAKESIDE_RAMBLER_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lakeside Walker</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_LAKESIDE_RAMBLER_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Each unique district built gives +3 [ICON_HOUSING] Housing, +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to lake and coastal tiles.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_SIESTA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seastar</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_SIESTA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seastar</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_SIESTA_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seastar</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_SIESTA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seastar</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_RHAPSODY_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seastar Rhapsody</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_RHAPSODY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gain 500% more [ICON_GREATMUSICIAN] Great Musician Points, Great Music Works provide an additional +4 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +4 [ICON_FAITH] Faith, +4 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +4 [ICON_SCIENCE] Science, and [ICON_GREATWORK_MUSIC] Great Music Works provide 400% more [ICON_TOURISM] Travel. The Palace provides 5 Great Works slots.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_DISTRICT_MUSIC_HALL_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seastar Music Hall</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_DISTRICT_MUSIC_HALL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A special area</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_BUILDING_RAP_VENUE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rap venues</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_BUILDING_RAP_VENUE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A distinctive building</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_BUILDING_ELECTRONIC_MUSIC_VENUE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Electronic music venues</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_BUILDING_ELECTRONIC_MUSIC_VENUE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A distinctive building</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_BUILDING_HEAVY_METAL_VENUE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Heavy Metal Venues</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_BUILDING_HEAVY_METAL_VENUE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A distinctive building</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_POMPEY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pompeii</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_YEDAO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Night Sword</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_XUNLINZHE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ranger</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_HEIJIAO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Black Corner</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_DULIN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dulin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_FEN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Finn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_MIGELU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Beagle</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_FURONG" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hibiscus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_KELUOSI" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cross</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_MEILANSHA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Roseland</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_KATI" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Katie</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_ANDEQIEER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Anderchel</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_SHIDUHUADE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stewart</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_ZILAN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zilan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_YUEJIANYE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Moon night</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_KONGBAO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Airstrike</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_NAME_PAOPUKA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Popka</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_CEYLON" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ceylon is the daughter of the mayor of Xiosta. She was sent to Victoria to study since she was young, which allowed her to be exposed to the most advanced science and technology. The long-term study abroad life has made her develop a very independent character, so she is somewhat different from the image of &quot;rich children&quot; in everyone's impression. In Ceylon's past life, everything was logically moving towards success. In her mind, she still has no correct understanding of words such as setbacks and failures. This sense of self-confidence cultivated by countless successes is reflected in her words and deeds all the time, because most of the time, she is always right, and if she is wrong, she will never be stingy with &quot;sorry&quot;. Of course, for Ceylon, the opinions of others are irrelevant. In her eyes, there is always only the future and the people she cherishes.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MUSIC_HALL_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seastar Music Hall</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_MUSIC_HALL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xiosta Cultural Heritage Area replaces the Theater Square Area, and requires half the production capacity. Gain 1 [ICON_GREATWRITER] Great Writer Point, gain 3 [ICON_GREATMUSICIAN] Great Musician Points, Xiosta Music Hall provides [ICON_FAITH] Faith equal to the Culture Value Bonus. Each adjacent area gains the standard Culture Value bonus, and each adjacent Wonder, Coast, and Lake gains double the Culture Value bonus. Citizens provide additional [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold Coin bonus.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_DISTRICT_COAST_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture comes from adjacent lake or coast {1_NUM : plural 1?cells; other?cells;}.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_RAP_VENUE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rap venues</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_RAP_VENUE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xiosta unique building, replaces the Roman Theatre, +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, 1 [ICON_GREATWRITER] Great Writer point, 3 [ICON_GREATMUSICIAN] Great Musician points, and provides 2 Great Works slots.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ELECTRONIC_MUSIC_VENUE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Electronic music venues</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_ELECTRONIC_MUSIC_VENUE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A Seastar unique building that replaces the Art Gallery, grants +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, 1 [ICON_GREATWRITER] Great Writer point, 3 [ICON_GREATMUSICIAN] Great Musician points, and 3 Great Works slots. Cannot be built if there is already a heavy metal venue in the Seastar Music Hall area.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_HEAVY_METAL_VENUE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Heavy Metal Venues</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_HEAVY_METAL_VENUE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A Xiosta unique building that replaces the Archaeological Museum. It provides +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, 1 [ICON_GREATWRITER] Great Writer, 3 [ICON_GREATMUSICIAN] Great Musician, and 2 Great Works. Upon completion, it grants a Rock Band. It cannot be built if there is already a music venue in the Xiosta Music Hall area.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_SIESTA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The mayor of the independent city-state of Xiosta and the father of Operator Ceylon, he runs the independent city-state of Xiosta from the place where his wife Barbara rests forever. He developed Xiosta into a vibrant new city. His confidant Kronin has been running Xiosta with Herman for fifteen years. During this Obsidian Festival, Herman pretended to leave Xiosta and left Black to investigate Kronin. In the end, the crisis was avoided with the help of Rhodes Island. Herman agreed that his daughter Ceylon would go to Rhodes Island to take up the office accompanied by Black. At the same time, he also announced that Xiosta City, which is near the volcano, would be gradually moved.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_AMIYA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ceylon is a graduate of the Originium Research Program at the National University of Victoria. Operator Ceylon is the daughter of the mayor of Xiosta City. She was sent to Victoria to study since she was a child, which allowed her to be exposed to the most advanced science and technology. The long-term study abroad life has made her develop a very independent character, so it is somewhat different from the image of &quot;rich children&quot; in everyone's impression. In Ceylon's past life, everything was logically moving towards success. In her mind, she still has no correct understanding of words such as setbacks and failures. This sense of self-confidence cultivated by countless successes is reflected in her words and deeds all the time, because most of the time, she is always right, and if she is wrong, she will never be stingy with &quot;sorry&quot;. Of course, for Ceylon, the opinions of others are irrelevant. In her eyes, there is always only the future and the people she cherishes.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_MUSIC_HALL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The venue for the Seastar Music Festival.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_RAP_VENUE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The venue built by &quot;Emperor&quot;. Codenamed &quot;Emperor&quot;, real name unknown. In the second phase of SIDE STORY event &quot;Heart of Fire and Blue&quot;, he participated in the Obsidian Festival-Most Anticipated Artist Voting Event as a rapper. His real identity is a record producer under Siren Records, a veteran Columbia rap star, and an entrepreneur. His rap stage name is &quot;The Great Emperor&quot;.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_ELECTRONIC_MUSIC_VENUE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The venue established by &quot;D.D.D.&quot;. His stage name is &quot;D.D.D.&quot;, and his full name is &quot;Destructive Dragon Demon&quot;. He participated in the second phase of SIDE STORY's &quot;Heart of Fire and Blue&quot; Obsidian Festival as an electronic music DJ.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_HEAVY_METAL_VENUE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The venue was built by &quot;AUS&quot;. The band Sunset is abbreviated as AUS, a famous heavy metal band, but the identity of its members is very mysterious. After being ignored in the early days, the band was signed by Siren Records and released its first album &quot;Dark Sea&quot;, which was well received as soon as it came out, establishing the band's position in the heavy metal field. The songs in the album do not contain any swear words, which changed the style of other heavy metal bands of the same period whose works were not accepted by the public.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
