<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Automatically translated with the help of google translate.-->
<!-- Fri Mar 22 21:59:55 2024-->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokqiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Conference of Kedokya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_DESCRIPTION_JFD_CIVILIZATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Conference of Kedokya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokqiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_KHJY_BINOMIAL_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kechaqiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JSYS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Strong warrior</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JSYS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[Military Tradition] is unlocked, has a unique promotion tree and initially has level 1 [ICON_Promotion] promotion, +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power when escorting. . [NEWLINE] After construction, -1 [ICON_Citizen] population, enjoy the title of Governor [Magnus] [Supply Guarantee], and will be eliminated with the unlocking of [Military Science].</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JMQS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Death Knight</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_UNIT_JMQS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[Military Science] Unlocked, expensive special cavalry that must be purchased with gold coins. Fight anti-cavalry units without being suppressed, move quickly, have a unique promotion tree and gain double the experience points. [NEWLINE] The escorted unit gains the same [ICON_Movement] movement ability, +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power when escorted [NEWLINE] is eliminated as [Internal Combustion Engine] is unlocked</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_UNIT_ABILITY_SEFE_UNIT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} Hero</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_UNIT_ABILITY_JMQS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Experience gained doubled</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GID_RELIGIOUS_UNIT_SPREAD_CHARGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} Number of missions</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GID_RELIGIOUS_UNIT_CONVERT_BARBS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The number of missions you can use to influence the surrounding barbarians</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_GID_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_GID_QUOTE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The pictures will turn into thought-provoking poems, the calls will turn into heart-stirring songs, and the tribe will eventually become a country that the world loves.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_GID_QUOTE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I love you, runaway horse. Therefore, I must let you abandon me and find the freedom you have longed for.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_GID_LOADING_INFO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Use your foresight to respond to those difficult administrators, Son of God Kid, and under your leadership, Kedokia can easily make changes. Build your ideal world, guide everything with your nimble and popular fingers, and protect your observation vessel from contamination. You will one day provide the best answer to mankind.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_GID_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The construction of the specialized area of ​​Kedokia can be carried out very early. When completed, territory can be acquired through cultural bombs. It itself can also provide flexible governance methods, and the builders who are initially gifted can also develop the territory earlier. .
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] When you trigger the Eureka of a future technology that cannot be researched currently, Ji De can withdraw the research points provided by the Eureka and invest in current research to enjoy it earlier. This benefit brought by Eureka is more likely to unlock multiple technologies within one turn. The same goes for inspiration and culture.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]If the technology upgrade triggered is the technology you are currently researching, it will not be affected, and the Eureka progress that would have overflowed can even be retained in the form of research points for the next research project. Therefore, you may often need to spend a little time planning the research sequence for the next period of time.
[NEWLINE][Warning: If the progress provided by Eureka is 50%, 10% of the research progress for the corresponding technology will be retained. If the progress provided by Eureka is 30%, the research cost required for the corresponding technology will be +10%. 】
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]At the same time, all of Ji De's units have the ability to influence the surrounding barbarians. This is achieved by using the number of missions, so when the unit uses this ability and the number of missions reaches 0, it will disappear. However, Ji De's religious unit also has an extra number of missions.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] In addition, Ji De can also provide additional wildcard slots, and external trade routes can bring scientific research and cultural bonuses to both parties. This is under the influence of Keluqiya's characteristic area [urban] , Ji De can become an important trade node for the entire camp.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Kedokia itself does not focus on any one way of victory, nor is it suitable for any one way of victory. The leader Ji De can give Keluoqiya the potential to maintain technological leadership for a period of time. At the same time, the invasion of barbarians is not a challenge but a reward for Ji De. If you want to make good use of this advantage, it will test the player's understanding of the game.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_GID_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokia's zone building is often accompanied by culture bombs to the point where they can &quot;peacefully&quot; take over your territory, and it's not a good idea to peacefully coexist in close quarters with such a neighbor. [Mississippi Mound] can maintain the early economy of Kedoqiya, and the existence of [Urban City] also allows Kedoqiya to build a high-development city with high bonus trade routes and areas.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Leader Ji De can improve the technological development in the early and mid-term at the expense of the later stage, and will not be afraid of invasion from the barbarians, but will have the opportunity to receive a large amount of military support from the barbarians.
[NEWLINE][Warning: If the progress provided by Eureka is 50%, 10% of the research progress for the corresponding technology will be retained. If the progress provided by Eureka is 30%, the research cost required for the corresponding technology will be +10%. 】
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] However, as Ai does not seem to be able to use the ability of [Converting Barbarians], I had to add reinforcement effects to it, adding [Charismatic Leader] and [Army Modernization] policy card effects and city-states to the agenda The ability to open borders and cause dissatisfaction to decay more quickly. Although as AI, Ji De is unlikely to initiate a war.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] In addition, Ji De can also provide additional wildcard slots, and external trade routes can bring scientific research and cultural bonuses to both parties. This is under the influence of Keluqiya's characteristic area [urban] , Ji De can become an important trade node for the entire camp.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_KHJY_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>living kingdom</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_KHJY_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Converts a military policy slot, an economic policy slot, and a foreign policy slot into a general policy slot, giving an [ICON_Unit] builder whenever an [ICON_Capital] capital is established.
[NEWLINE]The city builds its first [ICON_District] Specialized District in half the [ICON_Turn] time, and the [ICON_District] Specialized District triggers the Culture Bomb.
[NEWLINE] [Engineering] technology unlocks the construction rights of [Dams] and [Canals] in advance.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_GID_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Enlightenment Catalysis</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_GID_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Converts [ICON_TechBoosted] Eureka / [ICON_CivicBoosted] Inspiration to the equivalent [ICON_Science] Tech / [ICON_Culture] Culture. (The conversion progress value is limited to 40%)
[NEWLINE] Foreign trade routes provide both parties with an additional +2 [ICON_Science] technology value and +2 [ICON_Culture] culture value.
[NEWLINE] All units gain +1 missionary count and can influence nearby barbarian units. When the missionary count reaches 0, the unit will disappear.
[NEWLINE]You will get a wildcard policy slot after unlocking [Administrative Department].</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>urban area</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>urban area</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Keluoqiya's special area: placed in a canal, fixedly provides +6 [ICON_Housing] housing. Allowed to be placed in woods and geothermal fissures. Only 1 can be built per city.
[NEWLINE] Allowed to run featured projects, move capital [ICON_Capital] here, and gain 1 [ICON_Unit] merchant.
[NEWLINE]Give cities a limit of 1 [ICON_TradeRoute] trade route.
[NEWLINE]Gives adjacent specialization areas a large adjacent bonus, and receives a large adjacent bonus food [ICON_Food] from the adjacent [water channel].</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_CAPITAL_MOVE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>New development focus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_CAPITAL_MOVE_SHORT_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>New development focus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROJECT_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_CAPITAL_MOVE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Special projects that can be carried out in any city with [urban area]. When completed, move the [ICON_Capital] capital to this city and gain 1 [ICON_Unit] merchant in the [ICON_Capital] capital.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Culture] Culture value comes from adjacent urban areas.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_FAITH" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Faith] Faith value comes from adjacent urban areas.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_GOLD" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Gold] Gold coins from adjacent urban areas.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_PRODUCTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Production] Production comes from adjacent urban areas.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Science] Science value comes from adjacent urban areas.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_FOOD" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Food] Food comes from adjacent urban areas.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_AQUEDUCT_FOOD" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+{1_num} [ICON_Food] Food comes from adjacent water channels.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_BUILDING_HANGING_GARDENS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>All cities [ICON_FOOD] food +15%. It must be built next to a river.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_GID_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>childish wise teacher</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_GID_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It is unlikely to take the initiative to declare war. [NEWLINE] The dissatisfaction caused by [NEWLINE] declines twice as fast. It has the [Army Modernization] and [Charismatic Leader] policy card effects, and the city-state opens its borders to it. Civilizations hostile to Gid gain double war exhaustion. [NEWLINE] I like a happy civilization where science and technology and culture are prosperous and great people appear frequently.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is something we both would like to see, thank you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I value your proposal very much, but the people of Kedokia will not be happy...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The people of Kedaqiya very much hope to establish a stable and friendly relationship with you. What is your opinion...?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This is something we both would like to see, thank you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We respect your choice...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Is there anything we can't sit down and talk about?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The raging anger of the people can no longer be suppressed, and the Kedokiya people are eager to resolve the conflict with you - yes, with blood and tears...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sorry, the xenophobia among the Kdokqiya people has been rising recently. For your sake, we will discuss this later.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Good day, we at Keluoqiya would like to have more communication with you and learn more about you. Our delegation has brought some interesting and valuable gifts and we hope you will treat them kindly.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What a memorable moment, I wish you a happy life.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well, we'll come back later.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for your visit. Kedokia values ​​this meeting very much.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Good day, we hope to establish an embassy in your capital to better carry out exchanges between the two sides. We will contract the construction funds. We guarantee that this will not harm your sovereign interests. In addition, this is a small gesture of goodwill and respect, so please be sure to accept it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for your trust and may our friendship last forever.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well, we understand how you feel too...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There are many lives on this land, but few can disappoint me as much as you. [NEWLINE](condemn you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>……Who are you? How are you qualified to judge us?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Welcome, it’s been a hard work coming all the way. Everyone in Keluqiya regards me as the Son of God, but you can call me Ji De. The things you carry are really interesting. Can you show them to me?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Want to take a break here? We will prepare clean accommodation and warm bath water. After bathing, we will also have hot milk to drink, ensuring that we can wash away the fatigue of the day.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We are very interested in the new country we are acquainted with, and we would be happy to visit and experience your happy lifestyle. Of course, everyone is different, and it’s normal for some people to be uncomfortable with it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you want to trade city locations with us? This will facilitate subsequent communication between us.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You say.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Your skill points are very high, or there are many great people, and the people are happy)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GID_GREAT_PEOPLE_ADVOCATE_KUDO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your civilization has produced many great men</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Your skill points are very low, or there are few great people, and the people are suffering)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GID_GREAT_PEOPLE_ADVOCATE_WARNING" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your civilization cannot retain any talents</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GID_HIGH_HAPPINESS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You are truly an admirable leader who loves your people like a son.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GID_LOW_HAPPINESS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Treat your people well. I can hear the roar of the people standing here.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_ANY_GID_AGENDA_GREAT_PERSON_ADVOCATE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Why does it take so long for someone without the ability to show up? Is your education lagging behind?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_ANY_GID_AGENDA_GREAT_PERSON_ADVOCATE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A country with outstanding people is full of hope and is doing well.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GID_LIKE_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Many times I don't know what I should do. I want to be the best in everything, but I still can't escape the phenomenon of being the villain in someone's life... If only I could make up my mind like you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_MODIFIER_AGENDA_GID_LIKE_LS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dear elders, longing will</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's time to put this proposal on the table - and let's build an alliance that will bring more benefits.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I think we have no reason to fight anymore.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let alone you and me, none of the people who died on the battlefield, their relatives and friends would choose to agree.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The blood has turned cold and the tears have dried up, but are you...satisfied?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The activities of your military units have sparked considerable debate among the Kdokiya people, who all want to know if this is all your intentions.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_HUMAN_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>That would be great...but we will all watch your every move.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Congratulations, you won. Isn’t it time to enter the period of reflection and anti-war? Repent to everyone that you have killed the happiness, hopes, and dreams of many people, and then declare a state of war again? Sigh... You can only start a war directly. It would be strange if you can repent.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Congratulations, you won. Isn’t it time to enter the period of reflection and anti-war? Repent to everyone that you have killed the happiness, hopes, and dreams of many people, and then declare a state of war again? Sigh... You can only start a war directly. It would be strange if you can repent.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although a bit disappointed, we will come back again.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thanks.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's been arranged, and as long as you don't wander around, there won't be any trouble.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The people of Kedokiya will not be happy...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Good day, we hope that you will allow our troops to pass through your land, and we promise not to cause any trouble to you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_DEAL_AI_ADJUST_DEAL_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I think this bill will be easier to live with.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_AI_REFUSE_DEMAND_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;As heaven moves forward, a gentleman should constantly strive for self-improvement.&quot; Please respect yourself and stop being an international beggar. You can use other ways to get what you want, such as [trading].</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_AI_ACCEPT_DEMAND_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...Oh, it won’t happen next time.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_HUMAN_ACCEPT_DEMAND_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I'm sorry to propose this condition to you. In fact, you can refuse it, but I would like to express my personal gratitude to you for still providing all this.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_HUMAN_REFUSE_DEMAND_FROM_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I see.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_DONT_SETTLE_NEAR_ME_AI_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your expansion around here has caused huge controversy in Keluqiya. A large number of people claim that you have seized our land... I can suppress this matter, but please cooperate with the suspension of expansion. activities to avoid stimulating people’s nervousness...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_DONT_SETTLE_NEAR_ME_HUMAN_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for your cooperation.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_DONT_SETTLE_NEAR_ME_HUMAN_RESPONSE_NEGATIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Alas, the workload has increased again...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_DONT_SETTLE_NEAR_ME_AI_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>…I know, I can only say that I will try my best to guide immigrants away from your land, but in the end their choice is their own decision, and I apologize in advance for any future offense.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_DONT_SETTLE_NEAR_ME_AI_RESPONSE_NEGATIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Kedokiya people are famous for their freedom and freedom, and I really couldn't make an impossible promise.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_AI_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I apologize for those reckless guys and thank you for informing me about this... I hope they will calm down and listen to me.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_AI_RESPONSE_NEGATIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I have tried to dissuade those reckless guys, but obviously they are all angry... You must be prepared for war, I am worried that this will turn into a fierce conflict.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_STOP_SPYING_ON_ME_AI_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well, I will leave the information advantage to your side for now...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_STOP_SPYING_ON_ME_AI_RESPONSE_NEGATIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sorry, I can't give in here. The advantage of information is the key to the survival of a country.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_STOP_SPYING_ON_ME_LEADER_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gui'an, let's talk about private information today... Forget it, let's open the skylight and speak frankly - we already have evidence of your espionage activities on our side. You and I both know this is not a good thing, so please think twice about this.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_STOP_DIGGING_UP_ARTIFACTS_AI_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I see. I will cooperate with you. However, I am afraid that the Keduqiya people will not easily agree to return these unearthed cultural relics.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_STOP_DIGGING_UP_ARTIFACTS_AI_RESPONSE_NEGATIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I see. It seems that those cultural relics are ill-gotten gains. However, I am afraid that I am not capable of combating smuggling. Forgive me for not being able to make a promise. In addition, the people of Keluqiya will not easily agree to return those cultural relics... My personal words may be useless. But I still apologize.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_STOP_CONVERTING_MY_CITIES_AI_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Understood, I will prepare to stop these illegal missionary activities. I am really sorry for causing trouble to you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_STOP_CONVERTING_MY_CITIES_AI_RESPONSE_NEGATIVE_LEADER_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sorry, I'm at my wits end and there are more important things that I need to prioritize. I can only give you some advice here... Why are you leaving?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CAPITAL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokqiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stepping on armor and keran</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tamagotchi sprouts</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiaxia</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qituwan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tennessee</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>onerunga</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Micheli</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Michigan</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pioshoian</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yili Nuoyi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Liviang</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Aiweijiaqingang</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fatunmin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_14" Language="en_US">
			<Text>cansica</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_15" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mamko</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_16" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mai Anming</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_17" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fu He Qi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_18" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chumash</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_19" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Semler</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_20" Language="en_US">
			<Text>spvallin</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_21" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Auxelaica</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_22" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shi Xage</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_23" Language="en_US">
			<Text>O'Neal</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_24" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bu Lu Mideng</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CITY_25" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Milwaukee</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>white crow</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>horns</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gouyue</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>elegy</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Good morning</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>beaver</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>cold snow</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>supafia</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Liam</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>root</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>wind wolf</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mizukawa</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>sparrow song</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>sky apricot</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Popcorn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Quinlilo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Su Luo</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>sunflower</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wind whisper</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Time flies</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>One leaf knows autumn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>floating clouds passing by</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Still water and gentle waves</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>glory days</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>golden maple leaf</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Looking at the moon and remembering</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Virtue</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Clouds and rain drifting</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_MALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>God rewards those who work hard</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Magnificent sunset</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>old friend in old alley</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Seeing flowers in the smoke</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As pleasant as a dream</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Spring flower feast</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qinshui Lily</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Refreshing beauty</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>happy angel</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>haunting</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_KHJY_MODERN_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The subtle fragrance is astonishing</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_FLIRTATIOUS_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sometimes when I can't stand the pressure, I don't know why I always think of your face.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_CURMUDGEON_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for not interrupting me on certain things. As leaders we should all be doing more important things.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_FLIRTATIOUS_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You are really annoying and become a major source of stress for me...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_CURMUDGEON_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If it is not necessary in the future, please do not appear in front of me again. I am very tired.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It’s really easy to do things when you have money, don’t forget to spend it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Low income means inflexible governance, and you should pay attention to it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_INDUSTRY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You really attach great importance to industry. Diligence is a good thing, and don’t forget to take a break.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_INDUSTRY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't forget to take a break when you are diligent, but it is not good to be lazy.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Caring for large groups of people is a complex art, and I hope you find joy in it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If people do not have children, it is either due to lack of materials or unfavorable environment. Are you neglecting it too much?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_STANDING_ARMY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Deterrence is not a panacea, but no deterrence is absolutely impossible. Your citizens must feel very safe.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_STANDING_ARMY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pacifism is good, but without the ability to protect yourself, how can you maintain your own justice?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_PROTECT_CITY_STATES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's really admirable that you can stand up for those weak city-states.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_PROTECT_CITY_STATES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Pointing the finger at weak city-states? I should teach you that this is shameful.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_MED_PROTECT_CITY_STATES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You will really protect your subjects very well. Such a strong sense of responsibility is really amazing.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_MED_ATACK_CITY_STATES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I advise you not to be so insensitive, the whole world is watching your every move.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_CLEARS_BARBARIAN_CAMPS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thank you for bringing those bad guys to justice. That area should have some peace for a while.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_IGNORES_BARBARIAN_CAMPS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Is it really good to let those evil people do evil things? Should you be worried about this?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Culture is proof of the existence of a civilized society, and your civilization has become quite dazzling.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Culture is proof of the existence of a civilized society, but your civilization is silent.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The development of technology means how far a civilization can go, and it's great to see your civilization thrive.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The development of technology means how far a civilization can go, but it is difficult for me to see the future of your civilization.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_EXPANSIONIST" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It seems that you know very well that land is the most precious resource.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_EXPANSIONIST" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Land is limited and will not regenerate. If you ignore it, others will take it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GREAT_WHITE_FLEET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sea power is an important force in connecting with the world. It seems that you attach great importance to all this.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GREAT_WHITE_FLEET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sea power is an important force connecting the world. Don't underestimate it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_FAVOR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>There is no need to compete, as long as I am here, I will bring happiness to everyone.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_FAVOR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>No need to compete, I will point out the way forward for you, why bother yourself?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_TOURISM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Without an impressive culture, it would be too natural to become attached to our culture.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_TOURISM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>People are flocking to your city... Did I do something wrong? Our culture can’t even keep its own people?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_DIPLOVP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You can say that we are rebellious, but human will is like human hands, it should be free and realize its own ideals.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_DIPLOVP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Just talk about your so-called agenda and I won't listen to you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_TURTLER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I admire the people who were the first to stand up and defend the motherland. I hope you will not let them down.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_TURTLER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I admire the people who were the first to stand up and defend their motherland. As an invader, you must never forget it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_AIRPOWER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The importance of air power is no less important than any power, and it seems that you understand this well.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_AIRPOWER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Air power is as important as any power, and it's time you paid attention to it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_SYCOPHANT_GOLDEN_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, a shining pearl in the history of mankind, there is no doubt about it at this moment.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_SYCOPHANT_DARK_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wandering in confusion is hard work, and that's what you and your people are going to face... and it's best if you don't mean to do it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_SYMPATHIZER_DARK_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Are you confused and sad as your ideals are pushed further and further away by the rolling mountain waves? Don't be afraid, you are always with us.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_SYMPATHIZER_GOLDEN_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, one of the shining pearls of human history, but with all due respect - climbing to the top means you're going downhill. You must always be alert.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GOSSIP_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yes, some things exist there no matter how much we deny them, and they must be understood because they exist. Otherwise, how can we deal with the problems caused by those things?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_GID_REASON_AGENDA_GOSSIP_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You may get entangled in unknown problems even if you stay behind closed doors. Come on, establish more connections with the world and build more intelligence cafes in the world.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_LS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lieso</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Akira Kurashi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_AGENDA_LS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Appreciate civilizations that value industry and people's livelihood, especially those that defend city-states. There is quite a bit of criticism about a civilization that does not pay attention to production capacity or people's livelihood.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your civilization really sets a good example for our people!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_DESCRIPTION_HIGH_INDUSTRYAND_FUN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Leso admires your national style</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What do your people look like? Is this still a human being? They are just a bunch of beasts wearing clothes! Sleep when you are full, eat when you are full, mediocre and incompetent!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MODIFIER_DESCRIPTION_LOW_INDUSTRYAND_FUN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Leso is deeply indignant at the decline of your nation.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_LS_LOADING_INFO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The finger of God pulls civilization up from the dust of history, brings people together tightly, and continues to prosper - this is you, Lord Leso. This era is extremely dark, but under your leadership, people will surely open up a new bright future!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>God's call</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gain 10 [ICON_Faith] Faith for each Era Point gained, allowing [ICON_Faith] Faith to be used to purchase civilian units.
[NEWLINE] +33% [ICON_Production] production capacity when running projects in the city, and gain an [ICON_GOVERNOR] governor title when building the first specialized area.
[NEWLINE]Owns the unique unit the Brave Warrior.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lieso</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The first and only legal dictatorial consul general</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_LS_QUOTE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>&quot;The happiness of the people is the happiness of the country, and the cause of the country is the cause of the people.&quot; - Today's homework is to memorize this sentence. I will check it tomorrow.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_LS_QUOTE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Each generation has its own mission, and it is also my responsibility to leave opportunities for future generations to realize their own values.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>He is not only an upright and iron-fisted monarch, but also a deeply trusted one of the founders of the Republic. As a leader, although Lieso was born into a noble priesthood, he did not receive a proper education - when he was young, his parents suffered political persecution and died violently, and he was the only one to escape.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Losing his parents and his hometown was in a period of extreme poverty, it was natural for Lieso to leave his hometown and wander around. However, Lieso is obviously no ordinary person. With his growth and adventure, he has become a legendary hero. During this period, he also made many friends, including chiefs of various tribes and equally famous heroes from various places. At his call, Lieso gathered an army and attacked his hometown, avenging the murderers of his parents and ending their tyranny. However, in the face of everyone's election, he did not become the new chief.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The newly appointed chief &quot;Daydream&quot; is recognized as a good person. However, although his rule did not make things worse, it did not improve the current situation of the tribe. Decades later, Leso, who adopted a maiden, finally took over the power from &quot;Daydream&quot; and established the Kedokiya Empire.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]During Leso's reign, Kdokia's territory was at its most extensive and its influence was at its most extensive. It stretches from Hudson Bay to the north, Florida to the south, Newfoundland to the east, and California to the west. He recruited talents regardless of their origins, and social class mobility was smooth. It is said that the person he trusted and relied on most was his adopted daughter [Ji De]. Based on her suggestions, he adopted qualified elections, established a meeting system, and appointed officials. Schools were established and compulsory education was implemented. The term of office of officials, including heads of state, should not exceed four years, laying the foundation for the subsequent establishment of a republic in Kedoqiya. Under such a system, the beloved Leso was elected as the leader many times. Regarding this, [Ji De]'s student &quot;Gou Yue&quot; once commented that Leso was becoming the emperor in the republic, and Leso was After hearing this, I smiled and said, &quot;On the contrary, I am just a governor in the empire.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 1563, Lisso died. Before his death, as a citizen of Keluqiya, he chose to elect [Ji De] as the new governor (some versions of the legend also voted for [Ji De]'s most well-behaved student &quot;Ox Horn&quot;). After seeing the content of his vote, maybe it was a secret operation, or maybe everyone trusted his choice, and almost everyone made the same choice as him. Although it was later proven that he was also a mortal who could make mistakes, in the minds of the Kedokiya people, he was still, as he said, &quot;one of the fingers of the gods.&quot;</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JSYS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Brawny Warriors are heroes organized by Leso. As early as the barbaric era, the North American continent was filled with the footprints of legendary heroes. However, the number of heroes is limited, and the number of warriors who become stronger with the development of technology is unlimited. These soldiers abandoned by the times have to serve their old age. However, the core of combat in the army is always the veterans who have actually been on the battlefield. Lieso brought these soldiers together to establish a new special operations organization, which is famous for its agility, surprise attacks, support defense, and escort. Of course, for these experienced warriors, their treatment is naturally not low.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JSYS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] The Brave Warriors ended smoothly in 1563, when firearms became popular, which was also the year of Lieso's death.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The construction of the specialized area of ​​Kedokia can be carried out very early. When completed, it can also seize territory through cultural bombs. It itself can also provide flexible governance methods, and the builders who are initially gifted can also develop the territory earlier. .
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Leso is different from [Jid] who can bring explosive improvement. His style is relatively gentle. Leso pursues creating glorious historical moments to gain [ICON_Faith] faith that can mobilize builders and recruit great men. At the same time, he has a unique special unit - the Slender Warrior.
[NEWLINE]Meanwhile, Leso enjoys an additional productivity bonus in running projects to gain output and Greatness Points faster.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Although the basic combat abilities of the Brawny Warriors are not outstanding, the unique promotion tree can support them in special operations, such as harassing enemy lines and holding their positions. High-level Brawny Warriors even have the opportunity to stand alone on the frontal battlefield.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LS_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokia's zone building is often accompanied by culture bombs to the point where they can &quot;peacefully&quot; take over your territory, and it's not a good idea to peacefully coexist in close quarters with such a neighbor. [Mississippi Mound] can maintain the early economy of Kedoqiya, and the existence of [Urban City] also allows Kedoqiya to build a high-development city with high bonus trade routes and areas.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Under the leadership of Leso, the professional area built by Kedokia has released cultural bombs with the ability to seize the territory of other civilizations.
[NEWLINE] While Leso doesn't have a clear tendency to win, he can recruit great people by running projects quickly and gaining eras to gain [ICON_Faith] Faith, giving you an advantage in the way you want to win. At the same time, he can easily use [ICON_Faith] faith value to purchase builders to speed up territory construction.
[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]As an AI, Leso will not hesitate to declare war to regain territory, defend a city-state, or seek revenge. At the same time, Lesuo will actively clear out the barbarian villages.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Come, sit down. What is in front of you is Leso, the only great god in the world. Keluqiya is the country I am responsible for, and what is your purpose here? explain.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I can see that you travelers are tired, so I will point you to the road to the city near us. Go there. We have to continue on the road.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well, it's not a waste of time in any way.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>tired? So are we. So let's complete one last task before we take a break - let's visit each other's capitals to facilitate subsequent contact.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>explain.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Since they represent your face, come over.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's not that time yet.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We don't intend to cause conflict, so just accept these little gifts. at the same time. These lads will also be stationed as emissaries of Kedokiya, you know what I mean.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Smart move.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Humph...I don't know how to appreciate it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We want to rent a piece of land to build the embassy, ​​and we will provide the construction funds. This is a gift.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Smart move.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_EMBASSY_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>...I will come again.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Remember, no running around. Go ahead.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Now, there is no need to talk about this.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let's talk about the national border. Now our people need to pass through your land. We respect your sovereignty, so we came here to negotiate. Are you willing to sell us this favor?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>as you wish.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh, the time has not come yet.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Come, stand with me, shake hands, take a sip of wine, exchange pipes. This can bring peace for a generation.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Just like family members, right?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh, whatever.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Come work with me soon.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_ANY_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_INDUSTRYAND_FUN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your civilization really sets a good example for our people!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_PROTECT_CITY_STATES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It’s amazing that you can also shoulder your due responsibilities when dealing with outsiders! Everyone should really learn from you!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_MED_PROTECT_CITY_STATES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It’s amazing that you can also shoulder your due responsibilities when dealing with outsiders! Everyone should really learn from you!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_ANY_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_INDUSTRYAND_FUN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What do your people look like? Is this still a human being? They are just a bunch of beasts wearing clothes! Sleep when you are full, eat when you are full, mediocre and incompetent!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_PROTECT_CITY_STATES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Attacking weaker people does not show your strength, but makes you look extremely despicable.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_MED_ATACK_CITY_STATES" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You have neglected your duties and you are not worthy to be their ruler!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LS_LIKE_GID_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My child, don’t put too much pressure on yourself. You are my mentor and friend, and you have the ability to do all this well.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_AGENDA_LS_LIKE_GID" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My mentor, my beloved child</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let me give you a heads up and see for yourself where your army is?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_HUMAN_RESPONSE_POSITIVE_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't do it again next time!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ah, very good.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh, forget it.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Is this your attitude? Choose to stand against me?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If I can dig civilization out of the bloodshed of history, I can also bury you! [NEWLINE](condemn you)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_REASON_FROM_AI_LEADER_ANY_REASON_JFD_WORLD_SOCIALISM_DIFF_GOVERNMENT" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(Your civilization is too lax)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let's see what you are capable of!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's time to clean up the world's garbage!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You fought well. Now, let's make peace.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It won't end like this.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>These are the conditions we can provide, see for yourself.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's really unpredictable that I was defeated by you. It shows that I haven't worked hard enough, and it also shows that you work harder than me. I believe the people will live better under your rule, remember today.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_LS_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's really unpredictable that I was defeated by you. It shows that I haven't worked hard enough, and it also shows that you work harder than me. I believe the people will live better under your rule, remember today.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_FLIRTATIOUS_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If I were ten years younger, I would consider whether to adopt you as my adopted son; if I were twenty years younger, I would definitely talk about dreams and have a drink with you. If I were thirty years younger... I think I would pursue you. pity.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_CURMUDGEON_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As a leader, you should naturally let go of some personal emotions. I deeply sympathize with your efforts.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_FLIRTATIOUS_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I am glad that I am already an old man, so that I will not neglect my own duties because my mind is full of you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_SAILOR_CURMUDGEON_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I'm past the age of flirting, can't you find someone else to play with? !</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your ability to make money is obvious to all. What do you think, would you like to work here?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_INCOME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Due to the waste of tax money and vicious cycle, your country's financial industry has become like a pool of stagnant water. I want to see how you get through this difficulty.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Such a dense population means your responsibilities are heavy, and you must not let the people down.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>When I was most frustrated, I did not interfere in any affairs of people's livelihood. I thought that the population was at its lowest at that time, but I didn't expect that your rule was more powerful than mine.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_STANDING_ARMY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What a powerful and magnificent army. I guess there won't be any unsighted guy who will cause trouble for you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_STANDING_ARMY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oh, you just expect this little army to protect your country? They are really weak, pitiful, and helpless.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_CLEARS_BARBARIAN_CAMPS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well done to those bastards who only want to use violence to fight for property.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_IGNORES_BARBARIAN_CAMPS" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Are you colluding with those barbarians to allow them to cause trouble in your territory?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your national literacy is very good, keep it up.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_CULTURE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If you are illiterate, no matter how advanced your skills are, you are still like a child wielding a blade.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Technology is a concrete manifestation of understanding the world created by this great god, and the person who understands it most deeply is undoubtedly you.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_SCIENCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ignoring the laws of operation of the material world, no matter how popular you are, you will wither in your grave.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_EXPANSIONIST" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don’t be shy about expanding your land.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_EXPANSIONIST" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I just heard a joke recently, saying that to get to your house from here, you only need to go out and turn a few streets. ha……</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_GREAT_WHITE_FLEET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The navy is not only a basic force for crossing oceans, but also an important force for protecting our country. It seems that you do not take this lightly.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_GREAT_WHITE_FLEET" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The navy is not only a basic force for crossing oceans, but also an important force for protecting the country. It seems that you underestimate these things too much?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_FAVOR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yes, stand behind me, follow my footsteps, and listen to my leadership, and I will definitely give you the treatment you deserve.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_FAVOR" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Humph, it seems that you must have a chance encounter with me.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_TOURISM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The cultures of our two countries are separated by a thin strip of water.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_TOURISM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I won't let Keluqiya sink like this...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_DIPLOVP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yes, there is no need to compete with me, just do your own thing.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_DIPLOVP" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tighten your edge, it will only make you bruised and bruised.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_TURTLER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It is not smart at all to shift unresolved conflicts to foreign countries, and I appreciate that you think so.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_TURTLER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's not smart at all to shift unresolved conflicts to foreign countries, don't you think so?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_HIGH_AIRPOWER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Airpower is clearly going to be more and more important, and it seems you and I agree.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_LOW_AIRPOWER" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Airpower is clearly going to be more and more important, and you should take a longer view.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_SYCOPHANT_GOLDEN_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You have carved out a bright future for your people and you deserve appreciation.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_SYCOPHANT_DARK_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You let your people fall into the twilight age and struggle, you loser!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_SYMPATHIZER_DARK_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It seems that you have hit the bottom, but don't be discouraged. Looking ahead, your future is already an upward one!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_SYMPATHIZER_GOLDEN_AGE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You have indeed made your empire prosperous, but how should you deal with the future of decline?</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_GOSSIP_POSITIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If you want to solve a problem, you must first understand the problem, which requires a pair of eyes and ears that are good at discovery. I'm glad you and I are on the same page.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_LEADER_LS_REASON_AGENDA_GOSSIP_NEGATIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If you want to solve a problem, you must first understand the problem, which requires a pair of eyes and ears that are good at discovery. You should build an intelligence network.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] To this day, there are still doubts about whether the Kdokia people are the inheritors of the civilization that established the Cahokia ruins. After all, in the beginning, they were just one of the many clans and tribes in the vast land of North America. At that time, Keluqiya's name was Tagakkara, or [Tajia Keran]. After they became rich, they called themselves the Cahokians. Due to reservations about Keluoqiya civilization, the current academic circles' names for it come from the translation of Chinese elegant names.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] According to the historical record &quot;Sanshengmo&quot;, the Tajia Keran tribe was the leader of the alliance of five tribes for a long time. However, under the rule of a tyrant, the alliance fell apart and a large number of people were lost. At the same time, tornadoes and cold currents moving south also led to the plowing of fields. The harvest was so bad that even so the tyrant refused to listen to anyone's opinions and moved, even brutally murdering a tribal priest. More people chose to leave, but it wasn't long before people discovered that the bones of those people were hanging on the columns of the sacrificial site. [NEWLINE] Later, as in many legends, under the leadership of a hero, the tyrant was killed and the people cheered. And that hero was the son of the murdered priest. His name is [White Crow][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] In his early years, due to the death of his father, Bai Ya left the Tajia Keran tribe and traveled around, becoming a warrior full of wisdom and bravery. At the same time, he formed deep friendships with the surrounding tribes. Finally, he learned from these tribes He invited countless warriors to return to Tajia Keran with him and overthrew the tyrant's rule. [NEWLINE] At first, faced with the recommendation from everyone, Bai Ya was very humble. So Tajia Keran had no choice but to recommend another famous good man to rule. However, after thirty years, the situation of Tajia Keran has not improved. If it were not for the white crow standing firmly here, Tajia Keran would have become the dust of history. So Bai Ya decided to rule the Tajia Keran tribe by himself. [NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] Although White Crow is very respected, thirty years later, his reputation is no longer so resounding in the ears of the younger generation. So he decided to adopt a child. [NEWLINE] Adopt a child, why? As long as you pay attention to the name he gave his child and the name he later changed to himself, you will understand - [NEWLINE] [Son of God], and [Apostle]! [NEWLINE] ——Yes, he founded a religion, described the existence of an abstract and unique god, and claimed that a concrete [Son of God] and [Apostle] &quot;came&quot; to the world. This model is very similar to Christianity to a certain extent, but there are subtle differences: in fact, the person who founded the faith is the White Crow as the [Apostle], while the [Son of God] is the adopted son under his supervision. [NEWLINE] Some scholars believe that the reason why he did not establish himself as the [Son of God] may be to convey a message: &quot;You young people, stop being so stupid. Even the children of God have to behave when I am here.&quot; Be obedient!&quot; means...[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] Although the description of it in &quot;Sanshengmo&quot; is very vague, combined with some folk stories, this [Son of God] adopted by [Apostle] White Crow is also very mythical. According to legend, it was snowing heavily when she was born, but she could talk and run around as soon as she was born, and she was very intelligent. It is said that many of Keluoqiya's technologies came from her, ranging from forging technology to animal husbandry and even people's livelihood management. Although these may be just subjective assumptions written by people who recorded history after hearing folklore, this is also the best story currently until academics discover the truth about Keluoqiya's rapid technological and social level. [NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] In 1563, [Apostle] died, and the power of this hegemonic empire that almost occupied an entire continent was given to [Son of God], and [Son of God] chose to delegate power. This seems to be very enlightened and advanced in today's social values. However, history has proved that it seems that it was decentralized too early and too hastily. The decentralized power flows into the people like a trickle of water, but human beings are living creatures, and they are creatures who invent backpacks in order to carry away fruits that cannot be carried with both hands. Soon the power she had delegated was in the hands of the oligarchic class. In 1576, she was ousted from power and disappeared.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] Although the &quot;enlightened&quot; [Son of God] was kicked off the stage and disappeared, her followers still occupy a considerable political position in society. In other words, almost all oligarchs have publicly claimed that they are [Son of God] 】s student. However, it is obvious that what this Mr. [Son of God] taught them is very different, and the followers have different opinions on the suggestions and policies she left behind. This difference in opinions soon broke out into violent conflicts (perhaps this This is also the reason why [Son of God] chose to abdicate peacefully and disappeared). [NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] As the war situation intensified, many methods that Mr. [Son of God] would have condemned in the past were put on the stage by the student oligarchs. White phosphorus bombs that are difficult to extinguish, poison gas that destroys lives, prisoners or refugees are captured to make strategic materials, and in the end, even nuclear weapons that are used as a deterrent and must never be used are brought up by the ambitious ambitions who have broken their nerves... In the end , the former hegemony of Kedokia was destroyed, and nuclear winter spread across North America, which lasted for nearly 300 years before it became habitable. [NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_KHJY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE] Since then, in order to obtain the secrets of this legendary &quot;paradise kingdom&quot; that has gone to hell, all countries with conditions have chosen to log in to North America, which is full of mutant creatures, in an attempt to discover their secrets. And this became the predecessor of today's United States. The large number of technologies and theories unearthed from the remains of Kedokia made the United States once the most advanced country in the world, and it is still the only superpower in the world today. A super situation with many strong players. And the ruins of Keluoqiya have not yet been fully excavated... [NEWLINE] (The above encyclopedia is purely fictitious content created by the author, please do not take it seriously!)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_KHJY_LOCATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Illinois, USA</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_KHJY_SIZE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Covering an area of ​​8.376 million square kilometers (the actual core area is only 140,000 square kilometers)</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_KHJY_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>At its peak, there were more than 160 million people. After the split, only about 9,000 people remained.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_KHJY_CAPITAL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokqiya</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] [Downtown] is a community planning that closely integrates commercial and residential areas. The concept of [Downtown] is to encourage commercial activities to be carried out extensively and actively in the community through the overall planning of transportation and residential buildings. Therefore, in the [Downtown], you can see various shops selling daily necessities or food in the streets and alleys. But for this reason, the roads extending in all directions have been divided into sidewalks specifically for pedestrians to come and go; parts of each house have also been divided into shops, causing the place to be full of hustle and bustle all day long.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Although [urban area] is more economical, there are also facilities such as wholesalers, which requires businessmen to communicate with each other. At the same time, due to economic prosperity, residents often have better conditions to support their study and work away from home. However, because this kind of economical planning naturally tends to lead to overactive communities, [urban areas] must be built around the city center in order to be supervised by the administrative departments of the city center.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_DISTRICTS_PAGE_DISTRICT_GID_CAMPUS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] In addition, the location in the [urban area] is also very particular about beauty. It must be close to mountains and rivers, and it must also pursue coexistence with beautiful nature, but this is limited to pleasant woods and really warm geothermal heat. crack.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADER_GID" Language="en_US">
			<Text>【Jide】</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADER_GID_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although this is not her real name, she declined to reveal more.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TECH_FUTURE_TECH_QUOTE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>It's easy to go back in time, except that there's no one there anymore. [NEWLINE]——Jide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TECH_NUCLEAR_FISSION_QUOTE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Once upon a time there were people who dreamed of becoming astronauts, but they said rockets only carried nuclear warheads. [NEWLINE]——Kammi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TECH_ECONOMICS_QUOTE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Just because you won’t treat something you don’t own as a loss doesn’t mean that the economy won’t treat it as a loss. [NEWLINE]——Oho</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_TECH_GUNPOWDER_QUOTE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The sound of artillery and gunfire was deafening, and the sound of crushed bows seemed to praise its glory. [NEWLINE]——Leso</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVIC_FUTURE_CIVIC_QUOTE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>If we always look to the past for wisdom, there will be no progress or future. [NEWLINE]——Jide</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVIC_NATURAL_HISTORY_QUOTE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We must not let self-annihilation become the end point of human evolution! [NEWLINE]——Kammi</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVIC_DIVINE_RIGHT_QUOTE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Great God gave me the legal power to rule with one finger, and the Children of the Great God gave me the qualified wisdom to rule with companionship. And you, my friend, owe me a large amount of reasonable taxes on your income today! [NEWLINE]——Oho</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVIC_MYSTICISM_QUOTE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Smoking allows you to look at the foggy world with a clear mind, and faith will allow you to keep a clear mind in the foggy world. [NEWLINE]——Leso</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_GID_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The legendary figure of Keluqiya may indeed exist. According to legend, he is a child of God who possesses an abandoned orphan and brings various technologies to people. Finally, he is disappointed with mankind and returns to God.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_GID_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] According to legend, [Jide] was born in a snowstorm in the winter of 1521, and was abandoned by her parents in Tajia Keran, a small and run-down tribe at that time. As a result, she developed the root cause of her disease, and her skin became as if Snow is generally sickly white. Legend has it that she learned to walk, be eloquent, and clever since she was born, and thus supported herself. Until she was 5 years old, she was recognized by Chief Tajia Keran [Leso] and was adopted, known as [ Son of God]. The actual situation may be that she is Leso's illegitimate daughter, and for some reason she could not be adopted until she was 5 years old. ——Of course, this is just a joke made by an expert and professor.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_GID_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]If it really exists, then [Jide] should indeed be one of the important reasons for the rapid development of Keduqiya. Throughout her life, she invented important technologies such as paper and the wheel; surveyed and excavated iron ore that had previously been completely unminable; after controlling a few North American bison with nose rings, she imported horses and other livestock from European colonists; He invented the rod-pulled crossbow, and soon invented the steam engine and air gun. In just a dozen years, the tribe had world-leading technology. In terms of culture and politics, she advocated a republican system and respected all people regardless of class or ethnic group. During her rule, the status of human rights reached its peak; she established railways and planned transportation. It is said that Keluqiya and even the transportation system in the United States today are based on her. Based on the plan; promote jazz, rock music, hip-hop and other music genres, create sketches, abstract impressionist paintings that ignore some details, and beautify cartoons on this basis... In this regard, five-star General MacArthur said: If it is true There is such a person as [Jide], and the above deeds are all true. I think she must be a time traveler.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_GID_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Just like many prophets, such as Confucius who traveled to the seven countries with three thousand disciples, Moses who led the Jews to escape Egypt, the Buddha Sakyamuni who was loved by the monks, and who was &quot;loyally&quot; followed by the thirteen disciples Jesus... [Jide] also has his own students. She asked people to respect each other as &quot;Sir&quot;, which means &quot;life that goes before&quot;, and at the same time, she calls herself &quot;student&quot; which means &quot;life that is constantly learning from the world&quot;. She traveled widely during the reign of Leso, and her students were everywhere. Students will naturally raise various doubts to her, and [Jide] will naturally respond in most cases. Her students are all over Keluqiya. But there is a &quot;problem student&quot; named &quot;Gou Yue&quot; who gives [Ji De] a headache. His questions are often regarded as inappropriate, too cunning and mean, and annoying. However, this one student is the one who most obeys her will.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_GID_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]With the passage of time, some of [Jid's] dogmas, like those of many prophets, have been interpreted with different meanings. Each student claimed that his own opinion was the most correct and split into different sects. However, [Ji De], who was still alive, did not respond to their opinions, even if the other party's interpretation was already perverse. Her indifference undoubtedly chilled many students, but there were also loyal followers who claimed that she was doing it to &quot;preserve the diversity of human will.&quot; But this is undoubtedly weak for politics. Soon, [Jide] failed to fully delegate power to the masses and resigned.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_GID_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Regarding [Jide], people's opinions on her are very polarized. One group thinks that she is a fighter who devotes her whole life to realizing an ideal world; the other group thinks that she is just a person who gives things that everyone cannot achieve. The incompetent liar of dreams. But when it comes to who is the founder of Keluqiya, no one will question her lofty status.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JMQS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Death Knights were a group of &quot;Followers of the Son of God&quot; who were active from the late 16th century to the early 17th century. They were founded by &quot;Gou Yue&quot;, who was once the most troublesome student of the Son of God [Jide]. A quasi-theocratic force that claims to pursue and carry forward the fundamental doctrine of [Ji De] and deals with oligarchs and warlords.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JMQS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It is said that the behavior of the Death Knight is full of romanticism, very much like those noble and devout paladins in knight novels. These homeless knights work as &quot;mercenaries&quot; on the battlefield on weekdays. No matter how much they are paid, they give priority to civilian entrustments to maintain law and order. In addition, the desperate knights also need to study basic courses such as literature, mathematics, and foreign languages, as well as various interest courses such as physics, chemistry, and biomedicine. On the battlefield, they are not only a group of excellent doctors, but also a spear of destiny that can penetrate everything. Therefore, ambitious people who want to send this group of mercenaries to the battlefield have to pay a large commission and do not accept credit.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JMQS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Although they have a tradition of going to the battlefield as mercenaries, the original intention of the establishment of the Death Knights has not been forgotten-to carry forward the philosophy of the Son of God [Jide] and establish a prosperous ideal world of equal human rights. However, the spirit of this group of idealists did not impress the careerists, and Keluqiya was still burned in the flames of war.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JMQS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The last organized charge of the Death Knights was on September 11, 1603. Facing the new weapons and tanks under the command of the most powerful warlord at the time, &quot;Tiandaoqin&quot;, the desperate knights with only 27 people left launched a suicide charge without hesitation, creating a lot of sparks and chaos in the torrent of steel. In order to reverse the defeat, the warlord &quot;Fuyun Guoying&quot; who hired them to protect himself first launched nuclear weapons on the battlefield and hostile factories...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_UNITS_PAGE_UNIT_JMQS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] At this point, as the last desperate knight melted in the radiation, and the funeral horns for Kedokia continued, the end of an era came.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_IMPROVEMENT_MOUND_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>mississippi mounds</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_IMPROVEMENT_MOUND_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kedokia's special improvement facilities: +3 [ICON_GOLD] gold coins for the cell; every 2 adjacent areas will provide an additional +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] productivity. To unlock [Administrative Department], only 1 adjacent area is required. [NEWLINE]Give +1 [ICON_HOUSING] housing to the city. Unlocking [Cultural Heritage] will provide an additional +1 [ICON_HOUSING] housing. [NEWLINE] After unlocking [Games and Entertainment], the first Mississippi Mound provides the city with +1 points [ICON_AMENITIES] for livability, and after unlocking [Professional Sports], the second Mississippi Mound also provides the city with +1 point [ICON_AMENITIES] ] Livability. [NEWLINE]Cannot be built next to another Mississippi Mound.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CONCEPTS_PAGE_ENVIRONMENTAL_EFFECTS_CHAPTER_DROUGHTS_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Drought reduces a cell's [ICON_Food] food production by 1 point. In addition, all farms, camps, plantations, ranches, sheds, outback ranches, and Mississippi mound improvements built within the affected areas will be despoiled. During the worst droughts, these improvements have the potential to be removed entirely!</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Cahokia site is marked by huge mounds on the Mississippi River plains. It was a Native American urban and ceremonial site, and its importance has only recently been noted following archaeological research.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Archaeological evidence shows that the late Shulin people settled here around the 8th century. A distinct Mississippian culture began to emerge at this time, marked by widespread corn cultivation. The Aboriginal population grew and social organization became increasingly complex. It was during this time that construction of the Mississippi Mound, or Cahokia Mound, began, which would serve as the religious and ceremonial center of the city. Cahokia's main buildings were arranged along the astronomical axes and cardinal directions, and the remains of large wooden buildings remain on the site. Some of these wrecks are observatories built with cedar pillars in an astronomical layout (commonly known as &quot;Big Wooden Circles&quot;), and there are also hierarchical houses. There is also a rolling stone ballpark built on the site, and the players participating in the rolling stone game are also the main objects depicted in Cahokia's art works. St. Louis residents can therefore rest assured that their obsession with sports has historical roots.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cahokia's population surpassed London's in 1250. The Mississippi floodplain created agricultural land fertile enough to support the common people. Unearthed artifacts indicate that trade routes at this time extended as far as Mexico. But there is also evidence that conflict is also growing. A massive palisade several kilometers long was built in the middle of the century and has been continuously reinforced since then.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As the Medieval Warm Period ended, Cahokia's population and wealth also began to decline. As the climate cooled, the agricultural system practiced by Mississippians was unable to sustain Cahokia's population. Although Cahokia's urban center has declined in status, it is still used as a ceremonial and religious site. It was eventually abandoned in the 14th century, and was relocated to a new location and given its current name by the Illinivik Cahokia people in the 17th century. The names used by the original inhabitants have been lost to history.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During colonial times, French missionaries and traders established outposts in the Cahokia area. In 1809, a community of strict Cistercian monks built a monastery on one of the largest mounds, which later became known as the &quot;Monks' Mound&quot;. The exact nature of these mounds was not understood at the time. It was not until the mid-19th century that an enterprising farmer dug a well into the mound and their nature was revealed.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Cahokia Mounds site was established in 1979 and was added to the UNESCO World Heritage List in 1982. Research on Cahokia provides a more complete understanding of American Indian life before Western colonization, particularly in terms of urban development and trade networks. On the contrary, it also overturned the world's inherent impression of American Indian civilization. The Native Americans who built America's first major city along the Mississippi River hoped that time would continue to open a window into their future lives.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Although the civilization that built Cahokia has disappeared, the presence of mound structures similar to Cahokia's remains in the Mississippi Valley may be evidence of Cahokia's cultural influence. The Creeks were one of them. The Creeks were divided into two groups: the Muskogees, also known as the Upper Creeks, who lived in the northern part of the Creek land; and the Chichiti and Alabama people, who had the same habits as the Upper Creeks, but They speak a slightly different dialect and are called the Lower Creeks. They all belong to aboriginal tribes in North America who speak the Muskogee language. They originally lived in large areas of flat land in Georgia and Alabama. Their economy is generally based on growing corn, beans and Mainly pumpkin. Women farmed and men went out hunting or fighting.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Creek villages and towns are divided into white cities and red cities. White cities specialize in peace ceremonies, and red cities specialize in war ceremonies. They attach great importance to rank, but rank is based on personal merit - military exploits or intelligence - rather than being hereditary. Like most Southeastern Indians, they also love tattoos. [NEWLINE]Every village or town has a public square, surrounded by rectangular houses surrounded by wooden posts coated with mud to form a fence. The roof was coated with bitumen and covered with bark or thatch, and the chimney remained above the gable. If there is a temple in a village or town, the temple will have a round grass roof and be built on a 2.4-meter (8-foot) high earth mound, with steps built from the mound to the entrance of the temple. The square is a gathering place, and important religious ceremonies such as the Green Valley Festival are held here; the Green Valley Festival is the annual first fruit and new fire ceremony. What’s different about this midsummer festival is that any bad thing, wrong or sin can be forgiven on this day. [NEWLINE]The exception is murderers.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In 1539, DeSoto led his troops to invade Creek land, which was the beginning of contact between the Creeks and white people. Later, the Creeks and the British colonists united to fight against the Apalaches and the Spanish. The war began around 1703, and they fought against each other for several years. [NEWLINE]A Creek confederacy was formed in the 18th century but failed. [NEWLINE] When the Creek War broke out against the United States in 1813-1814, some towns fought alongside and some against the whites. After their defeat, the Creeks ceded 9,200,000 hectares of their land (23,000,000, half of Alabama and parts of southern Georgia), and in the 1830s they were forced to move to Indian Territory (now Oklahoma). There, the Creeks, Cherokee, Chickasaw, Choctaw and Seminole were known as the Five Civilized Tribes. [NEWLINE]After more than 70 years, each tribe was given a share of land and formed a quasi-autonomous government modeled on the U.S. government. In 1907, Oklahoma was preparing to become a state, and some of the tribal lands were allocated to individual Aboriginal people; the remaining lands were issued by the federal government and were open to white settlers or allocated to freed slaves for farming. The tribal government was actually dissolved in 1906, but still exists in some limited form. Some indigenous people live on this land known as tribal possessions.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In the late 20th century, approximately 20,000 Creeks lived in Oklahoma, many of whom had adopted the lifestyle of state residents and were Creeks in name only. About 15,000 of them live on federally issued land. Another group of people was more conservative and continued to speak the Creek language, maintain the early town organization form, and continued to observe Creek religious ceremonies such as the Baby Corn Festival celebration. [NEWLINE] There are also some Creeks who stayed in southwest Alabama, and their descendants number about 500. These people no longer speak the Creek language and have lost almost all traces of their Creek culture. The Seminoles in Florida and Oklahoma were an offshoot of the Creek Confederacy in the 18th and early 19th centuries.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>(End) [NEWLINE] In the setting of this MOD, Kedokia is a new culture developed from a descendant of the Cahokia culture. However, under the influence of [Jide], it is difficult to see the original culture. cultural appearance. Replacing Cahokia City-State with Creek City-State here is not disrespectful to Cahokia culture... [NEWLINE] I just want to give the green light to the civilization I want to build...</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_TRAIT_CAHOKIA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Creek Overlord Bonus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_LEADER_TRAIT_CAHOKIA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>-30% gold cost for purchasing cells.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_CAHOKIA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>creek</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>creek</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Creek city-state</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_CAHOKIA_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>creek</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_IMPROVEMENTS_PAGE_IMPROVEMENT_MOUND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Centuries before the arrival of Europeans, Native American civilizations such as the Ardennes, Hopewells, and Mississippians built thousands of mounds across the continent. The purpose of many similar mounds remains a mystery. Some are related to astronomical landmarks, but the greatest of them come from the Cahokia culture.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_IMPROVEMENTS_PAGE_IMPROVEMENT_MOUND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The largest mound in Cahokia is known as &quot;Monk's Mound&quot; as a community of Cathedral monks built settlements on and around it in early colonial times. But what Cahokia residents call it remains unknown. The largest part of the building is 274 meters long, 76 meters wide and approximately 6 meters high. Its clever design minimizes the shrinkage and expansion of the clay, which is why it has been able to survive centuries in areas that are prone to flooding. The monks' mound continued to expand over hundreds of years, until it was completely destroyed by an earthquake and the entire city was abandoned.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_IMPROVEMENTS_PAGE_IMPROVEMENT_MOUND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Because there were no written or inscribed records in the Cahokia culture, almost no information survives about the purpose of the large mound. Through the study of archaeological evidence at the site, experts speculate that the mound was once an important part of Cahokia's religious site.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_IMPROVEMENTS_PAGE_IMPROVEMENT_MOUND_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In this MOD, because the city-state was renamed Creek, the [Cahokia Mound] here was renamed [Mississippi Mound]. And because the Creeks suffered from the westward expansion movement, after considering the actual situation and the needs of the Mod, I decided to modify the ability bonus of this city-state. Due to limited technology, it is impossible to restore the bloody suffering suffered by the Creeks. Time and suffering have made it this way.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_WHCE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Crouching Tiger Charn</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_FLWG_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wind Wolf Wingo·Qitumaru</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_WHCE_1_ACTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Landing land units in the same cell does not end the turn.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_WHCE_2_ACTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ignore river obstacles when moving and attacking.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_WHCE_3_ACTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>And restore health after taking action.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_FLWG_1_ACTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Causes land units in the same cell to ignore area control when moving.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_FLWG_2_ACTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>And ignore the obstacles of terrain when moving,</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_FLWG_3_ACTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Attacking simultaneously does not end the turn.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_WHCE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Crouching Tiger Charn, whose surname is no longer known, was originally a heroic jaguar warrior of the Aztec Empire, renowned for his outstanding military courage and personal character. However, during an exploration in North America, he was questioned and persecuted by his companions, and was eventually forced to fall into the Mississippi River. Legend has it that while going down the river, he unexpectedly met a young girl called the [Son of God] (also known as Ji De), and her guardian Wind Wolf Winde.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_WHCE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Facing the unknown continent of North America, Crouching Tiger Charn showed courage and humility. He did not complain, but in order to find a new home in this strange land, he explored this wild land with [Son of God] Ji De.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_WHCE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In the end, Charn the Crouching Tiger surrendered to Leso, the most powerful monarch in North America, and became a loyal general of the Kedokiya Empire. In a battle in the lower Mississippi River Basin, with his outstanding command and military vision, he successfully intercepted the main force of the Jingkan people in the &quot;Battle of Tennessee&quot;, and skillfully used the river advantage to counterattack the enemy's attack. They attacked from a flank and achieved a double victory over the Jingkansheng and Fuaibulu people.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_WHCE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] After the Kedokiya Empire established its hegemony in North America, Crouching Tiger Charn was appointed as the admiral of Chitimacha, responsible for monitoring the safety of the empire's sea routes and ensuring the smooth transportation of supplies and military units. His resourcefulness and loyalty have allowed him to rise to prominence in the empire, guarding the territory of the Kedokiya Empire. However, some people believe that Crouching Tiger Charn, as a famous general who has fought on land all year round, was reduced to a &quot;border admiral&quot; with no achievements due to the [Battle of Tennessee]. The suspicion of &quot;foreign generals&quot;. But no matter what, he is almost impeccable as a general.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_FLWG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Wind Wolf Wingo Kidumaru, a wandering hero from Chisikuang, is said to be the strong guard of [Son of God] Ji De. As [Son of God] Ji De toured the North American continent, she bravely escorted [Son of God] Ji De to spread knowledge, fought wild beasts and murderers in dangerous situations many times, and foiled many conspiracies against [Son of God] Ji De. So much so that she is regarded as a patron saint of wisdom and courage.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_FLWG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]According to historical records, Wind Wolf Wengo was once the daughter of Qisikuang's female chief - Tianji Xing Qitumaru. She chose to take risks because she was dissatisfied with the easy life. Through arduous experience, she accumulated profound skills and reputation, and eventually became loyal to Lesuo, the monarch of the Kdokiya Empire.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_FLWG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] As a female warrior, Wind Wolf Wenge specializes in running tactics and led the troops to demonstrate outstanding breakthrough capabilities on the battlefield. Her guerrilla tactics became the key to victory, and she followed the empire's strategic guidelines in the north and south. No matter whether it was highlands, woods or swamps, they could not stop the actions of the troops under her leadership.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_GREATPEOPLE_PAGE_GREAT_PERSON_INDIVIDUAL_FLWG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Due to his outstanding military talents, Wingo the Wind Wolf and Charn the Crouching Tiger have equal status, and are known as the top generals of the Kdokiya Empire. Obviously, in people's hearts today, the Wind Wolf Wingo as the patron saint is more well-known to every household. Every New Year or Sunday, her portrait will be hung on the door as a folk tradition, which means like the Chinese door god - bringing everything together. Evil is kept out.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_JMQS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Death Knight</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dragon Rider Support</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Can move [ICON_Movement] after attacking, +10 [ICON_Strength] combat strength against non-cavalry land military units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_LQS2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dragon Rider Support</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_LQS2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+10 [ICON_Strength] combat strength against non-cavalry land military units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Screening treatment</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Including itself, adjacent friendly units have an additional +5 [ICON_Damaged] health when recovering.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Showdown</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+10 [ICON_Strength] combat strength when fighting cavalry units</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>first aid card</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Including itself, adjacent friendly units have an additional +10 [ICON_Damaged] health when recovering.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS5_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Till death do us part</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS5_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Allows one additional attack per round</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS6_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Strong horse and sharp soldiers</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JMQS6_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Movement [ICON_Movement] ignores terrain obstacles; if you suppress the enemy when attacking, it will be pushed back one cell. If the enemy has no way to retreat, it will take additional damage.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_CLASS_JSYS_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A hero with hundreds of refinements</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS1_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Adventures</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS1_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Movement [ICON_Movement] and vision are not obstructed by terrain, movement across rivers is not affected and combat is not at a disadvantage, boarding a ship does not end the turn, cliffs can be climbed, and invisible units can be detected.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS2_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Veterans never die</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS2_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Injury does not affect combat effectiveness. After winning the battle, 20 points of [ICON_Damaged] health will be restored.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS3_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lead by example</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS3_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ignore enemy area control, +5 [ICON_Strength] combat power when defending</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS4_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ambitious</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS4_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Even if you have taken action, you can still restore health. The restored health is not affected by neutral or hostile areas. +5 [ICON_Strength] combat strength.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS5_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Aiming for a thousand miles</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PROMOTION_JSYS5_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+10 [ICON_Strength] combat strength, +1 movement strength when escorting. Share your mobility with the escorted unit.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
